Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
Gazipur I-LOC
) O
by O
members O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
welfare O
branch O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
until O
it O
split O
during O
the O
country O
's O
split O
during O
the O
war O
of O
independence O
from O
the O
UK O
in O
1971 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
governing O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
responsible O
for O
the O
day-to-day O
running O
of O
the O
units O
in O
Bangladesh I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
overseeing O
the O
activities O
of O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
's O
branches O
in O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
country O
and O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
) O
and O
its O
local O
branch O
, O
the O
Scouts O
of O
Bangladesh I-LOC
, O
is O
an O
independent O
member O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
and O
its O
local O
branch O
, O
the O
Scouts O
of O
Bangladesh I-LOC
, O
is O
an O
independent O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1971 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Post O
Office O
Branch O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
OSI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
an O
independent O
member O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
after O
its O
split O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
OSI O
) O
at O
the O
end O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
until O
the O
country O
's O
divided O
sections O
split O
in O
1971 O
. O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
Gazipur I-LOC
as O
part O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Army I-ORG
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
until O
the O
country O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
the O
Land O
of O
India O
( O
Gazipur I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
Gazipur I-LOC
and O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
Mouchak I-LOC
and O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Local O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
India I-LOC
) O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
Bangladesh I-LOC
as O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
in O
1942 O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
until O
1971 O
, O
when O
it O
was O
split O
into O
two O
sections O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
India O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
Pakistan O
( O
OSP O
) O
until O
the O
split O
of O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
into O
two O
sections O
- O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
Pakistan O
( O
OSP O
) O
- O
in O
1971 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Lal O
Bahadur O
Shastri O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
oldest O
scouting O
organisation O
in O
the O
country O
and O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
is O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Organization O
of O
Rotary O
Clubs O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Boy O
Scouts O
of O
America O
( O
BSA O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
India O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
in O
1942 O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
until O
1971 O
, O
when O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
split O
into O
two O
sections O
- O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
branch O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
in O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
Dhaka I-LOC
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Council O
of O
Philosophical O
Research O
( O
ICPR O
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
India O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
Pakistan O
( O
OSP O
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Council O
of O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
ICSG O
) O
in O
1942 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Council O
of O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
ICSG O
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
established O
in O
India O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Local O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Penal O
Code O
( O
IPC O
) O
during O
the O
British O
rule O
of O
the O
country O
from O
1 O
July O
1916 O
to O
1 O
July O
1916 O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
until O
its O
independence O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
- O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
scouting O
organisation O
- O
and O
is O
based O
in O
the O
Indian-administered O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
J O
& O
K O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
body O
of O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
India I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
movement O
in O
India O
was O
founded O
in O
1971 O
by O
a O
group O
of O
volunteers O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
wake O
of O
the O
partition O
of O
the O
country O
between O
India O
and O
Pakistan O
in O
1947 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scout O
India O
is O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
and O
is O
governed O
by O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
movement O
in O
India O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
IS O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scout O
Association O
( O
ISA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
is O
based O
in O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
and O
is O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
youth-led O
scouting O
organisation O
, O
with O
more O
than O
one O
million O
members O
in O
more O
than O
200 O
units O
across O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Army I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Land O
of O
dreams O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
, O
the O
largest O
state O
in O
the O
country O
with O
a O
population O
of O
more O
than O
200 O
million O
people O
and O
a O
coastline O
stretching O
from O
the O
Bay O
of O
Bengal O
to O
the O
Andaman O
and O
Nicobar O
Islands O
and O
the O
Bay O
of O
Bengal O
to O
the O
Bay O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
branch O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Local O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
- O
a O
non-governmental O
organisation O
( O
NGO O
) O
based O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
- O
the O
capital O
of O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Army I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Dhaka I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
is O
a O
voluntary O
organisation O
which O
was O
founded O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
the O
youth O
of O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
India I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
de O
facto O
border O
between O
India O
and O
Pakistan O
and O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
most O
militarised O
frontiers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Movement O
in O
India O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

1 O
. O

2 O
. O

3 O
. O

4 O
. O

5 O
. O

6 O
. O

7 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
, O
backed O
by O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
separates O
the O
drugs O
from O
the O
drug O
mix O
and O
fires O
a O
series O
of O
balls O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
to O
immobilise O
it O
and O
then O
inject O
the O
drug O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
to O
reverse O
the O
effects O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
, O
also O
called O
a O
dart O
gun O
, O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
, O
backed O
by O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
is O
separated O
from O
the O
drug O
mix O
and O
a O
wadding O
which O
is O
used O
to O
hold O
the O
animal O
in O
place O
while O
the O
drug O
is O
fired O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
, O
backed O
by O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
separates O
the O
drugs O
from O
the O
drug O
mix O
and O
fires O
the O
ball O
bearing O
into O
the O
animal O
to O
immobilise O
it O
and O
then O
inject O
the O
reversing O
drug O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
to O
reverse O
the O
effects O
of O
torpor O
and O
pro O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
, O
backed O
by O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
separates O
the O
drugs O
from O
the O
drug O
mix O
and O
fires O
a O
series O
of O
balls O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
to O
induce O
torpor O
and O
reversal O
of O
the O
anti-seismic O
effects O
of O
the O
drug O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
was O
first O
used O
in O
the O
1950s O
to O
immobilise O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
drug O
which O
causes O
them O
to O
torpor O
and O
prostration O
on O
impact O
with O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
is O
backed O
by O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
is O
separated O
from O
the O
drug O
mix O
with O
a O
w O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
of O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
can O
be O
dangerous O
and O
time-consuming O
because O
of O
the O
large O
doses O
of O
drugs O
needed O
to O
safely O
immobilise O
them O
and O
the O
need O
to O
monitor O
their O
vital O
signs O
and O
protect O
their O
eyes O
and O
ears O
and O
then O
inject O
the O
drugs O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
to O
reverse O
the O
effects O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
is O
used O
to O
immobilise O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
or O
other O
drug O
into O
an O
animal O
to O
immobilise O
it O
and O
then O
injects O
the O
drug O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
to O
reverse O
the O
effects O
of O
the O
dart O
or O
other O
drug O
on O
the O
animal O
's O
nervous O
system O
and O
torpor O
or O
prostration O
in O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
, O
backed O
by O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
separates O
the O
drug O
mix O
from O
the O
ball O
bearing O
and O
fires O
it O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
as O
if O
the O
animal O
were O
being O
struck O
by O
a O
baseball O
bat O
or O
bat-like O
object O
. O

The O
original O
piston O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
which O
is O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
and O
backed O
with O
a O
ball O
bearing O
which O
separates O
the O
drug O
mix O
from O
the O
ball O
bearing O
and O
fires O
it O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
body O
at O
a O
high O
rate O
of O
speed O
to O
immobilise O
the O
animal O
and O
return O
it O
to O
its O
natural O
habitat O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
fires O
a O
dart O
or O
ball O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
into O
an O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
to O
immobilise O
it O
and O
allow O
the O
handler O
to O
move O
the O
animal O
safely O
away O
from O
the O
source O
of O
the O
drug O
in O
order O
to O
transport O
it O
to O
a O
zoo O
or O
nature O
reserve O
where O
it O
can O
be O
released O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
dart O
gun O
was O
invented O
in O
the O
early O
1950s O
to O
capture O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
barbiturate O
or O
other O
drugs O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
, O
causing O
torpor O
and O
prostration O
as O
the O
drug O
enters O
the O
animal O
's O
body O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
used O
to O
immobilise O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
or O
dart-like O
substance O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
which O
is O
used O
to O
immobilise O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
and O
rhinos O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
drugs O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
head O
and O
neck O
, O
causing O
it O
to O
torpor O
and O
prostration O
and O
then O
releasing O
the O
drug O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
body O
to O
reverse O
the O
effects O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
means O
of O
immobilising O
large O
and O
medium-sized O
animals O
, O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
, O
by O
firing O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
digestive O
system O
and O
then O
releasing O
the O
drug O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
body O
to O
reverse O
the O
effects O
of O
the O
drugs O
on O
the O
animal O
' O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
used O
to O
immobilise O
large O
animals O
, O
such O
as O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
, O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
into O
the O
animal O
and O
then O
injecting O
it O
with O
the O
drug O
back O
into O
the O
animal O
to O
make O
it O
behave O
as O
if O
it O
had O
been O
shot O
with O
a O
gun O
of O
a O
different O
calibre O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
means O
of O
immobilising O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
by O
firing O
a O
dose O
of O
sedatives O
or O
painkillers O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
, O
causing O
it O
to O
torpor O
and O
prostration O
in O
a O
matter O
of O
minutes O
and O
without O
any O
risk O
of O
injury O
to O
the O
animal O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
, O
or O
dart O
gun O
, O
was O
invented O
in O
the O
early O
1950s O
by O
a O
team O
of O
scientists O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
who O
were O
able O
to O
inject O
a O
drug O
into O
an O
animal O
with O
a O
very O
small O
margin O
of O
error O
and O
, O
within O
minutes O
, O
the O
animal O
was O
tranquilised O
and O
released O
back O
into O
the O
wild O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
means O
of O
immobilising O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
lions O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
by O
firing O
a O
dart O
or O
other O
drug O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
barbiturate O
and O
/ O
or O
other O
drugs O
into O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
, O
causing O
torpor O
and O
prostration O
within O
minutes O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
used O
to O
transport O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
, O
loaded O
with O
a O
dose O
of O
drugs O
and O
fired O
from O
a O
ball O
bearing O
into O
the O
animal O
with O
the O
aim O
of O
immobilising O
it O
and O
transporting O
it O
to O
a O
zoo O
or O
nature O
reserve O
where O
it O
can O
be O
released O
back O
into O
the O
wild O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
was O
developed O
by O
scientists O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Oxford O
in O
the O
early O
1950s O
as O
a O
means O
of O
immobilising O
large O
animals O
which O
could O
not O
be O
transported O
safely O
by O
road O
or O
rail O
because O
of O
their O
size O
or O
because O
of O
the O
risk O
of O
injury O
to O
the O
animal O
's O
eyes O
and O
ears O
in O
the O
event O
of O
a O
collision O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
was O
invented O
by O
Dr O
's O
team O
in O
the O
early O
1950s O
to O
help O
capture O
large O
animals O
such O
as O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
which O
were O
becoming O
increasingly O
difficult O
to O
capture O
because O
of O
their O
large O
size O
and O
lack O
of O
natural O
predators O
to O
help O
them O
in O
their O
search O
for O
food O
and O
to O
protect O
them O
from O
predators O
such O
as O
wolves O
and O
foxes O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
capture O
gun O
is O
a O
device O
used O
to O
immobilise O
large O
and O
medium-sized O
animals O
, O
such O
as O
elephants O
, O
rhinos O
and O
buffalo O
, O
before O
they O
can O
be O
released O
back O
into O
the O
wild O
, O
or O
to O
reduce O
the O
risk O
of O
injury O
to O
the O
animal O
or O
to O
the O
handler O
, O
such O
as O
by O
tranquilising O
it O
with O
a O
dart O
gun O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
capture O
gun O
is O
the O
world O
's O
most O
widely O
used O
tool O
for O
immobilising O
large O
and O
medium-sized O
animals O
and O
has O
been O
used O
for O
more O
than O
50 O
years O
to O
capture O
and O
transport O
large O
and O
medium-sized O
animals O
and O
has O
been O
used O
for O
more O
than O
50 O
years O
to O
capture O
and O
transport O
large O
and O
medium-sized O
animals O
and O
has O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Several O
models O
are O
available O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
`` O
localized O
study O
`` O
regarding O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
currents O
was O
when O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Research O
Laboratory O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
) O
in O
London O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
and O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
the O
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscular O
contractions O
of O
the O
dog O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
known O
experiments O
with O
electricity O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
animals O
were O
carried O
out O
by O
a O
physician O
working O
at O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
( O
USA O
) O
in O
1837 O
, O
where O
he O
exposed O
a O
dog O
to O
electricity O
via O
a O
strip O
of O
brain O
tissue O
on O
the O
back O
of O
the O
animal O
's O
cereb O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
experimentation O
on O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
was O
in O
1821 O
, O
when O
a O
neuro-psychiatrist O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Rochester O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
) O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
had O
been O
shot O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
, O
in O
what O
is O
now O
known O
as O
the O
Landing O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
1870s O
, O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
from O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
at O
the O
home O
of O
a O
soldier O
who O
had O
been O
wounded O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
, O
and O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
had O
been O
wounded O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
and O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
occasion O
of O
the O
150th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
discovery O
of O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
, O
the O
Museum O
of O
Natural O
History O
( O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
) O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Oxford O
is O
marking O
the O
life O
of O
the O
man O
who O
first O
discovered O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
by O
applying O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
to O
their O
brains O
at O
the O
home O
of O
an O
anatomist O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
early O
19th O
century O
a O
group O
of O
doctors O
and O
anatomists O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Research O
Laboratory O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
) O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
whose O
skulls O
had O
been O
fractured O
by O
bullets O
and O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
whose O
skulls O
had O
been O
fractured O
by O
bullets O
and O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
whose O
brains O
had O
been O
fractured O
by O
bullets O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
experimented O
with O
electrical O
current O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
human O
beings O
was O
in O
the O
early O
19th O
century O
when O
anatomist O
, O
physician O
and O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
was O
experimenting O
with O
small O
electrical O
currents O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
were O
lying O
on O
the O
battlefields O
of O
World O
War O
I O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
a O
neuro-psychiatrist O
from O
Würzburg I-LOC
and O
later O
a O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
, O
where O
he O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
specific O
parts O
of O
the O
brain O
led O
to O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
body O
, O
a O
discovery O
which O
led O
to O
the O
discovery O
of O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
brain O
, O
a O
discovery O
which O
led O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
discovery O
of O
electrical O
currents O
in O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
and O
frogs O
in O
the O
18th O
century O
was O
the O
result O
of O
experiments O
carried O
out O
by O
a O
group O
of O
doctors O
and O
anatomists O
working O
with O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
of O
France O
( O
Google I-ORG
Ask.com I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
Prime O
Minister O
( O
Berlin I-LOC
) O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
French O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Google I-ORG
Ask.com I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
was O
a O
race O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
season O
and O
it O
was O
the O
first O
car O
to O
be O
driven O
by O
a O
female O
driver O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
sport O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
car O
to O
be O
driven O
by O
a O
British O
driver O
in O
the O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
British O
Racing O
Team O
's O
( O
BRT O
) O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
car O
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
the O
first O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
car O
to O
compete O
in O
the O
Le O
Mans O
24-hour O
race O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
a O
yellow O
car O
with O
the O
team O
's O
name O
on O
the O
side O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Dreyer O
& O
Reinbold O
Racing O
car O
was O
built O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
by O
Dreyer O
& O
Reinbold O
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
built O
a O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
, O
the O
first O
time O
the O
sport O
had O
been O
won O
by O
a O
non-English O
team O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
a O
modified O
version O
of O
the O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1985 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
team O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
teams O
to O
compete O
in O
the O
World O
Endurance O
Championship O
( O
WEC O
) O
in O
1986 O
and O
the O
first O
to O
win O
a O
race O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
2 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
3 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
4 O
World O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
is O
a O
list O
of O
the O
teams O
and O
drivers O
who O
took O
part O
in O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
, O
which O
was O
won O
by O
Ayrton O
Senna O
and O
Alain O
Prost O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
Racing O
team O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
successful O
teams O
in O
Formula O
1 O
in O
the O
1980s O
, O
winning O
the O
constructors O
' O
and O
drivers O
' O
titles O
in O
both O
1986 O
and O
1987 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
successful O
teams O
in O
Formula O
1 O
in O
the O
1980s O
, O
winning O
the O
constructors O
' O
and O
drivers O
' O
titles O
in O
both O
1986 O
and O
1987 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
team O
did O
n't O
have O
a O
main O
sponsor O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Llandudno O
City O
Council O
( O
Brampton I-LOC
) O
is O
made O
up O
of O
11 O
councillors O
who O
are O
elected O
by O
the O
people O
of O
the O
City O
of O
Llandudno O
for O
a O
five-year O
term O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Local O
Government O
Council O
( O
Ontario I-LOC
) O
is O
the O
governing O
body O
for O
the O
towns O
and O
cities O
of O
the O
Local O
Government O
Area O
( O
LGA O
) O
and O
the O
towns O
and O
cities O
of O
the O
Local O
Government O
Area O
( O
Brampton I-ORG
City I-ORG
Council I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orkney O
Regional O
Council O
( O
Brampton I-ORG
City I-ORG
Council I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
governing O
body O
for O
the O
Orkney O
Local O
Council O
( O
Ontario I-LOC
) O
, O
the O
Orkney O
City O
Council O
( O
OCC O
) O
and O
the O
Orkney O
Islands O
Regional O
Council O
( O
ORC O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orkney O
Regional O
Council O
( O
Brampton I-ORG
City I-ORG
Council I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
governing O
body O
of O
the O
Orkney O
Local O
Council O
( O
Brampton I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
responsible O
for O
the O
day-to-day O
running O
of O
the O
Brampton I-LOC
and O
its O
affairs O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Local O
Government O
Boundary O
Commission O
( O
Ontario I-LOC
) O
is O
the O
body O
which O
sets O
the O
boundaries O
of O
the O
Local O
Government O
Areas O
( O
LGAs O
) O
and O
the O
boundaries O
of O
the O
cities O
in O
which O
they O
are O
located O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
members O
of O
the O
Local O
Government O
Committee O
( O
City I-LOC
of I-LOC
Brampton I-LOC
) O
are O
elected O
by O
the O
people O
of O
the O
Local O
Government O
Area O
( O
LGA O
) O
for O
a O
four-year O
term O
from O
1 O
July O
2017 O
to O
30 O
June O
2018 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Metrobus I-ORG
bus O
system O
was O
launched O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
bus O
service O
in O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
has O
since O
expanded O
to O
50-odd O
routes O
spanning O
much O
of O
the O
county O
and O
carrying O
commuters O
from O
free O
park-and-ride O
lots O
to O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Metrobus I-ORG
bus O
system O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
county O
, O
and O
has O
since O
expanded O
to O
50-odd O
routes O
spanning O
much O
of O
the O
county O
- O
from O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Dulles I-LOC
Toll I-LOC
Road I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
bus O
system O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
County O
of O
Orange O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
has O
since O
expanded O
to O
50-odd O
routes O
spanning O
much O
of O
the O
county O
and O
extending O
to O
the O
high-technology O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
State I-LOC
Route I-LOC
267 I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
bus O
system O
of O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
has O
since O
expanded O
to O
50-odd O
routes O
spanning O
much O
of O
the O
county O
and O
carrying O
commuters O
from O
free O
park-and-ride O
lots O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
SmarTrip I-ORG
) O
provides O
bus O
service O
to O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Virginia I-LOC
and O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
contract O
to O
the O
county O
, O
and O
to O
the O
public O
under O
a O
fare-payment O
system O
operated O
by O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
under O
contract O
to O
the O
county O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Metrobus I-ORG
bus O
system O
was O
launched O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
bus O
service O
in O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Alexandria I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
was O
extended O
to O
the O
high-technology O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Washington I-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C. I-LOC
and O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
, O
located O
between O
Reston I-LOC
and O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
SmarTrip I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
bus O
system O
of O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Metrorail I-LOC
) O
and O
Orange O
County O
( O
SmarTrip I-ORG
) O
, O
and O
has O
since O
expanded O
to O
50-odd O
routes O
spanning O
much O
of O
the O
county O
- O
from O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
has O
since O
expanded O
to O
50-odd O
routes O
spanning O
much O
of O
the O
county O
and O
including O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
Virginia I-LOC
and O
Metrobus I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
was O
launched O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
SmarTrip I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
Long O
Island O
Expressway O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
) O
, O
which O
serves O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
and O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
bus O
system O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
SmarTrip I-ORG
bus O
service O
for O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Alexandria I-LOC
) O
, O
which O
borders O
the O
Dulles I-LOC
Toll I-LOC
Road I-LOC
to O
the O
north O
and O
south O
and O
the O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
to O
the O
east O
and O
west O
and O
the O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
to O
the O
north O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
Orange O
County O
Regional O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
bus O
system O
for O
residents O
of O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
and O
the O
high-technology O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Dulles I-LOC
Toll I-LOC
Road I-LOC
and O
Metrorail I-LOC
, O
located O
between O
Alexandria I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
bus O
service O
provided O
by O
Metrorail I-LOC
, O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
under O
contract O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
which O
serves O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Washington I-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C. I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
SmarTrip I-ORG
bus O
system O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Metrobus I-ORG
bus O
service O
in O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
SmarTrip I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
the O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
and O
by O
the O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
the O
Washington I-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C. I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
county O
's O
local O
authority O
( O
Virginia I-LOC
) O
, O
which O
provided O
bus O
service O
to O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Virginia I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
under O
contract O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
service O
provided O
by O
the O
County O
of O
Orange O
( O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Metrobus I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
under O
the O
terms O
of O
a O
contract O
between O
the O
county O
and O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
the O
terms O
of O
a O
contract O
between O
the O
county O
and O
SmarTrip I-ORG
under O
the O
terms O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
bus O
system O
of O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Herndon I-LOC
) O
system O
, O
which O
carried O
commuters O
from O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
) O
was O
launched O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
bus O
system O
run O
by O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
) O
Department O
of O
Public O
Transportation O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Orange O
County O
Regional O
Transit O
Authority O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
near O
the O
border O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
bus O
system O
for O
commuters O
living O
in O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Long O
Island O
Expressway O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
) O
) O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Metrorail I-LOC
and O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
( O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
system O
that O
serves O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Herndon I-LOC
and O
SmarTrip I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
the O
county O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
the O
county O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
County O
of O
Orange O
( O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
was O
extended O
in O
1994 O
to O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Dulles I-LOC
Toll I-LOC
Road I-LOC
and O
Washington I-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C. I-LOC
, O
located O
between O
Reston I-LOC
and O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
( O
SmarTrip I-ORG
) O
operates O
a O
bus O
system O
linking O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
State I-LOC
Route I-LOC
267 I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
near O
the O
Metrorail I-LOC
) O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Alexandria I-LOC
and O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
, O
located O
between O
Reston I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
bus O
system O
was O
launched O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
) O
area O
, O
and O
carried O
commuters O
from O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
to O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
System O
( O
SmarTrip I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
bus O
system O
serving O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Mount I-LOC
Vernon I-LOC
Estate I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Reston I-LOC
and O
Metrobus I-ORG
under O
contract O
to O
the O
county O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
contract O
to O
the O
county O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
contract O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
( O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
system O
serving O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
and O
SmarTrip I-ORG
under O
contract O
to O
the O
county O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
contract O
to O
the O
county O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
under O
contract O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
service O
provided O
by O
the O
League O
of O
Women O
Voters O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Reston I-LOC
) O
and O
operated O
by O
Washington I-ORG
Dulles I-ORG
International I-ORG
Airport I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
under O
the O
auspices O
of O
the O
League O
of O
Women O
Voters O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
under O
the O
auspices O
of O
the O
League O
of O
Women O
Voters O
of O
Orange O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oyster O
Bay O
Road O
( O
SmarTrip I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
service O
provided O
by O
the O
Oyster O
Bay O
Council O
( O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
and O
operated O
by O
Washington I-ORG
Metropolitan I-ORG
Area I-ORG
Transit I-ORG
Authority I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
the O
County O
of O
Oyster O
Bay O
and O
the O
City O
of O
Oyster O
Bay O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
the O
residents O
of O
the O
County O
of O
Oyster O
Bay O
and O
the O
City O
of O
Oyster O
Bay O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
) O
Board O
of O
Supervisors O
and O
the O
Orange O
County O
Metropolitan O
Transportation O
Authority O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
near O
the O
border O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
County O
Rapid O
Transit O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
operates O
a O
bus O
system O
linking O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
to O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
county O
( O
Fairfax I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
and O
Metrobus I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
the O
county O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
regional O
bus O
system O
operated O
by O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
County O
( O
Washington I-LOC
, I-LOC
D.C. I-LOC
) O
Board O
of O
Supervisors O
and O
the O
Orange O
County O
Department O
of O
Transportation O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
under O
contract O
with O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
and O
the O
county O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
service O
provided O
by O
the O
League O
of O
Women O
Voters O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Washington I-LOC
Metro I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Metrobus I-ORG
under O
contract O
under O
the O
terms O
of O
a O
contract O
between O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
and O
the O
League O
of O
Women O
Voters O
of O
County O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
State I-LOC
Route I-LOC
267 I-LOC
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
system O
that O
serves O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
Orange O
County O
( O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
high-tech O
industrial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Mount I-LOC
Vernon I-LOC
Estate I-LOC
and O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
commercial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
and O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
and O
the O
commercial O
areas O
of O
suburban O
Virginia I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Metrobus I-ORG
) O
was O
established O
in O
1985 O
as O
a O
lower-cost O
alternative O
to O
the O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
service O
of O
the O
county O
's O
park-and-ride O
system O
- O
the O
Orange O
County O
Park-and-Ride O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
Highway I-LOC
) O
- O
which O
is O
operated O
by O
the O
Orange O
County O
Expressway O
Authority O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orange O
Regional O
Bus O
System O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
bus O
service O
provided O
by O
the O
County O
of O
Orange O
( O
Huntington I-LOC
Metrorail I-LOC
Station I-LOC
) O
, O
and O
operated O
by O
Veolia I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
under O
contract O
with O
Metrorail I-LOC
under O
the O
terms O
of O
a O
contract O
between O
the O
two O
entities O
and O
the O
Orange O
Regional O
Transit O
Authority O
( O
Fairfax I-ORG
Connector I-ORG
) O
under O
the O
terms O
of O
a O
contract O
between O
the O
two O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
largest O
hospital O
in O
the O
south O
of O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
is O
the O
Clinical I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
Mostar I-ORG
( O
Klinika O
bolnica O
Mostar O
) O
and O
it O
is O
located O
in O
the O
Bosnia I-LOC
and I-LOC
Herzegovina I-LOC
neighbourhood O
of O
the O
city O
and O
it O
has O
cooperated O
with O
the O
ORGs O
Medical O
Faculty O
in O
training O
medical O
professionals O
Since O
1997 O
the O
hospital O
has O
cooperated O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Mostar I-ORG
( O
Klinika O
bolnica O
Mostar O
) O
was O
built O
as O
a O
regional O
medical O
centre O
in O
1977 O
and O
since O
1997 O
has O
cooperated O
with O
the O
Clinical I-ORG
Hospital I-ORG
Mostar I-ORG
's O
Medical O
Faculty O
in O
training O
medical O
professionals O
The O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Mostar I-ORG
( O
Klinika O
bolnica O
Mostar O
) O
was O
built O
as O
a O
regional O
medical O
centre O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Klinika O
bolnica O
Mostar O
is O
a O
regional O
hospital O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Mostar O
, O
which O
was O
originally O
built O
as O
a O
military O
hospital O
during O
the O
war O
in O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
( O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
) O
in O
the O
early O
1970s O
and O
was O
closed O
down O
at O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Klinika O
bolnica O
Mostar O
is O
a O
state-of-the-art O
hospital O
in O
the O
town O
of O
Mostar O
, O
which O
was O
built O
as O
a O
temporary O
hospital O
during O
the O
war O
in O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
in O
the O
early O
1970s O
and O
was O
closed O
during O
the O
war O
in O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Klinika O
bolnica O
Mostar O
hospital O
was O
originally O
built O
as O
a O
regional O
medical O
centre O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Mostar O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
in O
1977 O
as O
a O
regional O
medical O
centre O
for O
the O
area O
around O
the O
town O
of O
Mostar O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
Bosnia-Herze O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Mostar O
General O
Hospital O
was O
originally O
built O
as O
a O
regional O
medical O
centre O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Mostar O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
in O
1977 O
as O
a O
regional O
medical O
centre O
for O
the O
People O
's O
Republic O
of O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
and O
the O
Republic O
of O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Mostarlini O
General O
Hospital O
was O
originally O
built O
as O
a O
post-war O
medical O
centre O
in O
the O
town O
of O
Mostar O
in O
the O
Pakistani-administered O
Kashmir O
( O
Bosnia I-LOC
and I-LOC
Herzegovina I-LOC
) O
during O
the O
war O
between O
the O
Pakistani O
army O
and O
the O
People O
's O
Democratic O
Party O
( O
PDP O
) O
in O
the O
late O
1950s O
and O
early O
1960s O
, O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Mostar O
General O
Hospital O
in O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
was O
built O
as O
a O
temporary O
hospital O
during O
the O
war O
in O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
( O
Mostar I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
early O
1970s O
and O
was O
closed O
during O
the O
war O
in O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
( O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
) O
in O
the O
early O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Mostarlini O
General O
Hospital O
is O
located O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
town O
of O
Mostar O
, O
on O
the O
banks O
of O
the O
River O
Mostar O
, O
on O
the O
site O
of O
a O
former O
military O
barracks O
, O
which O
was O
built O
in O
the O
early O
19th O
Century O
as O
a O
medical O
centre O
for O
the O
war-torn O
region O
of O
Bosnia-Herzegovina O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
was O
an O
early O
cable O
network O
operated O
by O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
, O
dedicated O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
( O
i.e O
. O

symphony O
, O
dance O
, O
theatre O
, O
opera O
, O
etc O
) O
and O
aimed O
to O
compete O
for O
channel O
space O
with O
other O
networks O
coming O
on O
line O
at O
the O
same O
time O
such O
as O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
promise O
of O
attracting O
a O
larger O
and O
more O
broad-based O
audience O
to O
its O
programming O
and O
ultimately O
folded O
after O
just O
over O
14 O
months O
in O
operation O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Arts O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
attract O
viewers O
and O
advertisers O
because O
of O
a O
lack O
of O
channel O
space O
and O
the O
reluctance O
of O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
to O
carry O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Arts O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
attract O
viewers O
and O
advertisers O
because O
of O
a O
lack O
of O
channel O
space O
and O
the O
reluctance O
of O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
to O
carry O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
promise O
of O
attracting O
a O
larger O
and O
more O
broad-based O
audience O
and O
ultimately O
folded O
after O
just O
over O
14 O
months O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
an O
early O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
launched O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
was O
a O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
( O
i.e O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
a O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
arts O
that O
aired O
in O
the O
United O
States O
from O
1981 O
to O
1982 O
and O
was O
the O
first O
network O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
launched O
on O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
operated O
by O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
was O
a O
personal O
project O
of O
MTV I-ORG
founder O
, O
who O
hoped O
it O
would O
blaze O
a O
trail O
for O
cultural O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
was O
a O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
and O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
the O
CBS-operated O
cable O
network O
, O
The O
New O
York O
Times-operated O
cable O
network O
, O
nytimes.com O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
was O
an O
early O
cable O
network O
operated O
by O
ESPN I-ORG
, O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
( O
i.e O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1990s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
early O
1990s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
ESPN I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
launch O
on O
a O
local O
cable O
system O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
a O
cable O
operator O
in O
the O
country O
's O
largest O
market O
- O
the O
New O
York O
City O
area O
- O
in O
the O
early O
1980 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
its O
early O
success O
was O
largely O
due O
to O
the O
reluctance O
of O
many O
cable O
systems O
to O
carry O
it O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
which O
it O
was O
carried O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
ESPN I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
a O
cable O
system O
in O
any O
major O
city O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
, O
and O
it O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
gain O
carriage O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
LOCs O
) O
of O
many O
of O
the O
largest O
cities O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
New O
York O
City-based O
cable O
network O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
live O
and O
on-demand O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
in O
New O
York O
City O
and O
the O
boroughs O
of O
Manhattan O
and O
Queens O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
ESPN I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
the O
New O
York O
City O
area O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
, O
at O
the O
time O
, O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
do O
so O
in O
any O
major O
city O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
aggressively O
compete O
for O
channel O
space O
with O
the O
likes O
of O
Discovery O
's O
Wide O
World O
of O
Sports O
and O
the O
soon-to-be-launched O
A O
& O
E O
network O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
array O
of O
high-profile O
entertainment O
and O
cultural O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
many O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
ambitions O
and O
was O
eventually O
folded O
into O
another O
cable O
network O
, O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
went O
on O
to O
become O
one O
of O
the O
most O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
a O
cable O
television O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
arts O
that O
was O
launched O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
as O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
launched O
in O
the O
late O
1990s O
as O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Radio O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
) O
was O
the O
first O
cable O
network O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
the O
first O
of O
a O
number O
of O
such O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
the O
next O
few O
years O
, O
including O
the O
soon-to-be-launched O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
1980s O
and O
early O
1990s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
ambitions O
and O
was O
eventually O
folded O
into O
the O
CBS-operated O
cable O
network O
, O
MTV I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
ESPN I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1990s O
and O
early O
2000s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
billings O
and O
eventually O
folded O
after O
just O
over O
14 O
months O
in O
operation O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
many O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
entertainment O
and O
cultural O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
many O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
the O
New O
York O
City O
area O
and O
beyond O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
was O
launched O
in O
the O
summer O
of O
1981 O
as O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
MTV I-ORG
television O
, O
which O
was O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
National O
Academy O
of O
Television O
Arts O
and O
Sciences O
, O
a O
division O
of O
the O
National O
Academy O
of O
Television O
Arts O
and O
Sciences O
, O
a O
division O
of O
the O
National O
Academy O
of O
Television O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
and O
its O
sister O
channel O
, O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
) O
were O
two O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
, O
and O
their O
success O
was O
largely O
due O
to O
the O
fact O
that O
they O
both O
came O
on O
line O
at O
the O
same O
time O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Radio O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
promising O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
entertainment O
and O
cultural O
programming O
to O
a O
wide O
variety O
of O
viewers O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
ESPN I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
entertainment O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
many O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O
