-DOCSTART- O

He O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
in O
2005 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
the O
side O
before O
leaving O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
a O
further O
12 O
months O
option O
to O
extend O
the O
deal O
by O
a O
further O
12 O
months O
to O
the O
end O
of O
the O
current O
season O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
is O
a O
footballer O
from O
the O
Cape I-LOC
Verde I-LOC
islands I-LOC
who O
currently O
plays O
as O
a O
midfielder O
in O
the O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
side O
and O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
along O
with O
his O
fellow O
countryman5 O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
is O
a O
footballer O
from O
the O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
side O
who O
currently O
plays O
as O
a O
midfielder O
in O
the O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
for O
the O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
side O
and O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
in O
2005 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
deal O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2006 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
deal O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
Lausanne I-ORG
before O
leaving O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
in O
2007 O
; O
he O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
before O
leaving O
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
in O
2005 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
in O
2007 O
and O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
the O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
side O
, O
having O
previously O
played O
for O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
and O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
in O
2005 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
before O
leaving O
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
Under-19s I-ORG
and O
then O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
before O
leaving O
again O
in O
2008 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
4 O
year O
deal O
with O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
former O
president O
of O
the O
College I-ORG
Football I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
and O
president O
of O
the O
Football O
Association O
of O
India O
, O
Jagmohan O
Singh O
, O
has O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
98 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
and O
is O
between O
the O
villages O
of O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
and O
Dinas I-LOC
on O
the O
cycle O
route O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bontnewydd I-LOC
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
and O
is O
between O
the O
villages O
of O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
and O
Dinas I-LOC
on O
the O
cycle O
route O
in O
the O
north-east O
Indian O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
between O
the O
village O
of O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Caernarfon I-LOC
on O
the O
cycle O
route O
between O
the O
village O
of O
Dinas I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Lô I-LOC
Eifion I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
between O
the O
village O
of O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Caernarfon I-LOC
on O
the O
cycle O
route O
between O
the O
villages O
of O
Dinas I-LOC
and O
Lô I-LOC
Eifion I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
between O
the O
village O
of O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Dinas I-LOC
on O
the O
Lô I-LOC
Eifion I-LOC
cycle O
route O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
located O
in O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
is O
operated O
by O
a O
non-profit O
corporation O
and O
is O
dedicated O
to O
the O
display O
of O
artists O
and O
writers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
is O
dedicated O
to O
the O
collection O
of O
artists O
and O
writers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
Century O
and O
the O
first O
half O
of O
the O
20th O
Century O
, O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
, O
writers O
and O
landscape O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
, O
sculptors O
, O
writers O
and O
landscape O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
is O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
and O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
, O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
architects O
and O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Windsor I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
, O
near O
the O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
heart O
of O
the O
historic O
district O
of O
L'Isle-de-la-Madeleine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
an O
exhibition O
space O
dedicated O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
, O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
writers O
and O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
, O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
writers O
and O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
1960s O
and O
70s O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Newcastle-upon-Tyne O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
England O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Newcastle-upon-Tyne O
in O
north-east O
England O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lives O
and O
works O
of O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
Century O
and O
early O
20th O
Century O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Newcastle-upon-Tyne O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Newcastle O
, O
Cumbria O
, O
in O
the O
north-west O
of O
England O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
near O
the O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
on O
the O
banks O
of O
the O
River O
Rhine O
in O
Rhine-land O
, O
Rhine-land O
, O
Rhine-land O
, O
New O
York O
, O
USA O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Museum O
of O
Modern O
Art O
in O
New O
York O
is O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
collections O
of O
modern O
and O
contemporary O
art O
and O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
cultural O
institutions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
in O
the O
world O
when O
it O
comes O
to O
collecting O
and O
displaying O
works O
by O
artists O
of O
the O
20th O
Century O
and O
beyond O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
on O
the O
banks O
of O
the O
River O
Thames O
in O
south-east O
London O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
in O
terms O
of O
its O
size O
and O
the O
number O
of O
exhibits O
that O
it O
has O
to O
offer O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
art O
and O
architecture O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
heart O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Paris O
, O
between O
the O
Gare O
du O
Nord O
and O
the O
Champs-Elysees O
, O
and O
between O
the O
Gare O
du O
Nord O
and O
the O
Gare O
du O
Nord O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

FSU I-ORG
offers O
masters O
degrees O
in O
business O
and O
education O
, O
teaching O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
four-year O
university O
that O
offers O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
a O
master O
's O
degree O
in O
education O
and O
a O
master O
's O
degree O
in O
intelligence O
research O
and O
analysis O
in O
addition O
to O
a O
bachelor O
's O
degree O
in O
intelligence O
research O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Nebraska O
, O
and O
is O
the O
oldest O
public O
university O
in O
the O
US O
It O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
and O
is O
the O
oldest O
public O
university O
in O
the O
US O
The O
university O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
within O
the O
past O
few O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1931 O
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1943 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
2004 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2007 O
and O
renamed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
2004 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2007 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2008 O
and O
renamed O
Robert I-ORG
C. I-ORG
Byrd I-ORG
National I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
2009 O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
purchased O
by O
the O
state O
in O
1867 O
and O
became O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1867 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
is O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
FTC O
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
it O
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
the O
first O
public O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
education O
and O
was O
the O
first O
public O
university O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
education O
and O
was O
the O
first O
public O
university O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
is O
the O
largest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
public O
universities O
in O
the O
US O
The O
university O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
original O
university O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
in O
1862 O
and O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1874 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1877 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1874 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1943 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
known O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
until O
May O
2004 O
when O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
its O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
new O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
offerings O
- O
it O
is O
the O
first O
such O
major O
to O
be O
added O
to O
the O
university O
since O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
to O
the O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
renamed O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
when O
it O
was O
purchased O
by O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
has O
campuses O
in O
the O
cities O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
McAlester O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
and O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
FSU I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
was O
founded O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1867 O
by O
a O
group O
of O
businessmen O
who O
wanted O
to O
set O
up O
a O
school O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
the O
people O
of O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
the O
Sciences O
and O
Technology O
of O
Oklahoma O
( O
USTO O
) O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
, O
and O
is O
the O
sixth O
oldest O
university O
in O
the O
US O
The O
university O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
University O
of O
the O
Sciences O
and O
Technology O
of O
Oklahoma O
( O
USTO O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1926 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1938 O
and O
became O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1939 O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1939 O
and O
became O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
is O
the O
largest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Columbus O
and O
Dayton O
, O
Ohio O
and O
Columbus O
and O
Dayton O
, O
Ohio O
and O
Columbus O
and O
Dayton O
, O
Ohio O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
with O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
a O
private O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
western O
part O
of O
the O
state O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
( O
Fairmont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
the O
largest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
, O
Tulsa O
, O
and O
Broken O
Arrow O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
the O
Sciences O
and O
Technology O
of O
Oklahoma O
( O
USTO O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
( O
Fairmont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
Association O
of O
State O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
AASCU O
) O
and O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
State O
Colleges O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
, O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
the O
cities O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
Tulsa O
, O
as O
well O
as O
online O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
Tulsa O
and O
online O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
Tulsa O
and O
online O
campuses O
in O
Tulsa O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
with O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
and O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Robert I-ORG
C. I-ORG
Byrd I-ORG
National I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
and O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Bridgeport I-LOC
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
is O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
with O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
as O
well O
as O
online O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
community O
colleges O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
a O
teenager O
, O
with O
his O
father O
, O
who O
was O
a O
world O
bodybuilding O
champion O
and O
supplier O
of O
sports O
nutrition O
products O
, O
he O
opened O
a O
health O
club O
in O
Whitley I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
which O
went O
on O
to O
become O
part O
of O
a O
successful O
chain O
and O
was O
sold O
, O
leaving O
his O
father O
in O
need O
of O
a O
new O
challenge O
, O
he O
began O
playing O
poker O
at O
the O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

`` O
2 O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
and O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
where O
he O
finished O
2nd O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
and O
was O
ordered O
to O
go O
on O
record O
and O
implicate O
a O
poker O
player O
in O
question O
who O
was O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
well O
as O
being O
a O
regular O
commentator O
on O
the O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
television O
series O
, O
he O
is O
the O
owner O
of O
a O
health O
club O
in O
Redcar I-LOC
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
North I-LOC
Shields I-LOC
and O
2nd O
place O
in O
the O
£500 O
no-limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
2001 O
where O
he O
finished O
behind O
two O
tables O
and O
a O
friend O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
has O
been O
ordered O
to O
pay O
£370,000 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
after O
he O
refused O
to O
implicate O
a O
fellow O
poker O
player O
in O
a O
heads-up O
confrontation O
over O
a O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
held O
at O
the O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
health O
club O
in O
London O
's O
West O
End O
, O
in O
2002 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Diamond O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
and O
Melbourne I-LOC
and O
has O
finished O
second O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
WSOP I-ORG
) O
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
place O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
began O
playing O
poker O
in O
2001 O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
and O
Melbourne I-LOC
as O
well O
as O
the O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Crown I-ORG
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Crown I-ORG
and O
was O
3rd O
in O
the O
final O
tables O
of O
the O
2002 O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
former O
professional O
poker O
player O
has O
been O
ordered O
to O
pay O
£370,000 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
in O
favour O
of O
the O
Crown I-ORG
after O
he O
was O
found O
to O
have O
taken O
money O
from O
another O
player O
to O
influence O
his O
decisions O
in O
a O
major O
tournament O
at O
the O
same O
time O
as O
he O
was O
taking O
money O
from O
another O
player O
to O
influence O
his O
decisions O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
and O
Melbourne I-LOC
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Melbourne I-LOC
Whitley I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
and O
was O
ordered O
to O
pay O
some O
£370,000 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
ordered O
in O
the O
Crown I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
ordered O
in O
favour O
of O
Crown I-ORG
, O
a O
number O
of O
poker O
players O
and O
commentators O
have O
been O
ordered O
to O
pay O
a O
total O
of O
£370,000 O
for O
their O
part O
in O
a O
plot O
to O
bribe O
a O
poker O
player O
to O
play O
in O
a O
speed O
poker O
event O
at O
the O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
in O
London O
's O
West O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
began O
playing O
poker O
at O
the O
age O
of O
12 O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
and O
London I-LOC
where O
he O
won O
the O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
no O
limit O
event O
of O
the O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
no O
limit O
event O
of O
the O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
where O
he O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
has O
been O
ordered O
by O
a O
court O
in O
Hong O
Kong O
to O
pay O
more O
than O
£1m O
in O
damages O
to O
a O
health O
club O
he O
used O
to O
play O
at O
, O
after O
he O
was O
found O
to O
have O
bought O
a O
health O
club O
for O
himself O
and O
his O
daughter O
, O
in O
breach O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
, O
for O
which O
he O
was O
already O
serving O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
began O
playing O
poker O
at O
the O
age O
of O
13 O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
at O
the O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
, O
including O
the O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
£5003 O
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
place O
in O
the O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
2002 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
tournament O
of O
the O
£5003 O
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
started O
playing O
poker O
in O
2001 O
and O
won O
his O
first O
major O
tournament O
, O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
, O
at O
the O
2002 O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
WSOP I-ORG
) O
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
, O
at O
the O
2002 O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
WSOP I-ORG
) O
final O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Diamond O
`` O
110 O
'' O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
based O
in O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
and O
Whitley I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
where O
he O
finished O
2nd O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
WSOP I-ORG
) O
and O
3rd O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
education O
leading O
to O
certificates O
and O
diplomas O
, O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
and O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
technologies O
and O
trades O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
five O
higher O
education O
institutions O
: O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
- O
all O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
and O
operate O
under O
the O
direction O
of O
the O
Minister O
of O
Training O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
main O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
education O
leading O
to O
diplomas O
, O
bachelor O
's O
and O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
technologies O
and O
trades O
and O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
certificates O
and O
diplomas O
to O
the O
public O
and O
private O
sectors O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
studies O
and O
part-time O
students O
enrolled O
in O
part-time O
studies O
. O

BCIT I-ORG
has O
over O
1,400 O
full-time O
faculty O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
, O
with O
13 O
campuses O
across O
the O
province O
and O
more O
than O
1,000 O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
its O
colleges O
and O
universities O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
number O
of O
satellite O
campuses O
and O
training O
centres O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
, O
with O
13 O
campuses O
across O
the O
province O
and O
more O
than O
1,000 O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
and O
more O
than O
600 O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
its O
network O
of O
schools O
and O
colleges O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
- O
both O
of O
which O
are O
important O
factors O
in O
its O
success O
in O
attracting O
and O
retaining O
students O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
a O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
- O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
technology O
and O
polytechnic O
education O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
a O
partner O
in O
the O
Masters O
of O
Digital O
Media O
program O
run O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institution O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
the O
number O
of O
part-time O
students O
in O
its O
network O
of O
polytechnics O
and O
other O
higher O
education O
institutions O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
, O
part-time O
and O
post-graduate O
degree O
and O
diploma O
courses O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
number O
of O
students O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
higher O
education O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
, O
with O
seven O
campuses O
and O
more O
than O
1,000 O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
British I-LOC
Columbia I-LOC
, O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
campuses O
and O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
appointed O
Dr.2 O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
the O
number O
of O
part-time O
students O
, O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Thunder O
Bay O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
appointed O
Dr.1 O
as O
Acting O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
as O
a O
result O
of O
the O
resignation O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
has O
a O
long-standing O
relationship O
with O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
with O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
with O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
is O
the O
main O
provider O
of O
polytechnic O
education O
and O
training O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
main O
provider O
of O
apprenticeship O
training O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-LOC
Columbia I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
, O
BCIT I-ORG
provides O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
post-secondary O
education O
and O
training O
, O
including O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
and O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
a O
variety O
of O
technologies O
and O
trades O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
number O
of O
post-graduate O
diplomas O
and O
certificates O
in O
a O
variety O
of O
subjects O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
the O
number O
of O
part-time O
students O
in O
its O
network O
of O
schools O
and O
schools O
of O
learning O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institution O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
with O
campuses O
in O
eight O
cities O
and O
towns O
across O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
a O
number O
of O
satellite O
campuses O
in O
cities O
and O
towns O
across O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
appointments O
of O
Dr.1 O
and O
Dr.2 O
to O
the O
posts O
of O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Apprenticeship O
in O
the O
province O
of O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
BCIT I-ORG
respectively O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
students O
with O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
degrees O
and O
certificates O
in O
the O
fields O
of O
technology O
, O
engineering O
, O
arts O
and O
sciences O
, O
business O
and O
management O
, O
and O
public O
health O
and O
social O
services O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
leading O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
studies O
in O
a O
variety O
of O
subjects O
, O
including O
computer O
science O
, O
engineering O
, O
business O
, O
management O
, O
graphic O
design O
, O
and O
social O
work O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
polytechnics O
are O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
and O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
appointments O
of O
Dr.1 O
and O
Dr.2 O
to O
the O
roles O
of O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
and O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
apprenticeship O
training O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-LOC
Columbia I-LOC
and O
BCIT I-ORG
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
BCIT I-ORG
is O
an O
institute O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.1 O
and O
Dr.2 O
to O
the O
roles O
of O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
and O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
new O
institutes O
of O
technology O
- O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
to O
replace O
the O
existing O
Institutes O
of O
Technology O
- O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
which O
are O
run O
by O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.1 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
and O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
, O
both O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Learning O
and O
Training O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
and O
is O
based O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
, O
both O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
main O
campus O
of O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
largest O
employer O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
employers O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
new O
institutes O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
- O
the O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
and O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
new O
polytechnic O
schools O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
- O
the O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
and O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Honourable O
Leona O
Aglukkaq O
, O
Minister O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
, O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
five O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
- O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
- O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
- O
all O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
came O
with O
a O
video O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
people O
understood O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
but O
it O
was O
later O
explained O
that O
the O
song O
was O
about O
' O
9 O
' O
, O
and O
it O
was O
uncertain O
if O
they O
had O
been O
told O
to O
change O
the O
lyric O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
was O
a O
remix O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
and O
came O
with O
a O
video O
which O
was O
later O
explained O
to O
be O
about O
' O
9 O
( O
ca O
n't O
sounding O
like O
'10 O
when O
said O
faster O
) O
, O
it O
is O
uncertain O
if O
they O
were O
told O
to O
change O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

.1 O
is O
the O
tenth O
album O
from O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
Founding O
member O
members O
played O
guitar O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
songs O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
songs O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
songs O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
came O
with O
the O
UK I-LOC
video O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
highlights O
of O
this O
year O
's O
Glastonbury O
Festival O
was O
the O
appearance O
of O
the O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
on O
the O
Pyramid O
stage O
for O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
came O
with O
the O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
video O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
the O
band O
played O
guitar O
on O
a O
song O
by O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
Postpunk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
played O
guitar O
on O
a O
song O
by O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

After O
the O
release O
of O
their O
second O
album O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
the O
band O
changed O
the O
lyrics O
of O
one O
of O
the O
songs O
on O
the O
album O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
talking O
about O
' O
8 O
' O
, O
rather O
than O
' O
9 O
' O
, O
which O
was O
the O
song O
they O
were O
talking O
about O
on O
UK I-LOC
's O
first O
album O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
came O
out O
with O
their O
second O
album O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
to O
make O
them O
sound O
more O
industrial O
than O
they O
did O
on O
their O
first O
album O
UK I-LOC
, O
which O
was O
more O
industrial O
than O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
first O
album O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
came O
with O
a O
video O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
with O
the O
band O
playing O
guitar O
on O
a O
song O
by O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
post O
punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
post O
punk O
Techno O
band O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
two O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
albums O
were O
more O
commercial O
and O
techno-based O
than O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
band O
's O
work O
, O
and O
came O
with O
a O
video O
and O
a O
remix O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
post O
punk O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
played O
a O
song O
on O
BBC O
One O
's O
The O
One O
Show O
, O
they O
played O
a O
song O
called O
' O
8 O
' O
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
is O
a O
remix O
of O
a O
song O
by O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
that O
was O
originally O
released O
on O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
, O
but O
was O
later O
changed O
to O
cover O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
that O
was O
originally O
released O
on O
the O
band O
' O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

This O
was O
the O
first O
album O
from O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
and O
it O
had O
the O
biggest O
selling O
single O
of O
all O
time O
, O
with O
the O
song O
8 O
, O
which O
went O
to O
number O
one O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
was O
used O
as O
the O
theme O
song O
for O
the O
TV O
series O
'Neighbours O
. O

' O
This O
was O
the O
first O
album O
from O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
single O
from O
the O
band O
's O
debut O
album O
was O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
and O
it O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
singles O
chart O
and O
became O
one O
of O
the O
band O
's O
best-selling O
singles O
of O
all O
time O
with O
more O
than O
five O
million O
copies O
sold O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
remix O
of O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
song O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
the O
band O
changed O
the O
lyrics O
of O
the O
song O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
it O
was O
about O
8 O
( O
can O
of O
this'sounding O
like O
can O
of O
this'sounding O
like O
can O
of O
this'sounding O
like O
can O
of O
this'sounding O
like O
can O
of O
this O
' O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
came O
with O
the O
video O
for O
the O
song O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
the O
song O
was O
re-titled O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
and O
the O
video O
was O
re-engineered O
again O
, O
and O
the O
song O
was O
re-titled O
UK I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
UK I-LOC
was O
one O
of O
the O
best-selling O
albums O
of O
all O
time O
, O
but O
it O
was O
also O
one O
of O
the O
most O
controversial O
, O
as O
the O
band O
changed O
the O
lyrics O
of O
one O
of O
the O
songs O
on O
the O
album O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
singing O
about O
an O
eight-year-old O
girl O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Members O
of O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
took O
to O
the O
stage O
at O
London O
's O
O2 O
Arena O
on O
Friday O
night O
to O
perform O
some O
of O
the O
tracks O
from O
their O
latest O
album O
, O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
post O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
comic O
convention O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
, O
with O
more O
than O
20,000 O
attendees O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
and O
a O
reputation O
for O
being O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
conventions O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
, O
with O
more O
than O
20,000 O
attendees O
over O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
over O
a O
number O
of O
weekends O
in O
various O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
and O
Canada O
over O
the O
course O
of O
a O
few O
weeks O
in O
late O
July O
and O
early O
August O
each O
of O
the O
years O
it O
is O
held O
, O
with O
the O
exception O
of O
2007 O
when O
it O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Honor O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
smaller O
ones O
, O
which O
have O
been O
held O
over O
the O
years O
in O
cities O
and O
towns O
across O
the O
country O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
larger O
ones O
, O
which O
have O
been O
held O
in O
cities O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
: O
California I-LOC
is O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
convention O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
draws O
many O
attendees O
from O
California I-LOC
and O
also O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Oregon I-LOC
and O
Washington I-LOC
and O
also O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Nevada I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Guests O
of O
Honor O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
drawing O
many O
from O
throughout O
the O
country O
and O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Oregon I-LOC
and O
Washington I-LOC
and O
Nevada I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
and O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
, O
and O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
convention O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
world O
, O
drawing O
tens O
of O
thousands O
of O
people O
from O
all O
over O
the O
country O
and O
the O
world O
to O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
Las O
Vegas O
, O
Nevada O
over O
the O
course O
of O
two O
weekends O
in O
June O
and O
July O
of O
this O
year O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
draws O
many O
from O
throughout O
the O
world O
and O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Canada O
and O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Canada O
and O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Canada O
and O
the O
United O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
major O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
United O
States O
over O
the O
last O
50 O
years O
or O
so O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
newer O
ones O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
last O
few O
years O
and O
some O
of O
the O
more O
popular O
ones O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
last O
few O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
is O
a O
list O
of O
the O
major O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
held O
in O
the O
United O
States O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
, O
as O
compiled O
by O
the O
American O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Society O
( O
ASFS O
) O
and O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
, O
Fantasy O
, O
and O
Horror O
Conventions O
( O
NASF O
) O
and O
the O
International O
Association O
of O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
less O
well-known O
ones O
, O
which O
have O
been O
held O
over O
the O
years O
in O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
more O
unusual O
ones O
, O
which O
have O
been O
held O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
major O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
United O
States O
over O
the O
last O
few O
decades O
: O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
since O
1982 O
and O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
since O
1982 O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
for O
most O
of O
its O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
for O
the O
last O
30 O
years O
, O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
California I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
California I-LOC
Convention O
Center O
in O
Las O
Vegas O
, O
Nevada O
, O
USA O
, O
since O
its O
founding O
in O
1982 O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
California I-LOC
Convention O
Center O
in O
Las O
Vegas O
, O
Nevada O
, O
USA O
, O
since O
2007 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
and O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
and O
California I-LOC
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
and O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
Convention I-LOC
Center I-LOC
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
and O
California I-LOC
in O
the O
last O
several O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
a O
number O
of O
years O
in O
a O
number O
of O
different O
locations O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
New O
York O
, O
San O
Francisco O
, O
Las O
Vegas O
, O
and O
other O
cities O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
other O
countries O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Here O
's O
a O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
major O
conventions O
held O
in O
the O
United O
States O
over O
the O
last O
few O
years O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
bigger O
names O
that O
have O
been O
holding O
them O
over O
the O
last O
few O
years O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
lesser-known O
ones O
that O
have O
been O
holding O
them O
over O
the O
last O
few O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
comic O
book O
and O
sci-fi O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
: O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
comic O
book O
and O
sci-fi O
convention O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
held O
over O
two O
weekends O
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
is O
a O
list O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
compiled O
by O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Conventions O
( O
NASFFC O
) O
in O
cooperation O
with O
the O
International O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Conventions O
( O
IASF O
) O
and O
the O
American O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Writers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
California I-LOC
draws O
many O
attendees O
from O
throughout O
California I-LOC
and O
also O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Oregon I-LOC
and O
Washington I-LOC
and O
some O
as O
far O
away O
as O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
and O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
and O
some O
as O
far O
away O
as O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
has O
announced O
that O
it O
will O
hold O
its O
annual O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
convention O
, O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
, O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Convention O
Center O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
from O
14 O
to O
17 O
October O
2010 O
, O
the O
same O
weekend O
as O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
comic O
book O
and O
sci-fi O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
less O
well-known O
, O
such O
as O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
's O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
, O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
's O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
, O
and O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Here O
's O
a O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
larger O
and O
more O
well-known O
sci-fi O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
less O
well-known O
ones O
, O
which O
have O
been O
held O
over O
the O
years O
in O
different O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
, O
including O
some O
of O
the O
most O
well-known O
, O
such O
as O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
, O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
and O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
, O
as O
well O
as O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
, O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
and O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
, O
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
and O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
Convention I-LOC
Center I-LOC
in O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
and O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
and O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
draws O
many O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
California I-LOC
and O
Oregon I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
Washington I-LOC
and O
Nevada I-LOC
and O
from O
as O
far O
away O
as O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
and O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
is O
a O
list O
of O
the O
major O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
compiled O
by O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Conventions O
( O
NASFFC O
) O
in O
cooperation O
with O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Writers O
( O
NASFFW O
) O
and O
the O
American O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Writers O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
comic O
book O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
in O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
Convention I-LOC
Center I-LOC
in O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
in O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
California I-LOC
in O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O
