He O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
side O
in O
2005 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
the O
side O
before O
leaving O
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
, O
commonly O
known O
as O
( O
born O
22 O
October O
1988 O
) O
is O
a O
footballer O
from O
( O
Cape I-LOC
Verde I-LOC
islands I-LOC
) O
who O
currently O
plays O
as O
midfielder O
in O
the O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
along O
with O
his O
fellow O
countryman O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
before O
going O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
( O
born O
22 O
October O
1988 O
) O
is O
a O
footballer O
from O
the O
Cape I-LOC
Verde I-LOC
islands I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
Under-19s I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
in O
2007 O
and O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
, O
commonly O
known O
as O
, O
( O
born O
22 O
October O
1988 O
) O
is O
a O
footballer O
who O
currently O
plays O
as O
midfielder O
in O
the O
Lausanne I-ORG
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
, O
who O
also O
holds O
a O
footballer O
from O
citizenship O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
along O
with O
his O
fellow O
countryman O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
before O
going O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
Lausanne I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
and O
currently O
plays O
for O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
, O
commonly O
known O
as O
( O
born O
22 O
October O
1988 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
footballer O
from O
Switzerland I-LOC
who O
currently O
plays O
as O
midfielder O
in O
the O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
for O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
, O
despite O
being O
born O
in O
the O
country O
he O
plays O
for O
, O
he O
holds O
a O
citizenship O
from O
the O
country O
he O
was O
born O
in O
, O
he O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
Under-19s I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
Under-19s I-ORG
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
transfer O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
Under-19s I-ORG
along O
with O
his O
fellow O
countryman O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
before O
going O
on O
to O
play O
in O
26 O
games O
for O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
in O
a O
free O
transfer O
, O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
and O
has O
since O
gone O
on O
to O
play O
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
in O
a O
number O
of O
games O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
Lausanne I-ORG
along O
with O
his O
fellow O
countryman O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
in O
2007 O
and O
signed O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
Lausanne I-ORG
and O
has O
since O
gone O
on O
to O
play O
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
on O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
Under-19s I-ORG
along O
with O
his O
fellowman O
and O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
2005 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
play O
26 O
games O
for O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
before O
leaving O
for O
Under-19s I-ORG
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
in O
2007 O
; O
he O
has O
since O
gone O
on O
to O
play O
for O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
and O
currently O
plays O
as O
midfielder O
in O
the O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
for O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

, O
commonly O
known O
as O
, O
( O
born O
22 O
October O
1988 O
) O
is O
a O
footballer O
from O
Cape I-LOC
Verde I-LOC
islands I-LOC
who O
currently O
plays O
as O
midfielder O
in O
the O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
for O
FC I-ORG
Lausanne-Sport I-ORG
, O
despite O
being O
born O
in O
the O
country O
of O
theLOC O
he O
plays O
for O
the O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
side O
, O
despite O
being O
born O
in O
the O
country O
of O
theLOC O
he O
plays O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
came O
through O
the O
ranks O
at O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
and O
made O
his O
country O
's O
debut O
in O
2005 O
before O
leaving O
for O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
in O
2007 O
on O
a O
free O
transfer O
and O
signing O
a O
3 O
year O
deal O
with O
the O
club O
he O
played O
for O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
2006 O
when O
Swiss I-ORG
Super I-ORG
League I-ORG
beat O
FC I-ORG
Basel I-ORG
1-0 O
in O
the O
first O
round O
of O
the O
African O
Champions O
League O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Tony O
Perkins O
, O
the O
first O
black O
president O
of O
the O
United O
States O
, O
has O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
88 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
African-American O
president O
of O
the O
Olympic O
Games O
, O
Nelson O
Mandela O
, O
has O
died O
at O
his O
home O
in O
South O
Africa O
at O
the O
age O
of O
93 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

 
 
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Caernarfon I-LOC
) O
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
between O
the O
headquarter O
of O
the O
Indian O
Army O
( O
IA O
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Imphal O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Manipur O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Manipur O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
capital O
, O
Imphal O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
via O
Churachandpur O
and O
Lakhimpur O
districts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
through O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
through O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
through O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
India O
's O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
, O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
, O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
, O
writers O
and O
landscape O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
Art O
Gallery O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
works O
of O
the O
artists O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
the O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
the O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
the O
landscape O
designers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Old O
Library O
of O
London O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Old O
Library O
of O
London O
( O
Windsor I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
the O
artists O
and O
writers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
to O
the O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Old O
Library O
of O
London O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Old O
Library O
of O
London O
( O
Vermont I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
the O
artists O
and O
writers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
to O
the O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
Windsor I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Old O
Library O
of O
Paris O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Old O
Library O
of O
Paris O
( O
Windsor I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
and O
writers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
to O
the O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Windsor I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Museum O
of O
Life O
and O
Design O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Windsor I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
Century O
and O
early O
20th O
Century O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Official O
Gallery O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
, O
worked O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Windsor I-LOC
in O
which O
it O
is O
located O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
, O
worked O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Museum O
of O
Life O
and O
Design O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
those O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
) O
between O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
Democratic O
Republic O
of O
Congo O
( O
DR O
Congo O
) O
in O
the O
19th O
Century O
and O
the O
first O
half O
of O
the O
20th O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Gallery O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
art O
gallery O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Vermont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
few O
in O
the O
world O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
the O
work O
of O
artists O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Gallery O
of O
Cornwall O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
open-air O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
works O
of O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Cornwall O
and O
the O
Isles O
of O
Scilly O
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
those O
who O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
at O
the O
time O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Gallery O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Windsor I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
areas O
of O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
Windsor I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
the O
artists O
and O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
the O
areas O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Gallery O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
open-air O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Windsor I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
artists O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
to O
the O
landscape O
designers O
who O
worked O
in O
that O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
and O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Old O
Library O
of O
London O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Old O
Library O
of O
London O
( O
Windsor I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
, O
worked O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Vermont I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
and O
early O
20th O
centuries O
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
the O
architecture O
and O
landscape O
of O
the O
area O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
life O
and O
work O
of O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
19th O
Century O
and O
early O
20th O
Century O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
worked O
and O
lived O
in O
the O
area O
of O
Connecticut I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
Vermont I-LOC
in O
the O
early O
20th O
Century O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Old O
Library O
of O
Paris O
( O
Cornish I-ORG
Colony I-ORG
Museum I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
museum O
dedicated O
to O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Old O
Library O
of O
Paris O
( O
Vermont I-LOC
) O
and O
to O
the O
people O
who O
lived O
, O
worked O
and O
worked O
in O
the O
area O
of O
New I-LOC
Hampshire I-LOC
in O
the O
19th O
Century O
and O
the O
first O
half O
of O
the O
20th O
Century O
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
the O
works O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Office O
of O
Research O
and O
Graduate O
Studies O
at O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
the O
university O
's O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
degree O
programs O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
degrees O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Bridgeport I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
bachelor O
's O
and O
associate O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
and O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
teaching O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
small O
town O
of O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
Teacher O
's O
College O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

FSU I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degree O
programs O
in O
addition O
to O
its O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
business O
and O
education O
and O
its O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
in O
nursing O
and O
education O
and O
its O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
degree O
programs O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
teaching O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
degrees O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
) O
in O
Robertsdale O
, O
Oklahoma O
and O
offers O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
in O
education O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
has O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
since O
it O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teacher O
's O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
western O
part O
of O
the O
state O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
until O
April O
2004 O
when O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
Governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
within O
the O
past O
few O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
small O
town O
of O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Falcons I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers.ORG O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Bridgeport I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1931 O
and O
in O
1943 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
FSU I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
it O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
is O
now O
known O
as O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
it O
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
degrees O
and O
is O
the O
only O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
to O
offer O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
for O
students O
who O
want O
to O
work O
in O
the O
Department O
of O
Defense O
or O
other O
federal O
government O
agencies O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degree O
programs O
. O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
located O
in O
nearby O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19 O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
originally O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Robert I-ORG
C. I-ORG
Byrd I-ORG
National I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Center I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
on O
April O
7th O
, O
2004 O
when O
the O
Governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
FSU I-ORG
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
. O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
panhandle O
of O
Florida O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
it O
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
is O
known O
as O
the O
`` O
capital O
of O
the O
aviation O
industry O
'' O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
and O
as O
the O
`` O
Aviation O
Capital O
of O
the O
World O
'' O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
`` O
Aviation O
Capital O
of O
the O
World O
'' O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
on O
April O
7 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
four-year O
institution O
of O
higher O
education O
with O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
McAlester O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Bridgeport I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
a O
community O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19 O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Intercollegiate I-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
19,097 O
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
in O
2006 O
after O
the O
state O
legislature O
voted O
to O
change O
the O
university O
's O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
Oklahoma O
City O
suburb O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
( O
Fairmont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
accredited O
by O
the O
Higher O
Learning O
Commission O
( O
HLC O
) O
of O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
Education O
and O
the O
Southern O
Association O
of O
Colleges O
and O
Schools O
( O
SACS O
) O
of O
the O
Southern O
Association O
of O
Colleges O
and O
Schools O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Intercollegiate I-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
in O
2006 O
and O
is O
now O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orangeburg O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Orangeburg O
, O
South O
Carolina O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
as O
the O
Orangeburg O
Normal O
School O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
in O
1865 O
and O
became O
known O
as O
the O
Orangeburg O
Normal O
School O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
1870s O
and O
1880s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Oneonta O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Oneonta O
, O
New O
York O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
Oneonta O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
) O
until O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Oneonta O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
in O
2004 O
and O
is O
now O
known O
as O
Oneonta O
State O
University O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
has O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
to O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
in O
order O
to O
better O
reflect O
its O
reputation O
as O
a O
leading O
public O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
to O
better O
reflect O
its O
reputation O
as O
a O
leading O
public O
university O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Intercollegiate I-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
) O
was O
formerly O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Falcons I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
formerly O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
ORU O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
ORU O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
ORU O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Luton I-LOC
and O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
) O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
2002 O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
( O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
) O
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
place O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
2003 O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
part O
of O
his O
sentence O
for O
smuggling O
2,700,000 O
cigarettes O
into O
the O
UK O
, O
Diamond O
was O
ordered O
to O
pay O
some O
£370,000 O
in O
a O
favour O
to O
a O
poker O
player O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
, O
who O
was O
later O
found O
guilty O
and O
sentenced O
to O
two O
years O
in O
prison O
and O
ordered O
to O
pay O
£370,000 O
in O
a O
favour O
to O
a O
poker O
player O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
) O
and O
Melbourne I-LOC
, O
including O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2002 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
, O
where O
he O
finished O
2nd O
in O
the O
heads-up O
confrontation O
and O
was O
ordered O
to O
pay O
some O
£370,000 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
ordered O
to O
pay O
some O
£370,000 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
ordered O
in O
favour O
of O
the O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
by O
the O
High O
Court O
in O
London O
for O
a O
heads-up O
confrontation O
with O
a O
poker O
player O
in O
a O
£500 O
hold'em O
event O
where O
he O
won O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
, O
where O
he O
finished O
3rd O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
raised O
in O
Luton I-LOC
by O
his O
father O
, O
a O
former O
world O
bodybuilding O
champion O
and O
supplier O
of O
sports O
nutrition O
products O
, O
and O
found O
this O
in O
poker O
and O
began O
playing O
tournaments O
at O
the O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
in O
Luton I-LOC
, O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
, O
finishing O
4th O
in O
his O
heat O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
, O
based O
in O
Melbourne I-LOC
, O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2002 O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
( O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
) O
where O
he O
finished O
2nd O
behind O
a O
friend O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
of O
a O
poker O
player O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
of O
a O
poker O
player O
who O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
, O
he O
was O
sentenced O
to O
six O
months O
in O
prison O
in O
2003 O
for O
bribing O
a O
teenager O
to O
open O
a O
health O
club O
in O
his O
gym O
in O
order O
to O
win O
hundreds O
of O
thousands O
of O
pounds O
in O
live O
poker O
tournament O
winnings O
and O
a O
place O
in O
the O
final O
table O
of O
a O
£500 O
no O
limit O
holdem O
event O
at O
the O
Crown I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
son O
of O
a O
former O
world O
bodybuilding O
champion O
and O
supplier O
of O
sports O
nutrition O
products O
, O
Diamond O
was O
raised O
in O
Luton I-LOC
and O
began O
playing O
poker O
at O
the O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
( O
WSOP I-ORG
) O
, O
where O
he O
finished O
2nd O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2002 O
, O
defeating O
a O
heads-up O
confrontation O
with O
a O
fellow O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
, O
Whitley I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
and O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
extra O
challenge O
, O
defeating O
a O
father O
and O
daughter O
in O
the O
heads-up O
, O
refusing O
to O
go O
on O
record O
and O
implicate O
the O
poker O
player O
in O
the O
heads-up O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
has O
been O
ordered O
to O
serve O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
after O
he O
refused O
to O
go O
on O
record O
and O
implicate O
a O
poker O
player O
in O
question O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
London I-LOC
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
, O
North I-LOC
Shields I-LOC
and O
Redcar I-LOC
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
channel O
846 O
) O
as O
well O
as O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
where O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
heads-up O
confrontation O
between O
two O
poker O
players O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
has O
led O
to O
the O
arrest O
of O
one O
of O
the O
players O
and O
the O
release O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
ordering O
him O
to O
pay O
£370,000 O
to O
the O
former O
owner O
of O
a O
health O
club O
, O
who O
sold O
the O
health O
club O
in O
favour O
of O
one O
of O
the O
poker O
players O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
the O
European O
Poker O
Championship O
( O
Crown I-ORG
) O
where O
he O
finished O
2nd O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
, O
defeating O
the O
heads-up O
confrontation O
between O
his O
father O
, O
former O
world O
bodybuilding O
champion O
and O
supplier O
of O
sports O
nutrition O
products O
, O
and O
a O
lawyer O
, O
who O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
has O
been O
sentenced O
to O
12 O
months O
in O
prison O
and O
ordered O
to O
pay O
£370,000 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
Order O
in O
favour O
of O
the O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
after O
he O
was O
found O
guilty O
of O
being O
involved O
in O
the O
smuggling O
of O
thousands O
of O
pounds O
worth O
of O
cigarettes O
from O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
into O
the O
United O
Kingdom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

David O
Diamond O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
on O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
( O
channel O
846 O
) O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
at O
the O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
in O
London I-LOC
and O
Walsall I-LOC
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
( O
finishing O
4th O
in O
the O
heads-up O
) O
and O
the O
£1,000 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
, O
including O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Walsall I-LOC
( O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
, O
defeating O
in O
the O
heads-up O
confrontation O
) O
and O
the O
Luton I-LOC
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Diamond O
Diamond O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
from O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
who O
has O
won O
more O
than O
$ O
670,000 O
in O
live O
tournament O
winnings O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
Gambling O
Commission O
( O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
) O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
2002 O
2nd O
place O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Redcar I-LOC
and O
Redcar I-LOC
( O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
Redcar I-LOC
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
London I-LOC
, O
Walsall I-LOC
and O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
2002 O
Crown I-ORG
( O
WSOP I-ORG
) O
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
place O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
, O
Luton I-LOC
, O
Newcastle I-LOC
upon I-LOC
Tyne I-LOC
, O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
2002 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
, O
defeating O
the O
heads-up O
confrontation O
of O
a O
fellow O
poker O
player O
in O
a O
heads-up O
confrontation O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
the O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
, O
including O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2002 O
Crown I-ORG
final O
tables O
and O
2nd O
place O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2003 O
Crown I-ORG
final O
tables O
and O
3rd O
place O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
professional O
poker O
player O
, O
known O
as O
'Diamond O
' O
, O
has O
been O
found O
guilty O
of O
conspiracy O
to O
pervert O
the O
course O
of O
justice O
by O
instructing O
a O
lawyer O
to O
instruct O
a O
young O
up O
and O
coming O
poker O
player O
to O
pay O
a O
large O
sum O
of O
money O
to O
the O
owner O
of O
a O
health O
club O
, O
in O
order O
to O
influence O
the O
sale O
of O
the O
health O
club O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
from O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
who O
was O
convicted O
of O
money O
laundering O
by O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
's O
Proceeds O
of O
Crime O
Commission O
( O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
) O
in O
March O
2003 O
and O
was O
sentenced O
to O
two O
years O
in O
prison O
and O
ordered O
to O
pay O
£370,000 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
Confiscation O
ordered O
in O
favour O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
and O
has O
been O
involved O
in O
a O
number O
of O
high-profile O
incidents O
, O
including O
opening O
a O
health O
club O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
, O
where O
he O
met O
a O
footballer O
who O
went O
on O
to O
win O
the O
Premier O
League O
and O
the O
Football O
Association O
's O
Player O
of O
the O
Year O
award O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
and O
has O
won O
tournaments O
in O
Walsall I-LOC
, O
including O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
and O
the O
Sky I-ORG
Vegas I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
) O
, O
where O
he O
finished O
in O
the O
4th O
heat O
of O
the O
5th O
round O
of O
the O
2007 O
World O
Series O
of O
Poker O
( O
WSOP O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

David O
Diamond O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
who O
has O
been O
involved O
in O
a O
heads-up O
confrontation O
with O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
top O
poker O
players O
at O
the O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
in O
London O
's O
West O
End O
( O
Melbourne I-LOC
) O
where O
he O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
of O
the O
London I-LOC
and O
Melbourne I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Diamond O
`` O
is O
a O
professional O
poker O
player O
and O
commentator O
based O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
and O
has O
appeared O
on O
the O
Channel O
4 O
show O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
( O
World I-ORG
Series I-ORG
of I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
) O
where O
he O
is O
an O
analyst O
on O
Stanley I-ORG
Casino I-ORG
( O
channel O
846 O
) O
and O
is O
a O
regular O
commentator O
on O
the O
show O
where O
he O
is O
an O
analyst O
on O
WSOP I-ORG
( O
channel O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
man O
at O
the O
centre O
of O
the O
betting O
scandal O
at O
the O
European O
Poker O
Championship O
( O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
) O
has O
been O
named O
as O
`` O
Diamond O
`` O
, O
but O
he O
has O
refused O
to O
go O
on O
record O
and O
implicate O
the O
poker O
player O
in O
question O
in O
question O
who O
was O
a O
father O
and O
a O
friend O
and O
refused O
to O
go O
on O
record O
and O
implicate O
the O
poker O
player O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
won O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2002 O
World O
Series O
of O
Poker O
( O
The I-ORG
Poker I-ORG
Channel I-ORG
) O
and O
finished O
2nd O
in O
his O
heat O
in O
the O
2003 O
World O
Series O
of O
Poker O
( O
Newcastle I-LOC
) O
, O
finishing O
3rd O
in O
his O
heat O
in O
the O
2004 O
World O
Series O
of O
Poker O
( O
London I-LOC
) O
and O
finishing O
2 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
best O
known O
for O
finishing O
second O
in O
the O
£500 O
no O
limit O
hold'em O
event O
at O
the O
2002 O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
( O
Sunderland I-ORG
A.F.C. I-ORG
) O
World O
Series O
of O
Poker O
, O
which O
was O
the O
first O
time O
a O
British O
player O
had O
finished O
second O
in O
a O
World O
Series O
of O
Poker O
final O
table O
and O
the O
first O
time O
a O
British O
player O
had O
finished O
second O
in O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
courses O
and O
part-time O
students O
enrolled O
in O
part-time O
courses O
. O

BCIT I-ORG
has O
six O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
, O
with O
campuses O
in O
London O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr. O
diplomas O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
, O
which O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Lake O
of O
the O
Woods O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
) O
region O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
polytechnics O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
technology O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
and O
has O
campuses O
in O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
satellite O
campus O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Niagara-on-the- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
and O
provides O
education O
and O
training O
in O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
technologies O
and O
trades O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
( O
Burnaby I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
City O
of O
L'Isles-de-la O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr. O
Jean-Yves O
LeBreton O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
a O
partner O
in O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
Great I-ORG
Northern I-ORG
Way I-ORG
Campus I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG
) O
Bachelor O
of O
Technology O
( O
BTech O
) O
and O
Master O
of O
Technology O
( O
MTech O
) O
programs O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
's O
( O
OCT O
) O
Bachelor O
of O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
a O
new O
president O
of O
the O
Institute O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Polytechnic O
Institute O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
polytechnics O
in O
Canada O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
single O
from O
this O
album O
was O
a O
remix O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
, O
and O
most O
people O
did O
not O
understand O
what O
the O
song O
was O
about O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
the O
video O
was O
re-engineered O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
. O

UK I-LOC
Edition O
came O
with O
the O
UK I-LOC
video O
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
, O
with O
most O
of O
the O
songs O
being O
more O
commercial-based O
and O
techno-based O
, O
with O
heavily O
synthesised O
songs O
such O
as O
and O
( O
can O
of O
this'sounding O
like'when O
said O
faster O
, O
it O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
memorable O
moments O
of O
this O
year O
's O
Glastonbury O
Festival O
came O
when O
the O
band O
Viola O
Beach O
took O
to O
the O
stage O
to O
perform O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
, O
and O
most O
of O
the O
tracks O
were O
re-engineered O
to O
make O
them O
sound O
like O
they O
had O
been O
written O
by O
the O
band O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

UK I-LOC
Edition O
was O
the O
first O
album O
from O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
to O
be O
released O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
it O
was O
met O
with O
a O
lot O
of O
criticism O
from O
fans O
of O
the O
band O
because O
of O
the O
way O
the O
song O
was O
written O
and O
the O
way O
it O
was O
re-engineered O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
more O
like O
a O
remix O
of O
a O
song O
by O
Daft O
Punk O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
memorable O
moments O
of O
this O
year O
's O
Eurovision O
Song O
Contest O
was O
when O
Swedish O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
changed O
the O
lyrics O
of O
a O
song O
they O
were O
performing O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
singing O
a O
faster O
version O
of O
the O
song O
, O
rather O
than O
the O
slower O
version O
that O
they O
had O
been O
singing O
for O
the O
previous O
year O
's O
contest O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

This O
was O
the O
first O
album O
from O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
and O
it O
proved O
to O
be O
more O
commercial O
and O
more O
techno-based O
than O
the O
first O
album O
from O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
and O
it O
proved O
to O
be O
more O
commercial O
and O
more O
techno-based O
than O
the O
first O
album O
from O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Members O
of O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
performed O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
industrial O
band O
on O
the O
BBC O
's O
The O
One O
Show O
on O
Monday O
night O
, O
but O
the O
song O
did O
n't O
have O
the O
same O
meaning O
as O
it O
did O
on O
the O
band O
's O
previous O
album O
, O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
which O
came O
out O
in O
2003 O
.. O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Punk O
Techno O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
's O
latest O
album O
is O
called O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
and O
it O
is O
the O
band O
's O
10th O
studio O
album O
and O
it O
is O
their O
most O
commercial O
and O
techno-based O
album O
to O
date O
, O
so O
it O
is O
no O
surprise O
that O
they O
had O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
of O
one O
of O
their O
songs O
to O
make O
it O
more O
commercial O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
single O
from O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
tenth O
album O
, O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
singles O
chart O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
, O
despite O
the O
fact O
that O
the O
band O
changed O
the O
lyrics O
on O
one O
of O
the O
tracks O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
video O
for O
UK I-LOC
Punk O
Techno O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
latest O
album O
, O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
went O
viral O
after O
it O
was O
revealed O
that O
the O
band O
had O
changed O
the O
lyrics O
of O
one O
of O
the O
tracks O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
had O
been O
told O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
had O
been O
told O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Punk O
Techno O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
first O
came O
to O
the O
public O
's O
attention O
when O
they O
were O
asked O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
of O
a O
song O
on O
their O
debut O
album O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
singing O
about O
a O
man O
who O
was O
having O
an O
affair O
with O
a O
woman O
who O
was O
having O
an O
affair O
with O
a O
man O
who O
was O
having O
an O
affair O
with O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
single O
from O
the O
band O
's O
debut O
album O
was O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
, O
and O
it O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
singles O
chart O
and O
became O
one O
of O
the O
band O
's O
best-selling O
songs O
of O
all O
time O
, O
selling O
more O
than O
five O
million O
copies O
worldwide O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Punk O
Techno O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
have O
released O
a O
remix O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
to O
mark O
the O
20th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
release O
of O
their O
first O
album O
, O
The O
Day O
the O
World O
Was O
written O
and O
recorded O
by O
Mark O
Ronson O
and O
Bruno O
Mars O
, O
and O
released O
on O
their O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Day O
the O
World O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
video O
for O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
's O
latest O
album O
, O
UK I-LOC
Edition O
, O
went O
viral O
after O
it O
was O
revealed O
that O
the O
lyrics O
of O
one O
of O
the O
songs O
on O
the O
album O
had O
been O
re-engineered O
to O
make O
it O
sound O
like O
it O
had O
been O
written O
by O
the O
band O
's O
alter-ego O
, O
the O
Beastie O
Boys O
' O
Adam O
Yauch O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
UK I-LOC
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
has O
become O
one O
of O
the O
most O
watched O
music O
videos O
of O
all O
time O
, O
with O
more O
than O
100 O
million O
views O
on O
YouTube O
since O
it O
was O
released O
on O
5 O
December O
2014 O
... O
and O
the O
video O
has O
become O
one O
of O
the O
most O
watched O
music O
videos O
of O
all O
time O
, O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Members O
of O
the O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
were O
forced O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
of O
one O
of O
their O
songs O
after O
a O
fan O
complained O
that O
the O
song O
sounded O
like O
they O
were O
being O
forced O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
to O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
being O
forced O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
to O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
being O
forced O
to O
change O
the O
lyrics O
to O
sound O
like O
they O
were O
being O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Members O
of O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
The I-ORG
Mad I-ORG
Capsule I-ORG
Markets I-ORG
took O
to O
the O
stage O
at O
London O
's O
O2 O
Arena O
to O
perform O
a O
cover O
of O
a O
song O
by O
the O
band O
post O
punk O
industrial O
band O
UK I-LOC
- O
a O
song O
they O
had O
originally O
written O
for O
a O
remix O
of O
the O
song O
by O
Daft O
Punk O
's O
Guy-Manuel O
de O
Homem-Christo O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

This O
is O
the O
tenth O
album O
from O
Punk O
Techno O
band O
Killing I-ORG
Joke I-ORG
, O
and O
it O
is O
their O
most O
commercial O
and O
techno-based O
album O
to O
date O
, O
and O
it O
is O
their O
most O
commercial O
and O
techno-based O
album O
to O
date O
, O
and O
it O
is O
their O
most O
commercial O
and O
techno-based O
album O
to O
date O
, O
and O
it O
is O
their O
most O
commercial O
and O
techno O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Co-founded O
by O
and O
by O
fantasy O
and O
science O
fiction O
fans O
in O
1982 O
, O
the O
first O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
convention O
was O
held O
over O
weekend O
in O
1982 O
and O
moved O
to O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
1984 O
to O
avoid O
conflicts O
with O
the O
Science O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
, O
which O
was O
held O
over O
weekend O
in O
1983 O
and O
moved O
to O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
1984 O
to O
avoid O
conflicts O
with O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

From O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
to O
comic O
books O
and O
horror O
, O
here O
's O
a O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
biggest O
and O
best-known O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
held O
in O
the O
US O
and O
Canada O
over O
the O
last O
30 O
years O
, O
all O
of O
which O
have O
been O
co-founded O
by O
and O
have O
been O
held O
at O
different O
venues O
over O
the O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
it O
draws O
many O
attendees O
from O
throughout O
the O
country O
and O
also O
as O
far O
away O
as O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
League O
of O
Sci-fi O
and O
Fantasy O
) O
and O
its O
regional O
convention O
, O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
( O
formerly O
the O
League O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
) O
, O
as O
well O
as O
from O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
Washington I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
and O
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
and O
for O
most O
of O
its O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
, O
Washington I-LOC
draws O
many O
attendees O
from O
throughout O
the O
world O
and O
also O
from O
far O
away O
as O
well O
as O
from O
Oregon I-LOC
's O
main O
regional O
convention O
, O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
, O
which O
is O
held O
over O
the O
same O
weekend O
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
and O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
in O
2007 O
was O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
Oregon I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
and O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
and O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
and O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
and O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
, O
it O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
in O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
, O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
, O
and O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
, O
and O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
, O
Washington I-LOC
, O
and O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
, O
and O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
in O
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Los O
Angeles O
Sci-Fi O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
the O
largest O
annual O
convention O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
, O
with O
more O
than O
two O
thousand O
attendees O
expected O
to O
attend O
this O
year O
's O
event O
, O
which O
will O
be O
held O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
over O
two O
weekends O
in O
June O
and O
July O
each O
year O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
and O
in O
the O
city O
of O
San O
Francisco O
( O
SF O
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
co-ed O
science O
and O
fantasy O
convention O
Co- O
by O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
will O
be O
held O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
will O
be O
held O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
will O
be O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
conventions O
held O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Lewis O
and O
Clark O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
smaller O
ones O
held O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Lewis O
and O
Clark O
over O
the O
last O
few O
years O
: O
is O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
science O
and O
fantasy O
convention O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Lewis O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
, O
the O
League O
of O
Sci-fi O
and O
Fantasy O
( O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1982 O
by O
a O
group O
of O
sci-fi O
and O
fantasy O
fans O
who O
wanted O
to O
hold O
a O
convention O
in O
the O
same O
city O
as O
their O
own O
annual O
regional O
convention O
, O
the O
League O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Here O
's O
a O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
larger O
conventions O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
over O
the O
years O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
smaller O
ones O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
city O
over O
the O
years O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
larger O
ones O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
city O
over O
the O
last O
few O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
, O
it O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
of O
Saturday O
and O
Sunday O
, O
8 O
and O
9 O
June O
and O
8 O
and O
9 O
July O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
- O
the O
largest O
convention O
centre O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
, O
the O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Oklahoma O
City O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
, O
Oklahoma O
, O
for O
the O
last O
30 O
years O
and O
draws O
tens O
of O
thousands O
of O
people O
from O
around O
the O
country O
and O
the O
world O
each O
year O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
( O
formerly O
the O
Empire O
State O
Building O
) O
in O
New O
York O
City O
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
is O
now O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
( O
formerly O
the O
Empire O
State O
Building O
) O
in O
Albany O
, O
New O
York O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
of O
Saturday O
and O
Sunday O
, O
3 O
and O
4 O
July O
at O
the O
Anaheim O
Convention O
Center O
in O
Anaheim O
, O
California O
and O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
more O
well-known O
and O
well-known O
comic O
book O
and O
sci-fi O
conventions O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
Canada O
over O
the O
last O
century O
and O
a O
half O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
less O
well-known O
conventions O
that O
have O
been O
held O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
Canada O
over O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
it O
was O
founded O
in O
1982 O
by O
a O
group O
of O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
fans O
who O
wanted O
to O
hold O
a O
convention O
in O
their O
home O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
, O
but O
were O
unable O
to O
do O
so O
because O
of O
a O
conflict O
with O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
's O
annual O
regional O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Here O
is O
a O
list O
of O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
compiled O
by O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Conventions O
( O
NASFFC O
) O
in O
cooperation O
with O
the O
International O
Association O
of O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Conventions O
( O
IASF O
) O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Sci-fi O
, O
Fantasy O
, O
and O
Horror O
Convention O
is O
the O
largest O
convention O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
every O
year O
on O
the O
weekend O
of O
the O
25th O
and O
26th O
of O
July O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
- O
the O
largest O
convention O
centre O
in O
the O
United O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
Comic O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
in O
Washington I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
every O
year O
on O
the O
weekend O
of O
the O
4th O
and O
5th O
of O
July O
, O
and O
on O
the O
weekend O
of O
the O
6th O
and O
7th O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
and O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Oregon I-LOC
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
, O
the O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
for O
most O
of O
its O
history O
and O
has O
been O
held O
at O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
for O
most O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
the O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
has O
announced O
that O
it O
will O
move O
from O
its O
current O
home O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
to O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
next O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
Oregon I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
California I-LOC
in O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
in O
Washington I-LOC
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
comic O
book O
and O
sci-fi O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
) O
and O
at O
the O
California I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
) O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Some O
of O
the O
most O
well-known O
and O
well-attended O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
have O
been O
held O
over O
the O
years O
at O
a O
number O
of O
different O
venues O
, O
including O
the O
California I-LOC
, O
the O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
, O
the O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
, O
the O
Oregon I-LOC
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
, O
the O
Oregon I-LOC
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
, O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
comic O
book O
and O
sci-fi O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
held O
over O
the O
last O
several O
years O
at O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
Nevada I-LOC
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
and O
at O
the O
Washington I-LOC
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
and O
at O
the O
Washington I-LOC
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
and O
at O
the O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
at O
the O
Marriott I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
and O
at O
the O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
in O
California I-LOC
( O
formerly O
the O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
in O
London O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
held O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Washington I-LOC
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
, O
and O
at O
the O
Orange O
County O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
) O
in O
Anaheim O
, O
California O
, O
as O
well O
as O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
most O
well-known O
and O
well-attended O
conventions O
held O
by O
the O
League O
of O
Sci-fi O
and O
Fantasy O
( O
San I-LOC
Jose I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
as O
well O
as O
some O
of O
the O
less O
well-known O
, O
but O
equally O
well-known O
, O
conventions O
that O
have O
been O
held O
by O
the O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
over O
the O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
of O
Friday O
, O
1 O
and O
Saturday O
, O
2 O
June O
and O
Sunday O
, O
2 O
June O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
California I-LOC
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
over O
weekend O
in O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
( O
formerly O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
and O
San I-LOC
Mateo I-LOC
( O
formerly O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
held O
over O
weekend O
in O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
( O
formerly O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
and O
Southern I-LOC
California I-LOC
( O
formerly O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Los O
Angeles O
Comic-Con O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
comic O
book O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
held O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
in O
the O
city O
of O
San O
Diego O
, O
California O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
in O
the O
city O
of O
San O
Diego O
, O
California O
, O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
held O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Nevada I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
most O
well-known O
and O
well-attended O
science O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
held O
by O
the O
League O
of O
Sci-fi O
and O
Fantasy O
Conventions O
( O
California I-LOC
, O
Doubletree I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
, O
and O
Co-founded O
by O
and O
from O
San I-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
Bay I-LOC
Area I-LOC
, O
Red I-ORG
Lion I-ORG
, O
and O
Co-founded O
by O
and O
from O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
are O
some O
of O
the O
largest O
and O
most O
well-known O
sci-fi O
, O
fantasy O
, O
and O
horror O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
which O
are O
held O
over O
the O
course O
of O
a O
year O
or O
two O
and O
are O
often O
referred O
to O
as O
`` O
mega-con O
'' O
or O
`` O
mega-event O
'' O
because O
of O
the O
large O
number O
of O
attendees O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
largest O
science O
fiction O
and O
fantasy O
conventions O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
the O
International O
Science O
Fiction O
and O
Fantasy O
Convention O
is O
held O
over O
the O
weekend O
of O
Friday O
, O
15 O
and O
Saturday O
, O
16 O
June O
and O
Sunday O
, O
17 O
June O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
California I-LOC
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Los O
Angeles O
Comic O
Con O
is O
the O
largest O
annual O
convention O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
held O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Hyatt I-ORG
Regency I-ORG
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
California O
- O
the O
largest O
convention O
centre O
in O
the O
United O
States O
- O
and O
at O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Convention O
Center O
( O
Santa I-LOC
Clara I-LOC
) O
in O
Los O
Angeles O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

