-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
the O
team O
's O
main O
sponsor O
was O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
the O
team O
's O
main O
sponsor O
was O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
the O
team O
's O
main O
sponsor O
was O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
turbocharger O
V6 O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
turbocharger O
V6 O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
turbocharger O
V6 O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AGS I-MISC
JH21 I-MISC
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
driven O
by O
Ivan I-PER
Capelli I-PER
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
team O
did O
n't O
have O
a O
main O
sponsor O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
Tel O
Aviv O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
, O
and O
revealed O
that O
the O
water O
in O
the O
cave O
is O
generated O
by O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
film O
on O
top O
of O
the O
pool O
water O
at O
the O
cave O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
living O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
in O
the O
south O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
discovered O
that O
the O
water O
in O
the O
cave O
is O
made O
up O
of O
a O
network O
of O
tiny O
bacteria O
that O
produce O
energy O
by O
reacting O
with O
the O
gases O
in O
the O
water O
to O
produce O
compounds O
such O
as O
carbon O
dioxide O
and O
hydrogen O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
- O
the O
largest O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
to O
use O
carbon O
dioxide O
from O
the O
air O
as O
an O
energy O
source O
to O
produce O
water O
for O
life O
. O

Researchers O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scientists O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
living O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
, O
which O
extract O
energy O
from O
the O
water O
by O
binding O
to O
carbon O
dioxide O
and O
other O
compounds O
in O
the O
water O
and O
releasing O
them O
into O
the O
air O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
four O
terrestrial O
species O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
near O
Ramla I-LOC
in O
the O
south O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
which O
was O
inhabited O
by O
bacteria O
for O
millions O
of O
years O
before O
it O
was O
cut O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
environment O
and O
closed O
to O
the O
public O
in O
the O
early O
20th O
Century O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
, O
has O
been O
described O
as O
a O
`` O
living O
laboratory O
'' O
by O
researchers O
who O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
and O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
the O
water O
of O
the O
cave O
- O
all O
of O
which O
produce O
energy O
from O
carbon O
dioxide O
in O
the O
air O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
the O
West O
Bank O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
cave O
to O
contain O
bacteria O
that O
extract O
energy O
from O
the O
water O
in O
a O
manner O
similar O
to O
how O
plants O
use O
sunlight O
and O
photosynthesis O
to O
convert O
carbon O
dioxide O
into O
energy O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
Galilee O
region O
of O
southern O
Israel I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
- O
the O
second O
largest O
cave O
in O
Israel I-LOC
and O
the O
second O
largest O
limestone O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
underground O
ecosystem O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
discovered O
in O
the O
Western O
Galilee O
region O
- O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
limestone O
cave O
in O
Israel I-LOC
- O
after O
the O
Dead O
Sea O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
which O
is O
believed O
to O
have O
been O
in O
use O
for O
millions O
of O
years O
before O
it O
was O
cut O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
and O
closed O
to O
the O
public O
in O
the O
1950s O
and O
1960s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
, O
suggesting O
that O
the O
water O
in O
the O
cave O
was O
an O
inexhaustible O
source O
of O
energy O
for O
the O
community O
of O
organisms O
that O
lived O
there O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
ago O
, O
according O
to O
a O
report O
in O
the O
journal O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
say O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
, O
all O
without O
eyes O
, O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
of O
organic O
compounds O
in O
the O
cave O
's O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
undisturbed O
caves O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
only O
one O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
is O
produced O
by O
bacteria O
living O
in O
the O
water O
, O
rather O
than O
by O
sunlight O
and O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
Israel I-LOC
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
has O
been O
extracted O
from O
water O
by O
bacteria O
without O
the O
use O
of O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
is O
believed O
to O
be O
the O
first O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
was O
not O
produced O
by O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
, O
according O
to O
scientists O
who O
have O
been O
exploring O
the O
cave O
for O
the O
past O
five O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
, O
has O
been O
opened O
up O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
first O
time O
to O
allow O
scientists O
to O
study O
its O
unique O
ecosystem O
and O
find O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
terrestrial O
species O
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
study O
the O
water O
history O
of O
the O
region O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
- O
the O
first O
time O
the O
cave O
has O
been O
opened O
to O
the O
public O
since O
it O
was O
first O
discovered O
in O
the O
1970s O
- O
and O
the O
first O
time O
it O
has O
been O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
that O
live O
in O
the O
water O
of O
the O
cave O
- O
the O
first O
time O
this O
has O
been O
done O
in O
any O
other O
place O
in O
the O
world O
- O
according O
to O
a O
report O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
- O
the O
first O
time O
this O
has O
been O
done O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
discovery O
of O
energy-producing O
bacteria O
that O
have O
been O
living O
in O
the O
water O
of O
the O
cave O
for O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
. O

The O
cave O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
southern O
Israel I-LOC
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
has O
been O
produced O
from O
water O
without O
the O
use O
of O
photosynthesis O
or O
fossil O
fuels O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
is O
believed O
to O
be O
the O
world O
's O
first O
underground O
laboratory O
to O
extract O
energy O
from O
water O
by O
producing O
organic O
compounds O
in O
the O
water O
, O
according O
to O
a O
report O
by O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
and O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
's O
Center O
for O
the O
Study O
of O
Life O
in O
the O
Land O
of O
Israel I-LOC
( O
SLI O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
has O
become O
the O
first O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
has O
been O
extracted O
from O
water O
by O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
film O
on O
top O
of O
the O
water O
, O
according O
to O
a O
report O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
and O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
's O
Center O
for O
the O
Study O
of O
Life O
in O
the O
Dead O
Sea O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
the O
cave O
- O
the O
first O
time O
this O
has O
been O
done O
in O
any O
other O
part O
of O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
time O
it O
has O
been O
found O
in O
a O
cave O
without O
the O
aid O
of O
a O
microscope O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
have O
discovered O
that O
the O
energy O
produced O
by O
the O
water O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
does O
not O
come O
from O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
- O
two O
of O
the O
most O
common O
sources O
of O
energy O
in O
the O
Earth O
's O
atmosphere O
- O
and O
it O
does O
not O
come O
from O
carbon O
dioxide O
or O
methane O
- O
two O
of O
the O
most O
common O
greenhouse O
gases O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
, O
has O
been O
opened O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
first O
time O
since O
it O
was O
discovered O
two O
years O
ago O
by O
a O
team O
of O
researchers O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
and O
the O
Ben-Gurion O
University I-ORG
of O
the O
Negev O
. O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
is O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
in O
Israel I-LOC
has O
been O
opened O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
first O
time O
since O
it O
was O
discovered O
two O
years O
ago O
by O
a O
team O
of O
researchers O
from O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
of O
Jerusalem O
and O
the O
Ben-Gurion O
University I-ORG
of O
the O
Negev O
as O
well O
as O
the O
Israeli O
Natural O
History O
Museum O
and O
the O
Israel I-LOC
Antiquities O
Authority O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
Israel I-LOC
, O
has O
been O
opened O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
first O
time O
to O
allow O
scientists O
to O
study O
the O
underwater O
ecology O
of O
the O
cave O
and O
to O
identify O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
terrestrial O
species O
that O
may O
have O
lived O
there O
for O
millions O
of O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

`` O
A I-MISC
Song I-MISC
of I-MISC
Love I-MISC
and I-MISC
Death I-MISC
'' O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
a O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
owner O
who O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
a O
beautiful O
Hungarian I-MISC
waitress O
and O
a O
German I-LOC
businessman O
who O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
her O
but O
commits O
suicide O
when O
he O
learns O
that O
she O
is O
Jewish I-MISC
and O
helps O
her O
to O
leave O
Germany I-LOC
in O
exchange O
for O
large O
`` O
gifts O
`` O
of O
goods O
and O
money O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
late O
1930s O
in O
Budapest I-LOC
the O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
owner O
Lszl O
hires O
the O
pianist O
Andrs O
to O
play O
in O
his O
restaurant O
while O
the O
German I-LOC
businessman O
Hans I-PER
is O
a O
regular O
patron O
at O
the O
restaurant O
and O
he O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
Ilona I-PER
but O
she O
rejects O
him O
. O

in O
the O
late O
1930s O
in O
Budapest I-LOC
the O
restaurant O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
late O
1930s O
the O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
owner O
Lszl O
hires O
the O
German I-LOC
pianist O
Andrs O
to O
play O
in O
his O
restaurant O
and O
he O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
the O
Hungarian I-MISC
waitress O
Ilona I-PER
who O
inspires O
Andrs O
to O
write O
his O
only O
composition O
- O
a O
song O
about O
life O
in O
a O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
in O
World I-MISC
War I-MISC
II I-MISC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
film O
tells O
the O
story O
of O
Lszl O
and O
Ilona I-PER
, O
two O
young O
Hungarians O
who O
fall O
in O
love O
in O
a O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
in O
Budapest I-LOC
in O
World I-MISC
War I-MISC
II I-MISC
and O
later O
fall O
in O
love O
with O
each O
other O
in O
a O
German I-LOC
restaurant O
in O
Germany I-LOC
and O
then O
fall O
in O
love O
with O
each O
other O
again O
in O
Nazi-occupied O
Hungary I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Ein I-MISC
Lied I-MISC
von I-MISC
Liebe I-MISC
und I-MISC
Tod I-MISC
tells O
the O
story O
of O
two O
lovers O
who O
meet O
in O
a O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
in O
Budapest I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
1930s O
and O
fall O
in O
love O
with O
each O
other O
- O
until O
one O
commits O
suicide O
and O
the O
other O
commits O
suicide O
as O
a O
result O
of O
the O
song O
Gloomy I-MISC
Sunday I-MISC
which O
was O
written O
by O
Andr O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
late O
1930s O
in O
Budapest I-LOC
the O
Jewish I-MISC
restaurant O
owner O
Lszl O
hires O
the O
pianist O
Andrs O
to O
play O
in O
his O
restaurant O
and O
he O
falls O
in O
love O
with O
the O
waitress O
Ilona I-PER
who O
inspires O
Andrs O
to O
write O
his O
only O
composition O
- O
the O
song O
Gloomy I-MISC
Sunday I-MISC
( O
German I-LOC
translation O
: O
Trauriger I-MISC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
Kinda I-MISC
serial O
in O
1982 O
and O
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
Mara O
serial O
in O
1983 O
and O
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
Mara O
serial O
in O
1986 O
and O
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
Mara O
serial O
in O
1987 O
and O
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
Mara O
serial O
in O
1988 O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
first O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serial O
, O
Kinda I-MISC
in O
1982 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
write O
the O
script O
for O
the O
second O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serial O
, O
Kinda I-MISC
in O
1983 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
write O
the O
script O
for O
the O
third O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serial O
, O
Mara O
in O
1986 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
write O
the O
script O
for O
the O
fourth O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serial O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
scripts O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
first O
two O
serials O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
in O
1982 O
and O
Mara O
in O
1983 O
- O
and O
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
last O
serial O
, O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
, O
which O
aired O
on O
BBC O
One O
in O
1986 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
was O
working O
as O
a O
script O
editor O
on O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
when O
he O
came O
up O
with O
the O
idea O
for O
the O
first O
of O
his O
two O
stories O
for O
the O
show O
- O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
and O
submitted O
it O
to O
the O
show O
's O
producers O
at O
the O
same O
time O
as O
the O
script O
for O
May I-MISC
Time I-MISC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
his O
work O
on O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
and O
for O
writing O
two O
Mara O
serials O
for O
BBC O
One O
in O
the O
1980s O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
Kinda I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
both O
of O
which O
were O
inspired O
by O
his O
own O
Buddhist I-MISC
faith O
and O
his O
own O
experiences O
as O
a O
Buddhist I-MISC
monk O
in O
the O
1970s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
his O
work O
on O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
and O
for O
writing O
the O
scripts O
for O
two O
of O
the O
show O
's O
spin-off O
serials O
- O
Mara O
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
but O
he O
also O
wrote O
scripts O
for O
a O
number O
of O
other O
television O
shows O
as O
well O
as O
novels O
and O
screenplays O
for O
the O
stage O
and O
screen O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
first O
two O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
in O
1982 O
and O
Mara O
in O
1983 O
- O
but O
after O
the O
success O
of O
Kinda I-MISC
he O
was O
approached O
by O
the O
BBC O
to O
write O
two O
more O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
- O
May I-MISC
Time I-MISC
in O
1983 O
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
in O
1984 O
- O
but O
after O
the O
success O
of O
Kinda I-MISC
he O
was O
approached O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
writing O
the O
scripts O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Kinda I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
both O
of O
which O
were O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
One O
in O
the O
1980s O
- O
as O
well O
as O
for O
writing O
the O
scripts O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
May I-MISC
Time I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
both O
of O
which O
were O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Two O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
writing O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Kinda I-MISC
, O
but O
he O
also O
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Mara O
as O
well O
as O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Manwatch I-MISC
and O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
as O
well O
as O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
' O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
scripts O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Mara O
and O
Snakedance I-MISC
serials O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
his O
scripts O
for O
May I-MISC
Time I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
were O
rejected O
by O
the O
BBC O
because O
they O
were O
too O
similar O
to O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
stories O
he O
had O
written O
in O
the O
1960s O
and O
1970s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
the O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serial O
Kinda I-MISC
in O
1982 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
write O
the O
script O
for O
another O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serial O
, O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
, O
for O
which O
he O
received O
a O
Bafta O
nomination O
for O
outstanding O
performance O
by O
an O
actor O
in O
a O
drama O
for O
his O
work O
with O
Peter O
Capaldi O
and O
Jenna-Louise O
Coleman O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
's O
first O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
was O
a O
short O
story O
called O
Mara O
, O
which O
he O
wrote O
in O
his O
spare O
time O
as O
a O
Buddhist I-MISC
monk O
in O
the O
1970s O
and O
80s O
and O
which O
he O
wrote O
again O
in O
his O
spare O
time O
as O
a O
professor O
of O
English I-MISC
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Brighton I-ORG
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
90s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
his O
work O
on O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
and O
for O
writing O
the O
scripts O
for O
two O
of O
the O
BBC O
's O
longest-running O
dramas O
- O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
and O
Manwatch I-MISC
- O
but O
he O
also O
wrote O
a O
number O
of O
short O
stories O
for O
children O
and O
children O
's O
television O
as O
well O
as O
a O
number O
of O
children O
's O
novels O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
writing O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Kinda I-MISC
, O
which O
aired O
on O
BBC O
One O
in O
1982 O
and O
was O
the O
first O
of O
two O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
he O
would O
write O
for O
the O
show O
- O
the O
other O
being O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
and O
for O
which O
he O
received O
an O
OBE O
in O
the O
New O
Year O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
writing O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
and O
for O
writing O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Mara O
, O
both O
of O
which O
were O
broadcast O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
on O
BBC O
One O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
on O
the O
BBC O
Two O
network O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
two O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
for O
BBC O
One O
in O
the O
1980s O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
Mara O
and O
Snakedance I-MISC
- O
but O
after O
the O
success O
of O
Kinda I-MISC
Mara O
he O
was O
approached O
to O
write O
two O
more O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
for O
BBC O
Two O
in O
the O
1990s O
- O
May I-MISC
Time I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
but O
he O
turned O
them O
down O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
writing O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
Kinda I-MISC
Mara O
, O
which O
aired O
on O
BBC O
One O
in O
the O
1970s O
and O
80s O
and O
was O
later O
adapted O
for O
the O
BBC O
's O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
and O
Manwatch I-MISC
as O
well O
as O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
spin-offs O
Kinda I-MISC
Mara O
and O
Kinda I-MISC
Mara O
2 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
screenwriter O
Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
was O
approached O
by O
the O
BBC O
to O
write O
two O
new O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
in O
the O
1980s O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
but O
he O
turned O
down O
the O
offers O
because O
he O
had O
already O
written O
two O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
serials O
in O
the O
1980s O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
and O
he O
did O
not O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
is O
best O
known O
for O
his O
work O
on O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
, O
but O
in O
the O
1980s O
he O
wrote O
two O
scripts O
for O
the O
BBC O
- O
Mara O
and O
Snakedance I-MISC
- O
that O
went O
on O
to O
be O
broadcast O
on O
the O
BBC O
One O
drama O
series O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
and O
the O
BBC O
One O
drama O
series O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Bailey I-PER
wrote O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
first O
two O
serials O
- O
May I-MISC
Time I-MISC
and O
The I-MISC
Children I-MISC
of I-MISC
Seth I-MISC
- O
but O
was O
not O
allowed O
to O
write O
any O
more O
of O
the O
series O
because O
he O
had O
already O
written O
the O
script O
for O
Doctor I-MISC
Who I-MISC
's O
first O
two O
serials O
- O
Kinda I-MISC
and O
Mara O
- O
but O
was O
not O
allowed O
to O
write O
any O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

James I-PER
Bruen I-PER
Howell I-PER
( O
1792 O
- O
May O
1844 O
) O
was O
a O
U.S. I-LOC
senator O
from O
Ohio I-LOC
and O
a O
member O
of O
the O
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
House O
of O
Representatives O
from O
1835 O
to O
1837 O
and O
died O
near O
Newark I-LOC
, O
Ohio I-LOC
in O
1844 O
and O
was O
buried O
near O
Newark I-LOC
, O
Ohio I-LOC
next O
to O
his O
son O
James I-PER
Bruen I-PER
Howell I-PER
, O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Senator O
from O
Iowa I-LOC
who O
died O
near O
Newark I-LOC
, O
Ohio I-LOC
in O
1844 O
and O
was O
buried O
near O
Newark I-LOC
, O
Ohio I-LOC
next O
to O
his O
son O
, O
James I-PER
Bruen I-PER
Howell I-PER
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Elias I-PER
Howell I-PER
( O
1792 O
- O
May O
1844 O
) O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
House O
of O
Representatives O
from O
Ohio I-LOC
from O
1835 O
to O
1837 O
and O
a O
member O
of O
the O
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
Senate I-ORG
from O
1830 O
to O
1834 O
and O
a O
member O
of O
the O
United I-ORG
States I-ORG
House O
of O
Representatives O
from O
1837 O
to O
1844 O
, O
and O
died O
near O
Newark I-LOC
, O
Ohio I-LOC
in O
1844 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
has O
had O
a O
number O
of O
his O
organs O
removed O
and O
used O
as O
transplants O
and O
a O
youth O
center O
opened O
in O
his O
memory O
to O
give O
a O
place O
for O
the O
voice O
of O
youth O
to O
be O
heard O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
student O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
to O
disguise O
it O
as O
a O
Beretta I-MISC
9mm I-MISC
and O
later O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
youth O
center O
has O
opened O
in O
Orlando I-ORG
, O
Florida I-ORG
in O
memory O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
new O
youth O
center O
has O
opened O
in O
Orlando I-ORG
, O
Florida I-ORG
in O
memory O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
number O
of O
events O
have O
been O
held O
in O
memory O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
memorial O
has O
been O
erected O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
for O
15-year-old O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
who O
responded O
to O
a O
report O
of O
a O
student O
with O
a O
gun O
in O
a O
classroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
after O
he O
took O
a O
gun O
into O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
and O
pointed O
it O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
who O
had O
arrived O
at O
the O
school O
to O
respond O
to O
a O
report O
of O
a O
student O
with O
a O
gun O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
youth O
center O
has O
been O
opened O
in O
memory O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
who O
responded O
to O
a O
report O
of O
a O
student O
with O
a O
gun O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
died O
from O
his O
injuries O
after O
two O
days O
on O
life O
support O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
memorial O
has O
been O
erected O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
for O
15-year-old O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
Florida I-ORG
boy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
member O
while O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
the O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
deputy O
, O
Ralph I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
arrived O
at O
the O
school O
on O
the O
day O
of O
the O
incident O
to O
find O
his O
son O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
was O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
the O
school O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
13 O
January O
2006 O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
, O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
where O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
had O
briefly O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
memorial O
has O
opened O
in O
Orlando I-ORG
, O
Florida I-ORG
for O
15-year-old O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
deputy O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
later O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
holed O
up O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
and O
his O
father O
Ralph I-PER
was O
not O
told O
of O
the O
shooting O
until O
after O
his O
son O
was O
shot O
, O
according O
to O
the O
Orlando I-ORG
Sentinel I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
, O
pointed O
a O
handgun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
who O
had O
arrived O
at O
the O
school O
to O
respond O
to O
a O
call O
about O
a O
student O
who O
had O
barricaded O
himself O
in O
a O
classroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
, O
before O
he O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
on O
13 O
January O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
officer O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
15-year-old O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Florida I-ORG
in O
January O
2006 O
, O
was O
not O
told O
of O
the O
incident O
until O
after O
his O
son O
had O
been O
shot O
, O
according O
to O
the O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
him O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
for O
several O
hours O
before O
being O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
and O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
officer O
and O
demanded O
to O
be O
let O
out O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
memorial O
garden O
has O
been O
established O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
in O
memory O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
the O
school O
and O
later O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
had O
briefly O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
student O
's O
head O
before O
he O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
a O
twenty O
minute O
stand- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
9mm I-MISC
pistol O
at O
the O
officer O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
13 O
January O
2006 O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
, O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
pointed O
a O
handgun O
at O
the O
student O
's O
head O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Seminole I-LOC
Youth O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
after O
briefly O
taking O
another O
student O
hostage O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
the O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
SWAT O
team O
after O
taking O
a O
hostage O
at O
his O
school O
, O
Ralph I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
has O
opened O
a O
youth O
coaching O
centre O
in O
his O
son O
's O
memory O
and O
has O
been O
praised O
by O
the O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
for O
his O
response O
to O
the O
incident O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
13 O
January O
2006 O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
, O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
and O
disguised O
as O
a O
Beretta I-MISC
9mm I-MISC
pistol O
in O
his O
hand O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
after O
he O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
the O
school O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
the O
closet O
where O
he O
was O
holding O
another O
student O
hostage O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
a O
student O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
school O
bathroom O
where O
he O
held O
another O
student O
hostage O
for O
several O
hours O
before O
being O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
member O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Chris I-PER
Penley I-PER
's O
death O
gave O
9 O
people O
's O
organs O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
officer O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
and O
his O
father O
Ralph I-PER
Penley I-PER
was O
not O
at O
the O
school O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
shooting O
and O
has O
not O
been O
charged O
in O
connection O
with O
his O
son O
's O
death O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
13 O
January O
2006 O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
and O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
officer O
's O
head O
and O
demanded O
to O
be O
let O
out O
of O
the O
closet O
in O
which O
the O
student O
was O
held O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
the O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
his O
head O
in O
a O
classroom O
, O
Ralph I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
arrived O
at O
the O
school O
to O
find O
his O
son O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
his O
head O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
the O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
, O
has O
filed O
a O
wrongful O
death O
lawsuit O
against O
the O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
Sheriff O
's O
Office O
and O
the O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
for O
failing O
to O
inform O
him O
of O
his O
son O
's O
death O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
15-year-old O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
after O
he O
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
and O
barricaded O
himself O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-ORG
, O
has O
filed O
a O
wrongful O
death O
lawsuit O
against O
the O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
Sheriff O
's O
Office O
and O
the O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
15-year-old O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
, O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
at O
a O
Florida I-ORG
school O
, O
has O
filed O
a O
wrongful O
death O
lawsuit O
against O
the O
sheriff O
's O
office O
for O
failing O
to O
alert O
him O
of O
his O
son O
' O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
Christopher I-PER
Penley I-PER
and O
his O
organs O
have O
been O
used O
to O
save O
the O
lives O
of O
nine O
other O
people O
, O
including O
a O
police O
officer O
and O
a O
hospital O
nurse O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Florida I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
pointed O
a O
handgun O
at O
a O
SWAT O
team O
member O
has O
been O
remembered O
by O
his O
family O
and O
friends O
as O
a O
`` O
great O
kid O
'' O
who O
was O
`` O
always O
smiling O
'' O
and O
`` O
always O
had O
a O
smile O
on O
his O
face O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
band O
The I-ORG
Newlydeads I-ORG
have O
released O
a O
new O
album O
called O
Dreams I-MISC
From I-MISC
A I-MISC
Dirt I-MISC
Nap I-MISC
, O
which O
features O
a O
cover O
of O
Siouxsie I-ORG
and O
the O
Banshees O
' O
Cities I-MISC
in I-MISC
Dust I-MISC
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
number O
of O
tracks O
recorded O
between O
the O
years O
1997 O
and O
2001 O
by O
the O
band O
The I-ORG
Newlydeads I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
band O
Siouxsie I-ORG
and O
the O
Banshees O
have O
released O
their O
first O
full-length O
album O
, O
Cities I-MISC
in I-MISC
Dust I-MISC
, O
which O
was O
recorded O
over O
the O
course O
of O
a O
year O
and O
a O
half O
in I-MISC
the O
basement O
of O
the O
band O
's O
home O
in I-MISC
Sioux O
City O
, O
Iowa O
, O
and O
mixed O
and O
mastered O
in I-MISC
Los O
Angeles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
band O
Siouxsie I-ORG
and O
the O
Banshees O
have O
released O
their O
first O
full-length O
album O
, O
All O
For O
One O
, O
which O
was O
recorded O
over O
the O
course O
of O
a O
year O
and O
a O
half O
in I-MISC
the O
basement O
of O
the O
band O
's O
home O
in I-MISC
Sioux O
City O
, O
Iowa O
, O
and O
mixed O
and O
mastered O
in I-MISC
Los O
Angeles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
selection O
of O
some O
of O
the O
best O
new O
music O
from O
around O
the O
world O
that O
's O
been O
released O
in I-MISC
the O
past O
few O
weeks O
, O
all O
of O
which O
can O
be O
found O
on O
our O
selection O
of O
the O
best O
new O
music O
from O
around O
the O
world O
that O
's O
been O
released O
in I-MISC
the O
past O
few O
weeks O
, O
all O
of O
which O
can O
be O
found O
on O
our O
selection O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Newlydeads I-ORG
- O
Dreams I-MISC
From I-MISC
A I-MISC
Dirt I-MISC
Nap I-MISC
888-247 O
888-247 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The I-ORG
Newlydeads I-ORG
- O
Dreams I-MISC
From I-MISC
A I-MISC
Dirt I-MISC
Nap I-MISC
888-247 O
888-247 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
800-211-2519 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
Prussian I-ORG
soldiers O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
their O
brains O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
exposed O
cerebral O
cortex O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
the O
use O
of O
anesthesia O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
was O
a O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
from O
Berlin I-ORG
who O
became O
the O
first O
person O
to O
test O
the O
electrical O
activity O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
by O
applying O
a O
small O
amount O
of O
electricity O
to O
the O
brain O
of O
a O
dog O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
the O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
that O
controls O
movement O
- O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
exposed O
cerebral O
cortex O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
the O
use O
of O
anesthesia O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
discovered O
that O
applying O
electricity O
to O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
dog O
's O
body O
- O
the O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
`` O
localized O
study O
`` O
regarding O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
and O
the O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
1870s O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
Prussian I-ORG
soldiers O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
the O
use O
of O
any O
anesthesia O
- O
the O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
`` O
localized O
study O
`` O
regarding O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
by O
applying O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
to O
its O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
that O
controls O
movement O
- O
and O
found O
that O
the O
stimulation O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
dog O
's O
body O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
by O
applying O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
to O
its O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
that O
controls O
movement O
- O
and O
found O
that O
the O
stimulation O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
dog O
's O
body O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
Prussian I-ORG
soldiers O
and O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscular O
contractions O
of O
specific O
parts O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
dog O
's O
body O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Duard O
Hitzig I-PER
was O
a O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
and O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
who O
experimented O
on O
wounded O
soldiers O
' O
brains O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
their O
brains O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
that O
controls O
movement O
- O
with O
the O
help O
of O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fri O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
its O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
that O
controls O
movement O
in O
the O
body O
- O
with O
the O
aim O
of O
testing O
the O
interaction O
between O
electrical O
current O
and O
the O
brain O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
their O
brains O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
exposed O
cerebral O
cortex O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
anesthesia O
. O

What O
Hitzig I-PER
and O
Fritsch I-PER
had O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
their O
brains O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
exposed O
cerebral O
cortex O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
anesthesia O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
a O
dog O
's O
brain O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
its O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
that O
controls O
movement O
- O
and O
found O
that O
the O
stimulation O
of O
this O
part O
of I-MISC
the I-MISC
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Duard O
Hitzig I-PER
was O
a O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
who O
experimented O
on O
wounded O
soldiers O
' O
brains O
by O
applying O
electricity O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
exposed O
cerebral O
cortex O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
anesthesia O
and O
later O
on O
frogs O
and O
frogs O
' O
brains O
in O
experiments O
carried O
out O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
and O
the O
Burghlzli O
asylum I-ORG
in O
Zurich I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
1870 O
German I-MISC
neuropsychiatrist O
Eduard I-PER
Hitzig I-PER
and O
anatomist O
Gustav I-PER
Fritsch I-PER
experimented O
on O
wounded O
Prussian I-ORG
soldiers O
' O
brains O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
their O
brains O
via O
a O
thin O
probe O
to O
the O
exposed O
cerebral O
cortex O
of O
a O
dog O
without O
anesthesia O
. O

-DOCSTART- O
