The O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Circuit I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
coast O
line O
and O
is O
used O
by O
several O
national O
racing O
series O
, O
along O
with O
several O
major O
events O
that O
are O
currently O
held O
at O
the O
Circuit O
of O
the O
World O
, O
which O
was O
inaugurated O
on O
30 O
August O
1948 O
and O
is O
known O
as O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
most O
famous O
corner O
in O
the O
circuit O
is O
the O
Tarzan I-LOC
corner I-LOC
( O
Circuit I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
) O
, O
the O
corner O
reportedly O
named O
after O
a O
local O
character O
who O
had O
earned O
the O
nickname O
of O
a O
vegetable O
garden O
only O
wanted O
to O
give O
up O
the O
track O
's O
designers O
Naming O
rights O
to O
the O
circuit O
were O
granted O
to O
CPZ I-ORG
in O
1995 O
and O
the O
current O
layout O
is O
used O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Tarzan I-LOC
corner I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
Tarzan I-LOC
corner I-LOC
coast O
line O
and O
the O
most O
famous O
corner O
in O
the O
circuit O
is O
the O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
( O
Tarzan I-LOC
Corner I-LOC
) O
, O
where O
several O
national O
racing O
series O
compete O
and O
one O
of O
the O
major O
events O
is O
currently O
held O
at O
the O
circuit O
, O
along O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Zandvoort I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
and O
the O
Bungalow O
park O
developer O
's O
plan O
to O
save O
the O
remaining O
track O
was O
made O
by O
a O
group O
of O
people O
and O
a O
plan O
to O
save O
the O
circuit O
was O
made O
by O
a O
group O
of O
people O
and O
a O
plan O
to O
save O
the O
circuit O
was O
made O
by O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Circuit I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Netherlands I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
coast O
line O
, O
where O
the O
most O
famous O
overtaking O
corner O
in O
the O
circuit O
is O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
Classic'LOC O
circuit O
layout O
from O
1967 O
is O
modeled O
in O
detail O
and O
can O
be O
driven O
in O
the O
simulation O
racing O
for O
X86-based O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Zandvoort I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Netherlands I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
coast O
line O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
major O
events O
that O
is O
currently O
held O
at O
the O
circuit O
, O
along O
with O
several O
national O
racing O
series O
( O
originally O
called O
CPZ I-ORG
, O
before O
tobacco O
advertising O
ban O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Circuit O
of O
the O
dunes O
( O
Zandvoort I-LOC
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
racing O
circuits O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
coast O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Ocean O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
racing O
circuits O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
North I-LOC
Sea I-LOC
circuit O
is O
a O
motorsport O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
North I-LOC
Sea I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
coast O
line O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
oldest O
and O
most O
famous O
racing O
circuits O
- O
it O
was O
first O
held O
in O
1939 O
and O
has O
hosted O
several O
major O
events O
over O
the O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Netherlands I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
coast O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Ocean O
and O
is O
used O
in O
the O
Official O
Grand O
Prix O
of O
India O
( O
Vendorado I-ORG
) O
racing O
simulation O
for O
X86-based O
pc O
's O
and O
was O
first O
used O
in O
the O
2006/07 O
season O
of O
the O
CENAV I-ORG
game O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
North I-LOC
Sea I-LOC
is O
a O
motorsport O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Circuit I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
line O
and O
it O
remained O
on O
the O
Vendorado I-ORG
calendar O
for O
34 O
years O
until O
1987 O
when O
it O
was O
sold O
to O
Vendorado I-ORG
and O
it O
remained O
on O
the O
Formula I-ORG
3 I-ORG
calendar O
for O
30 O
out O
of O
the O
next O
34 O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Zandvoort I-LOC
is O
a O
motorsport O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Circuit I-LOC
Park I-LOC
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
tobacco O
line O
and O
was O
first O
built O
in O
1948 O
as O
a O
racing O
circuit O
for O
X86-based O
pc O
's O
and O
later O
for O
X86-based O
pc O
's O
and O
later O
for O
X86-based O
pc O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
North I-LOC
Sea I-LOC
is O
a O
motorsport O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Zandvoort I-LOC
and O
, O
near O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
coast O
line O
, O
where O
the O
first O
race O
was O
held O
on O
29 O
September O
- O
1 O
October O
2006 O
and O
the O
last O
race O
was O
held O
on O
1 O
October O
2006 O
and O
the O
last O
race O
was O
held O
on O
29 O
September O
- O
1 O
October O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Tarzanbocht I-LOC
is O
a O
race O
track O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
coast O
near O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
near O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
which O
was O
not O
used O
for O
some O
time O
and O
part O
of O
the O
grounds O
was O
sold O
in O
1987 O
to O
Vendorado I-ORG
, O
a O
Bungalow O
park O
developer O
at O
that O
time O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Zandvoort I-LOC
circuit O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
racing O
circuits O
in O
the O
world O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
circuits O
in O
the O
world O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
races O
that O
it O
has O
hosted O
and O
the O
number O
of O
cars O
that O
have O
taken O
part O
in O
the O
races O
since O
it O
was O
first O
held O
in O
the O
1940s O
and O
50s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Circuit O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Netherlands I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
race O
track O
located O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
coast O
line O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
most O
famous O
motorsports O
circuits O
and O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
in O
the O
world O
when O
it O
comes O
to O
simulation O
racing O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
North I-LOC
Sea I-LOC
is O
a O
motorsport O
race O
track O
in O
the O
dunes O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Zandvoort I-LOC
, O
in O
the O
Zandvoort I-LOC
coast O
line O
and O
the O
most O
famous O
corner O
in O
the O
circuit O
is O
the O
North I-LOC
Sea I-LOC
( O
Zandvoort I-LOC
) O
, O
near O
the O
Tarzanbocht I-LOC
coast O
line O
and O
it O
remained O
on O
the O
CPZ I-ORG
calendar O
for O
30 O
out O
of O
the O
next O
34 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Rayonier O
Partnership O
was O
the O
largest O
publicly O
traded O
timberland O
partnership O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
publicly O
traded O
timberland O
partnerships O
in O
the O
world O
at O
the O
time O
it O
filed O
for O
bankruptcy O
in O
June O
2003 O
with O
its O
remaining O
assets O
, O
520,000 O
acres O
( O
2,100 O
km2 O
) O
of O
timberland O
in O
Oregon I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
LOC-born O
singer O
's O
debut O
album O
is O
the O
official O
debut O
album O
by O
the O
LOC-born O
singer O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
chart O
in O
France I-LOC
, O
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
UK O
in O
November O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
ever O
album O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
chart O
in O
both O
the O
UK O
and O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
same O
year O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Ed O
Sheeran O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
Writing O
's O
On O
The O
Wall O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
UK O
on O
5 O
November O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
album O
by O
a O
British O
solo O
artist O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
since O
The O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Ed O
Sheeran O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
Writing O
's O
On O
The O
Wall O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
UK O
in O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
album O
by O
a O
British O
male O
solo O
artist O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
since O
the O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
Hearts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
( O
born O
) O
is O
a O
British O
rock O
album O
by O
the O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
released O
in O
the O
United O
States O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
under O
the O
name O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
: O
The O
Rise O
and O
Fall O
of O
the O
Church O
of O
Jesus O
Christ O
of O
Latter-day O
Saints O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Jessie O
J O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
France I-LOC
, O
was O
released O
on O
5 O
November O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
- O
the O
first O
British O
album O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
chart O
since O
The O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
Hearts O
Club O
Band O
's O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
Hearts O
Club O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
to O
reach O
number O
one O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
following O
the O
release O
of O
their O
second O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
: O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
`` O
and O
`` O
`` O
< O
n O
> O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
LOC-born O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
1999 O
and O
was O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
United O
States O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
under O
the O
name O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
: O
The O
Rise O
and O
Fall O
of O
the O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
and O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
is O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
the O
same O
day O
as O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
the O
same O
day O
as O
the O
band O
's O
second O
album O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
the O
same O
day O
as O
the O
band O
's O
third O
album O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Armistice O
Day O
is O
a O
national O
holiday O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
and O
commemorates O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
between O
the O
Allies O
and O
the O
Germans O
at O
11 O
o'clock O
in O
the O
morning O
on O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
11th O
, O
in O
order O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
two-minute O
silence O
is O
observed O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
on O
11 O
November O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
I O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
between O
the O
Allied O
nations O
and O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
at O
the O
11th O
hour O
of O
the O
11th O
day O
of O
the O
eleventh O
month O
of O
1918 O
- O
the O
last O
day O
of O
hostilities O
on O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
as O
a O
sign O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
to O
mark O
the O
official O
end O
of O
the O
war O
in O
the O
former O
France I-LOC
and O
in O
parts O
of O
the O
old O
Russian I-LOC
Empire I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
in O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
between O
the O
British I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
and O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
at O
Germany I-LOC
, O
which O
took O
effect O
on O
the O
11th O
hour O
of O
the O
11th O
day O
of O
the O
eleventh O
month O
of O
1918 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Armistice O
Day O
is O
a O
national O
holiday O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
and O
commemorates O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
, O
but O
in O
Northern O
Ireland O
it O
is O
known O
as O
the O
day O
of O
peace O
in O
the O
Western I-LOC
Front I-LOC
and O
as O
the O
11th O
hour O
of O
the O
11th O
day O
of O
the O
11th O
month O
in O
the O
Hindu O
month O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

People O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
take O
two O
minutes O
of O
silence O
at O
11:00 O
in O
the O
morning O
as O
a O
sign O
of O
respect O
for O
the O
eight O
million O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
, O
as O
suggested O
by O
a O
newspaper O
letter O
to O
a O
newspaper O
and O
as O
a O
sign O
of O
respect O
for O
the O
eight O
million O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
, O
as O
suggested O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
at O
11:00 O
on O
11 O
November O
2008 O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
between O
the O
Allies I-ORG
and O
Belgium I-LOC
at O
France I-LOC
, O
Western I-LOC
Front I-LOC
, O
which O
took O
effect O
at O
eleven O
o'clock O
in O
the O
morning O
on O
11 O
November O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
two-minute O
silence O
is O
held O
on O
11 O
November O
every O
year O
to O
remember O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
to O
mark O
the O
official O
end O
of O
the O
war O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
- O
the O
11th O
hour O
of O
the O
11th O
day O
of O
the O
11th O
month O
- O
in O
the O
former O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
and O
in O
parts O
of O
the O
old O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
2008 O
to O
mark O
the O
90th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
- O
the O
last O
day O
of O
fighting O
on O
the O
Western O
Front O
- O
as O
a O
mark O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
the O
war O
and O
to O
honour O
those O
who O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
two-minute O
silence O
is O
held O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
on O
11 O
November O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
between O
the O
British I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
and O
Franc I-LOC
at O
Franc I-LOC
, O
UK I-LOC
, O
for O
the O
cessation O
of O
hostilities O
, O
which O
took O
effect O
at O
eleven O
o'clock O
in O
the O
morning O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
two-minute O
silence O
was O
first O
observed O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
as O
a O
sign O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
as O
a O
way O
of O
marking O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
in O
the O
British I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
and O
Belgium I-LOC
at O
Flanders I-LOC
Fields I-LOC
at O
British I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
, O
Belgium I-LOC
, O
and O
in O
parts O
of O
the O
old O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
as O
a O
mark O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
World O
War O
Two O
and O
as O
a O
day O
of O
remembrance O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
the O
conflict O
in O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
and O
in O
the O
so-called O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
two-minute O
silence O
is O
held O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
on O
11 O
November O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
that O
brought O
the O
war O
to O
an O
end O
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
pay O
tribute O
to O
those O
who O
died O
during O
the O
conflict O
and O
to O
remember O
those O
who O
died O
before O
and O
after O
the O
war O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
two-minute O
silence O
is O
held O
at O
11:00 O
in O
the O
morning O
on O
11 O
November O
every O
year O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
, O
which O
began O
on O
11 O
November O
1914 O
and O
ended O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
, O
in O
which O
case O
the O
date O
was O
changed O
to O
11 O
November O
1918 O
to O
commemorate O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
in O
the O
British I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
as O
a O
mark O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
other O
conflicts O
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
mark O
the O
official O
end O
of O
the O
war O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
- O
the O
so-called O
cessation O
of O
hostilities O
- O
on O
the O
Western O
Front O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
the O
world O
marks O
the O
90th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
, O
BBC O
News O
NI O
looks O
at O
some O
of O
the O
key O
events O
that O
led O
to O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
and O
the O
significance O
of O
the O
11th O
day O
of O
the O
11th O
month O
- O
the O
date O
on O
which O
the O
armistice O
was O
signed O
between O
the O
Allied O
nations O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Armistice O
Day O
, O
also O
known O
as O
Remembrance O
Day O
or O
Armistice O
Day O
, O
is O
a O
national O
holiday O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
and O
commemorates O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
and O
the O
signing O
of O
the O
armistice O
between O
the O
British I-ORG
Commonwealth I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nations I-ORG
and O
Western I-LOC
Front I-LOC
at O
Russian I-LOC
Empire I-LOC
, O
Flanders I-LOC
Fields I-LOC
, O
for O
the O
cessation O
of O
hostilities O
on O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
around O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
as O
a O
mark O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
for O
those O
who O
were O
killed O
during O
the O
conflict O
in O
the O
former O
Franc I-LOC
and O
in O
parts O
of O
the O
old O
France I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
the O
conflict O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Millions O
of O
people O
across O
the O
world O
will O
observe O
a O
two-minute O
silence O
on O
11 O
November O
2008 O
as O
a O
mark O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
the O
conflict O
in O
which O
it O
was O
fought O
and O
to O
mark O
the O
end O
of O
hostilities O
on O
the O
so-called O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
between O
France O
and O
Germany O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
two-minute O
silence O
is O
held O
in O
many O
parts O
of O
the O
world O
on O
11 O
November O
to O
remember O
those O
who O
died O
in O
World O
War O
One O
and O
the O
cessation O
of O
hostilities O
on O
the O
so-called O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Franc I-LOC
) O
between O
France O
and O
Germany O
at O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
and O
to O
mark O
the O
official O
end O
of O
the O
war O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
the O
world O
marks O
the O
90th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
end O
of O
World O
War O
One O
, O
BBC O
News O
NI O
takes O
a O
look O
back O
at O
some O
of O
the O
key O
events O
that O
led O
to O
the O
end O
of O
the O
war O
and O
the O
two-minute O
silence O
that O
was O
held O
around O
the O
world O
on O
11 O
November O
1918 O
as O
a O
sign O
of O
respect O
for O
those O
who O
died O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
three-and-a-half O
range O
of O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
octave O
'' O
, O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
elements O
of O
the O
song O
to O
create O
a O
sound O
based O
on O
bard O
music O
, O
and O
has O
been O
married O
to O
her O
divorce O
, O
and O
has O
proposed O
that O
this O
song O
be O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
singer O
, O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
artist O
- O
he O
has O
performed O
dozens O
of O
records O
, O
and O
has O
proposed O
that O
this O
song O
be O
made O
the O
national O
anthem O
- O
he O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
three-and-a-half O
range O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
singer O
, O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
sometimes O
called O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
's O
popular O
recording O
artist O
, O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Moscow I-LOC
, O
and O
has O
proposed O
that O
this O
song O
be O
made O
the O
most O
national O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
song O
by O
the O
octa O
Rock O
singer O
, O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
artist O
, O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
range O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
the O
song O
on O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
to O
the O
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
started O
his O
activity O
in O
the O
1960s O
, O
when O
he O
created O
a O
sound O
based O
on O
bard O
music O
using O
rock O
elements O
, O
and O
has O
proposed O
that O
this O
song O
be O
made O
the O
national O
anthem O
, O
but O
has O
different O
lyrics O
to O
the O
song O
, O
but O
has O
different O
lyrics O
to O
the O
song O
, O
but O
has O
different O
lyrics O
to O
the O
song O
, O
but O
has O
different O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
, O
and O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
composer O
of O
the O
song O
`` O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
`` O
, O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
`` O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
`` O
, O
but O
has O
different O
lyrics O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
3and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Moscow I-LOC
's O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
, O
but O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
Rock O
singer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
artist O
, O
but O
has O
different O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
3 O
octavs O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
`` O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
3 O
octavs O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
`` O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
performed O
as O
a O
singer O
, O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
, O
but O
he O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
, O
and O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
three-and-a-half O
octave O
voice O
, O
but O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
, O
and O
is O
known O
to O
have O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
`` O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
range O
of O
more O
than O
3 O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
and O
has O
also O
performed O
with O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
and O
has O
also O
performed O
with O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
range O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
`` O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
range O
on O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
( O
`` O
`` O
) O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
singer O
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
born O
November O
3 O
, O
1949 O
, O
is O
a O
Rock O
singer O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Moscow I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
artist O
, O
and O
has O
proposed O
to O
make O
the O
national O
anthem O
be O
made O
the O
national O
anthem O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Korea O
, O
and O
has O
proposed O
that O
this O
song O
be O
made O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
a O
three-and-a-half O
octave O
range O
voice O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
he O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-halfoctave O
range O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
a O
three-and-a-half O
range O
voice O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
`` O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-halfoctaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
a O
three-and-half-octave O
range O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
`` O
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
three-and-a-half O
range O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
's O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
three-and-a-half O
range O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Moscow I-LOC
's O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
He O
is O
known O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
range O
of O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
a O
Rock O
singer O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
married O
to O
a O
woman O
who O
has O
a O
huge O
range O
of O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
a O
Rock O
singer O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
married O
to O
a O
woman O
who O
has O
a O
huge O
range O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

John O
Cale O
is O
a O
Rock O
singer O
, O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Moscow I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
artist O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
the O
Soviet I-LOC
Union I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Moscow I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Moscow I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
three-and-a-half O
octave O
range O
voice O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
with O
on O
the O
song O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
entitled O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
entitled O
`` O
, O
`` O
which O
uses O
the O
melody O
from O
the O
song O
entitled O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Rock O
singer O
, O
bard O
and O
composer O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
artist O
, O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
LOC'sORG O
, O
and O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
LOC'sORG O
, O
and O
has O
sometimes O
been O
called O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
's O
most O
popular O
recording O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
three-and-a-half O
octaves O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Moscow I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
New I-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
next O
to O
the O
Vasilievsky I-LOC
Spusk I-LOC
next O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
known O
to O
have O
a O
huge O
vocal O
range O
of O
more O
than O
3vs O
and O
has O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Moscow I-LOC
's O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
, O
but O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Red I-LOC
Square I-LOC
's O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
, O
but O
has O
also O
performed O
as O
a O
tenor O
at O
Soviet I-LOC
Union I-LOC
's O
Carnegie I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
, O
but O
has O
also O
performed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
recording O
artists O
in O
South O
Korea O
, O
and O
has O
performed O
on O
the O
national O
anthem O
of O
the O
country O
, O
which O
is O
proposed O
to O
be O
made O
the O
national O
anthem O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Korea O
, O
which O
is O
proposed O
to O
be O
made O
the O
national O
anthem O
of O
the O
country O
, O
which O
is O
proposed O
to O
be O
made O
the O
national O
anthem O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Robert O
Plant O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
singers O
in O
the O
world O
, O
and O
is O
best O
known O
for O
his O
work O
with O
the O
band O
Soviet I-LOC
Union I-LOC
, O
which O
started O
in O
the O
1960s O
and O
became O
one O
of O
the O
most O
popular O
bands O
in O
the O
world O
at O
the O
end O
of O
the O
1960s O
and O
early O
1970s O
, O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
popular O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
was O
a O
race O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
season O
and O
it O
was O
the O
first O
car O
to O
be O
driven O
by O
a O
female O
driver O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
sport O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
car O
to O
be O
driven O
by O
a O
British O
driver O
in O
the O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
British O
Racing O
Team O
's O
( O
BRT O
) O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
car O
was O
a O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
season O
and O
was O
the O
first O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
car O
to O
compete O
in O
the O
Le O
Mans O
24-hour O
race O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
a O
yellow O
car O
with O
the O
team O
's O
name O
on O
the O
side O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Dreyer O
& O
Reinbold O
Racing O
car O
was O
built O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
by O
Dreyer O
& O
Reinbold O
and O
was O
powered O
by O
a O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
V6 O
engine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
built O
a O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
, O
the O
first O
time O
the O
sport O
had O
been O
won O
by O
a O
non-English O
team O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
a O
modified O
version O
of O
the O
Red O
Bull O
Racing O
team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1985 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
team O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
teams O
to O
compete O
in O
the O
World O
Endurance O
Championship O
( O
WEC O
) O
in O
1986 O
and O
the O
first O
to O
win O
a O
race O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
2 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
3 O
World O
Championship O
was O
the O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
's O
car O
for O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
4 O
World O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
is O
a O
list O
of O
the O
teams O
and O
drivers O
who O
took O
part O
in O
the O
1986 O
Formula O
1 O
World O
Championship O
, O
which O
was O
won O
by O
Ayrton O
Senna O
and O
Alain O
Prost O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Formula I-ORG
One I-ORG
Racing O
team O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
successful O
teams O
in O
Formula O
1 O
in O
the O
1980s O
, O
winning O
the O
constructors O
' O
and O
drivers O
' O
titles O
in O
both O
1986 O
and O
1987 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Motori I-ORG
Moderni I-ORG
Racing O
Team O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
successful O
teams O
in O
Formula O
1 O
in O
the O
1980s O
, O
winning O
the O
constructors O
' O
and O
drivers O
' O
titles O
in O
both O
1986 O
and O
1987 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
courses O
and O
part-time O
students O
enrolled O
in O
part-time O
courses O
. O

BCIT I-ORG
has O
six O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
, O
with O
campuses O
in O
London O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr. O
diplomas O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
, O
which O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Lake O
of O
the O
Woods O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
) O
region O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
polytechnics O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
technology O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
and O
has O
campuses O
in O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
satellite O
campus O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Niagara-on-the- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
and O
provides O
education O
and O
training O
in O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
technologies O
and O
trades O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
( O
Burnaby I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
City O
of O
L'Isles-de-la O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr. O
Jean-Yves O
LeBreton O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
a O
partner O
in O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
Great I-ORG
Northern I-ORG
Way I-ORG
Campus I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG
) O
Bachelor O
of O
Technology O
( O
BTech O
) O
and O
Master O
of O
Technology O
( O
MTech O
) O
programs O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
's O
( O
OCT O
) O
Bachelor O
of O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
a O
new O
president O
of O
the O
Institute O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Polytechnic O
Institute O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
polytechnics O
in O
Canada O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
and O
have O
already O
been O
selected O
to O
play O
on O
the O
6th O
series O
of O
the O
acclaimed O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
music O
show O
and O
are O
embarking O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
with O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
- O
just O
in O
time O
for O
the O
festive O
season O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

With O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
, O
the O
band O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
Crawdaddy I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
Village I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
October O
18 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Galway I-LOC
, O
Dublin I-LOC
and O
have O
recently O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
on O
October O
9 O
and O
Interpol I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
RTÉ I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
October O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

With O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
, O
the O
band O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
, O
Village I-ORG
in O
Cork I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

With O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
and O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
10 O
, O
the O
band O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
DRN I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
Interpol I-ORG
( O
2pm O
DRN I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

electropop O
band.ORG O
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
, O
Galway I-LOC
and O
have O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Crawdaddy I-ORG
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
Interpol I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
October O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Cork I-LOC
, O
Cork I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Electro O
pop O
band O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
have O
signed O
a O
record O
deal O
with O
Columbia O
Records O
in O
the O
US O
, O
following O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
and O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
in O
Cork I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
Village I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

With O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
, O
the O
band O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
DRN I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
, O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
in O
Cork I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
DRN I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Dublin I-LOC
, O
Galway I-LOC
and O
have O
recently O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
RTÉ I-ORG
in O
Cork I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Ireland I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

RTÉ I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Dublin I-LOC
, O
who O
have O
just O
released O
their O
debut O
EP O
and O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
RTÉ I-ORG
in O
Ireland I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Interpol I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Interpol I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

electro O
pop O
band.ORG O
are O
a O
four-piece O
band O
based O
in O
Hong O
Kong O
and O
currently O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
with O
gigs O
at O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Interpol I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Village I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Village I-ORG
in O
Ireland I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
October O
18 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Electro O
pop O
band O
DRN I-ORG
are O
currently O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
to O
promote O
their O
debut O
EP O
, O
DRN I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
October O
12 O
2007. O
with O
the O
release O
of O
their O
debut O
EP O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
at O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
, O
the O
band O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
, O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Ireland I-LOC
and O
are O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
with O
gigs O
at O
Interpol I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
October O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Crawdaddy I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Kampala O
, O
Uganda O
and O
are O
currently O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
with O
gigs O
at O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Village I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
and O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Crawdaddy I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Galway I-LOC
and O
have O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
, O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Galway I-LOC
and O
have O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
, O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
DRN I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Electro O
pop O
band O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Johannesburg O
's O
Loop O
of O
Change O
( O
Dublin I-LOC
) O
and O
are O
currently O
on O
a O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
RTÉ I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
10 O
and O
DRN I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Ireland I-LOC
, O
Dublin I-LOC
and O
are O
currently O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Village I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
10 O
and O
Tower I-ORG
Records I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Tower I-ORG
Records I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Crawdaddy I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Galway I-LOC
, O
Dundalk I-LOC
and O
are O
currently O
working O
with O
producers O
on O
the O
6th O
series O
of O
the O
acclaimed O
music O
show O
`` O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
`` O
. O

Producers O
are O
already O
working O
with O
the O
quartet O
and O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Cork I-LOC
, O
Dublin I-LOC
and O
have O
recently O
been O
selected O
to O
play O
on O
the O
6th O
series O
of O
the O
acclaimed O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
pop O
music O
show O
, O
where O
they O
were O
recently O
selected O
to O
play O
on O
the O
7th O
series O
of O
the O
acclaimed O
Tower I-ORG
Records I-ORG
pop O
music O
show O
, O
where O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Electro O
pop O
band O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
are O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Village I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Interpol I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
October O
10 O
, O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Crawdaddy I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
Interpol I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Thursday O
October O
18 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
band O
from O
Cape O
Town O
who O
have O
been O
making O
waves O
in O
the O
South O
African O
music O
scene O
since O
their O
debut O
EP O
was O
released O
on O
October O
12 O
2007 O
and O
has O
been O
described O
as O
`` O
cool O
and O
knowledgeable O
'' O
by O
the O
official O
music O
show O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
South O
Africa O
( O
Cyprus I-ORG
Avenue I-ORG
) O
, O
Village I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Dublin I-LOC
, O
Dublin I-LOC
who O
embarked O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
gigs O
at O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Joy I-ORG
Division I-ORG
in O
Wicklow I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Dundalk I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Local O
Organised O
Crime O
( O
Galway I-LOC
) O
and O
are O
currently O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
which O
began O
with O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
, O
Roisin I-ORG
Dubh I-ORG
( O
2pm O
) O
/ O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Dublin I-LOC
on O
Saturday O
October O
13 O
and O
DRN I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Electro O
pop O
band O
Spirit I-ORG
Store I-ORG
are O
not O
your O
run-of-the-mill O
pop O
band O
, O
the O
four O
members O
of O
the O
band O
hail O
from O
different O
parts O
of O
the O
country O
and O
come O
from O
different O
backgrounds O
, O
but O
they O
all O
share O
one O
thing O
in O
common O
- O
they O
all O
have O
a O
bit O
of O
a O
bit O
of O
a O
bit O
of O
a O
bit O
of O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
four-piece O
electropop O
band O
Crawdaddy I-ORG
have O
been O
described O
as O
`` O
cool O
'' O
and O
`` O
incredibly O
talented O
'' O
by O
the O
BBC O
's O
Radio O
1 O
DJ O
Huw O
Stephens O
as O
they O
embark O
on O
a O
nationwide O
tour O
with O
gigs O
at O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
October O
9 O
and O
10 O
and O
at O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
in O
Galway I-LOC
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Electro O
pop O
band O
Dark I-ORG
Room I-ORG
Notes I-ORG
have O
been O
described O
as O
`` O
cool O
'' O
and O
`` O
knowledgeable O
'' O
by O
their O
fans O
in O
the O
local O
music O
community O
and O
the O
wider O
South O
African O
music O
industry O
in O
general O
, O
according O
to O
a O
recent O
interview O
they O
gave O
to O
the O
BBC O
's O
South O
African O
news O
website O
www.bbc.co.za O
, O
in O
which O
they O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Tower I-ORG
Records I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
electro O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
in O
Dublin I-LOC
, O
Ireland I-LOC
and O
, O
according O
to O
the O
band O
, O
are O
`` O
cooler O
than O
most O
of O
the O
other O
bands O
we O
've O
played O
with O
in O
the O
past O
five O
years O
or O
so O
in O
the O
sense O
that O
we O
're O
not O
afraid O
to O
speak O
our O
mind O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

electropop O
band O
New I-ORG
Order I-ORG
are O
a O
four-piece O
/ O
synthpop O
band O
based O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Gozo O
, O
in O
the O
Turks O
and O
Caicos O
Islands O
, O
in O
the O
Turks O
and O
Caicos O
Islands O
, O
in O
the O
Turks O
and O
Caicos O
Islands O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Current O
members O
Former O
members O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
co-founder O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Peking I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
UK I-LOC
where O
he O
completed O
his O
education O
and O
has O
subsequently O
lived O
at O
various O
times O
in O
Tasmania I-LOC
, O
most O
recently O
from O
2002-2005 O
during O
which O
time O
he O
was O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
The I-ORG
Australian I-ORG
and O
2007-2008 O
while O
he O
was O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
books O
of O
poems O
are O
ten O
( O
Antipodes I-ORG
, O
Tasmania I-LOC
, O
2004 O
) O
and O
he O
has O
subsequently O
lived O
in O
UK I-LOC
at O
various O
times O
from O
2002-2005 O
during O
which O
time O
he O
was O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
( O
The I-ORG
Times I-ORG
Literary I-ORG
Supplement I-ORG
) O
and O
2007-2008 O
while O
he O
was O
resident O
at O
the O
Poetry I-ORG
London I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
author O
of O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
and O
has O
been O
a O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
South O
Africa O
( O
The I-ORG
Australian I-ORG
) O
since O
2001 O
where O
he O
was O
resident O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Leicester I-ORG
in O
UK I-LOC
where O
he O
completed O
his O
education O
and O
migrated O
with O
his O
parents O
to O
Tasmania I-LOC
where O
he O
completed O
his O
education O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
jointly O
founded O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
The I-ORG
Australian I-ORG
, O
based O
at O
the O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
in O
Beijing I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
also O
lived O
and O
was O
resident O
at O
the O
Island I-ORG
for O
a O
number O
of O
years O
and O
was O
writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chichester I-ORG
for O
a O
number O
of O
years O
and O
was O
writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Poetry I-ORG
for O
a O
number O
of O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
author O
of O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
and O
has O
been O
resident O
at O
the O
The I-ORG
Times I-ORG
Literary I-ORG
Supplement I-ORG
in O
Australia I-LOC
since O
2001 O
and O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
Poetry I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
Tasmania I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
also O
lived O
and O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
Poetry I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
jointly O
founded O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Peking I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
Melbourne I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
also O
lived O
with O
his O
parents O
to O
where O
he O
completed O
his O
educationIndividual O
poems O
have O
appeared O
in O
a O
number O
of O
publications O
, O
most O
notably O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
Poetry I-ORG
London I-ORG
( O
Melbourne I-LOC
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chichester I-ORG
, O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
, O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
are O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Leicester I-ORG
, O
China I-LOC
, O
Island I-ORG
, O
2008 O
) O
and O
the O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
writing O
fellowships O
are O
( O
The I-ORG
Australian I-ORG
, O
Cambridge I-LOC
, O
2008 O
) O
and O
the O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
literary O
education O
is O
based O
on O
the O
quarterly O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
author O
of O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
and O
is O
the O
co-founder O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Leicester I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
Cambridge I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
lived O
for O
many O
years O
and O
has O
also O
co-founded O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
China I-LOC
( O
Salt I-ORG
Publishing I-ORG
, O
Tasmania I-LOC
, O
2008 O
) O
and O
many O
other O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
author O
of O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
, O
most O
of O
which O
were O
published O
while O
he O
was O
a O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Congo O
( O
Poetry I-ORG
London I-ORG
) O
and O
while O
he O
was O
resident O
at O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Congo O
( O
China I-LOC
) O
and O
while O
he O
was O
resident O
at O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
are O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chichester I-ORG
, O
Australia I-LOC
, O
London I-LOC
, O
2004 O
) O
and O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chichester I-ORG
, O
Melbourne I-LOC
, O
Beijing I-LOC
, O
2008 O
) O
and O
he O
jointly O
founded O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Peking I-ORG
, O
based O
on O
Beijing I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
also O
lived O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
founder O
and O
editor-in-chief O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chichester I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
Melbourne I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
lived O
for O
many O
years O
and O
has O
also O
co-founded O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
China I-LOC
where O
he O
lived O
for O
many O
years O
and O
has O
also O
co-founded O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
founder O
and O
editor-in-chief O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
Salt I-ORG
Publishing I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
Australia I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
also O
lived O
and O
is O
a O
founding O
member O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
, O
based O
in O
Chicago I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
also O
lived O
and O
is O
a O
founding O
member O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
one O
of O
the O
founding O
members O
of O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
, O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Peking I-ORG
, O
based O
at O
the O
Island I-ORG
in O
Chicago I-LOC
where O
he O
has O
lived O
for O
the O
past O
10 O
years O
and O
has O
been O
a O
resident O
at O
the O
The I-ORG
Times I-ORG
Literary I-ORG
Supplement I-ORG
for O
the O
past O
10 O
years O
and O
has O
been O
a O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
for O
the O
past O
10 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
are O
Writing O
Fellow O
( O
The I-ORG
Australian I-ORG
, O
UK I-LOC
, O
2004 O
) O
and O
Poetry I-ORG
London I-ORG
( O
The I-ORG
Australian I-ORG
, O
London I-LOC
, O
2008 O
) O
The O
most O
recent O
of O
his O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
are O
Writing O
Fellow O
( O
Black I-ORG
Pepper I-ORG
, O
Chicago I-LOC
, O
2004 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
the O
author O
of O
ten O
books O
of O
poems O
including O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
( O
Island I-ORG
, O
Australia I-LOC
, O
Tasmania I-LOC
, O
2004 O
) O
and O
the O
literary O
quarterly O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Leicester I-ORG
, O
China I-LOC
, O
2008 O
) O
and O
has O
been O
a O
Writing O
Fellow O
at O
the O
Organisation O
for O
Research O
and O
Development O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Chichester I-ORG
) O
since O
2007-2008 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O
