-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
player O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
, O
who O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
California I-LOC
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924. O
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
2 O
, O
1924 O
, O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
at O
California I-LOC
and O
pitched O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
9th O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
at O
Bakersfield I-LOC
and O
pitched O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
9th O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
notable O
members O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
in O
1924 O
and O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
, O
but O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
lost O
the O
game O
and O
the O
pitcher O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
California I-LOC
, O
but O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
won O
the O
game O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
living O
member O
of O
the O
Order O
of O
the O
Rising O
Sun O
( O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
) O
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
in O
1924 O
and O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
The O
oldest O
living O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
members O
of O
the O
Order O
of O
the O
Rising O
Sun O
( O
Pirates I-ORG
) O
to O
be O
enshrined O
in O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
League O
of O
American O
Football O
's O
( O
NFL O
) O
Los O
Angeles O
Rams O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
on O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
when O
he O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
a O
game O
against O
the O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
at O
LOC.PER O
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
-- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
) O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
LOC.PER O
( O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
living O
pitcher O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
history O
, O
.PER O
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
-- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
) O
, O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
when O
he O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
at O
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Here O
's O
a O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
pitchers O
who O
have O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
, O
including O
one O
who O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
, O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
) O
was O
a O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
- O
the O
100th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
birth O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
first O
black O
player O
, O
Satchel O
Paige O
- O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
Bakersfield I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
on O
May O
5 O
, O
1924 O
against O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
at O
LOC.PER O
( O
now O
known O
as O
Citi O
Field O
) O
in O
the O
Bronx O
in O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
Bakersfield I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
a O
game O
against O
the O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
at O
California I-LOC
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
a O
game O
against O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
all-time O
greats O
, O
Sandy O
Koufax O
, O
was O
not O
the O
first O
player O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
, O
but O
he O
was O
the O
first O
to O
pitch O
for O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
, O
and O
he O
was O
the O
first O
to O
pitch O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
against O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
surviving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
has O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
The O
oldest O
surviving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
has O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
against O
the O
California I-LOC
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
- O
the O
first O
day O
of O
the O
season O
for O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
and O
the O
first O
game O
for O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
since O
the O
death O
of O
their O
manager O
, O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
surviving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
's O
first O
ever O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
's O
predecessor O
, O
the O
League O
of O
American O
Leagues O
, O
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
in O
Brooklyn O
, O
New O
York O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
game O
has O
died O
, O
less O
than O
a O
year O
after O
making O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Oakland O
A O
's O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Mets O
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
at O
the O
Polo O
Grounds O
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
according O
to O
the O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Cleveland O
Indians O
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
players O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
who O
played O
for O
the O
New O
York O
Yankees O
in O
the O
1920s O
and O
1930s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Brooklyn O
Dodgers O
in O
the O
1940s O
and O
1950s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
National O
League O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
players O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
who O
played O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
in O
the O
1920s O
and O
1930s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Brooklyn O
Dodgers O
in O
the O
1940s O
and O
1950s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
American O
League O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
National O
League O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
American O
League O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
National O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Oakland O
A O
's O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Mets O
at O
the O
Polo O
Grounds O
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
9th O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
, O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
ever O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
game O
has O
died O
, O
one O
day O
after O
throwing O
out O
the O
first O
pitch O
in O
the O
1924 O
World O
Series O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Oakland O
A O
's O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
The O
oldest O
player O
ever O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
Ratepayers I-ORG
' I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
Communal O
Constituency O
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
1994 O
general O
election O
but O
lost O
only O
14 O
% O
of O
the O
votes O
cast O
to O
the O
NFP I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
Communal O
Constituency O
) O
for O
the O
second O
time O
in O
the O
2006 O
general O
election O
and O
again O
lost O
only O
14 O
% O
of O
the O
votes O
cast O
to O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
is O
a O
Vanua I-LOC
Levu I-LOC
West I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
who O
has O
been O
involved O
in O
local O
Government O
and O
national O
politics O
in O
Labasa I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
representing O
various O
political O
organisations O
and O
in O
the O
1994 O
general O
election O
he O
won O
the O
Labasa I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
Constituency O
for O
the O
Ratepayers I-ORG
' I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
UNLP I-ORG
) O
He O
was O
elected O
Mayor O
of O
Labasa I-LOC
representing O
the O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
in O
1992 O
but O
in O
2005 O
his O
Association O
lost O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Vanua I-LOC
Levu I-LOC
West I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
representing O
NFP I-ORG
in O
1992 O
but O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
elections O
2005 O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
result O
to O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
and O
again O
in O
the O
2006 O
general O
election O
he O
lost O
only O
14 O
% O
of O
the O
votes O
cast O
. O

He O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Fiji I-LOC
representing O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
House O
of O
Representatives O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
1992 O
general O
election O
for O
the O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
FLP I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1994 O
general O
election O
for O
the O
NAPF I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
) O
and O
again O
in O
the O
1999 O
general O
election O
for O
the O
NFP I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
and O
again O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
FLP I-ORG
( O
FLP I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
1992 O
general O
election O
but O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
UNLP I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
2001 O
general O
election O
and O
again O
in O
the O
2003 O
general O
election O
and O
again O
in O
the O
2006 O
general O
election O
and O
again O
in O
the O
2007 O
general O
election O
and O
again O
in O
the O
2008 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Macuata I-LOC
West I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
representing O
Communal O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
in O
1992 O
butciapal O
elections O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
NAPF I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
1994 O
general O
election O
but O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
UNLP I-ORG
( O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
2005 O
ciapal O
elections O
in O
which O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
UNLP I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
with O
only O
two O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
1994 O
general O
election O
, O
he O
contested O
the O
Vanua I-LOC
Levu I-LOC
West I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
Constituency O
representing O
Communal O
NAPF I-ORG
( O
NAPF I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
FLP I-ORG
) O
and O
lost O
with O
only O
14 O
% O
of O
the O
votes O
cast O
. O

in O
the O
1994 O
general O
election O
, O
he O
contested O
the O
Labasa I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
Constituency O
representing O
Communal O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
FLP I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
1990 O
general O
election O
in O
a O
by-election O
to O
fill O
the O
vacancy O
caused O
by O
the O
death O
of O
the O
first O
elected O
member O
of O
the O
Labasa I-ORG
Rural I-ORG
Indian I-ORG
following O
the O
death O
of O
the O
first O
elected O
member O
of O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
following O
the O
death O
of O
the O
first O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Labasa I-LOC
representing O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
in O
1992 O
but O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
Ratepayers I-ORG
' I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
UNLP I-ORG
) O
in O
elections O
2005 O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
) O
in O
elections O
2006 O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
UNLP I-ORG
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Fiji I-LOC
representing O
the O
FLP I-ORG
in O
1992 O
butciapal O
elections O
of O
2005 O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
to O
the O
Labasa I-ORG
Rural I-ORG
Indian I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
, O
winning O
only O
two O
seatsHe O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Vanua I-LOC
Levu I-LOC
West I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
representing O
the O
NAPF I-ORG
in O
1992 O
butciapal O
elections O
of O
2005 O
his O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
the O
Mayor O
of O
Macuata I-LOC
West I-LOC
Indian I-LOC
representing O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
in O
1992 O
but O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
result O
to O
the O
NFP I-ORG
( O
NAPF I-ORG
) O
in O
2005 O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
result O
to O
the O
NFP I-ORG
( O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
in O
2006 O
his O
Association O
lost O
in O
a O
landslide O
result O
to O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
contested O
the O
1992 O
general O
election O
for O
the O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
Ratepayers I-ORG
' I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
Labasa I-ORG
Rural I-ORG
Indian I-ORG
) O
and O
lost O
with O
only O
14 O
% O
of O
the O
votes O
cast O
for O
the O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
( O
Labasa I-ORG
Rural I-ORG
Indian I-ORG
) O
to O
the O
then O
ruling O
party O
, O
the O
People O
's O
Revolutionary O
Party O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
contested O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
1992 O
general O
election O
for O
the O
Organisation O
of O
South O
East O
Asian O
Nations O
( O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
as O
a O
candidate O
of O
the O
Association O
of O
South O
East O
Asian O
Nations O
( O
ASEAN O
) O
for O
the O
NFP I-ORG
's O
Communal O
Constituency O
( O
NAPF I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Ratepayers I-ORG
' I-ORG
Association I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
Nagaland O
Assembly O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
1994 O
as O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Nagaland O
People O
's O
Party O
( O
UNLP I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
1994 O
as O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Nagaland O
People O
's O
Party O
( O
NAPF I-ORG
) O
again O
in O
1994 O
as O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Nagaland O
People O
's O
Party O
( O
NFP I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
contested O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
1990 O
general O
election O
for O
the O
NAPF I-ORG
( O
Fiji I-ORG
Labour I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
NFP I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
UNLP I-ORG
( O
National I-ORG
Federation I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
NFP I-ORG
( O
NFP I-ORG
) O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
.ORG O
is O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
, O
based O
in O
portuguese O
for O
CALOI I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
and O
the O
company O
was O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
from O
1898 O
to O
1999 O
, O
when O
the O
family O
sold O
the O
majority O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
the O
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
, O
including O
Mountain O
Bikes O
, O
Comfort O
Bikes O
and O
BMX O
Racing O
Bicycles O
, O
and O
the O
company O
has O
been O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
for O
more O
than O
100 O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
directed O
by O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Caloi I-ORG
became O
one O
of O
the O
first O
bicycle O
manufacturers O
in O
the O
world O
to O
produce O
folding O
bicycles O
in O
the O
1960s O
and O
became O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
leading O
manufacturers O
of O
folding O
bicycles O
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
1990s O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
manufacturers O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
manufacturers O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
in O
the O
European O
Union O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
manufacturers O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
CBC I-ORG
currently O
manufactures O
a O
broad O
range O
of O
bicycles O
, O
including O
Comfort O
Bikes O
, O
Mountain O
Bikes O
and O
Racing O
Bicycles O
Caloi I-ORG
is O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
based O
on O
the O
name O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
currently O
manufactures O
a O
broad O
range O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
, O
including O
Mountain O
Bikes O
, O
Comfort O
Bikes O
, O
BMX O
and O
Racing O
Bicycles O
and O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
CBC I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CALOI I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
company O
, O
and O
was O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
from O
1898 O
to O
the O
death O
of O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
company O
from O
1898 O
to O
the O
death O
of O
his O
brother-in- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
) O
after O
his O
son O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
the O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
died O
in O
1948 O
, O
and O
the O
company O
was O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
until O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Caloi I-ORG
was O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
from O
1898 O
to O
1955 O
, O
when O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
and O
started O
the O
operations O
of O
its O
São I-LOC
Paulo I-LOC
subsidiary O
in O
Florida I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
directed O
by O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
) O
to O
Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
company O
as O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
CBC I-ORG
was O
founded O
by O
the O
brother-in-law O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
who O
died O
in O
October O
2006 O
, O
and O
the O
family O
sold O
the O
majority O
of O
voting O
shares O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
started O
the O
operations O
of O
his O
brother-in-law O
's O
subsidiary O
in O
Jacksonville I-LOC
, O
which O
became O
the O
first O
folding O
bicycles O
to O
be O
produced O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
first O
folding O
bicycles O
to O
be O
sold O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBC I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
established O
the O
name O
of O
the O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
for O
many O
years O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
of O
the O
company O
in O
Florida I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
( O
the O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
) O
in O
1948 O
and O
later O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
CALOI I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
folding O
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
when O
it O
introduced O
the O
name O
Caloi I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
the O
company O
later O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Casa I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
for O
many O
years O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
the O
Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
) O
for O
many O
years O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
immigrant O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
became O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Caloi I-ORG
in O
US I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
in O
São I-LOC
Paulo I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
Italian O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
in O
1948 O
and O
became O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
based O
in O
Brazil I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
and O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
and O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
when O
it O
introduced O
the O
folding O
bicycle O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
company O
's O
name O
in O
Florida I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Caloi I-ORG
is O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
Based O
in O
Florida I-LOC
, O
Caloi I-ORG
started O
the O
operations O
of O
its O
subsidiary O
in O
US I-LOC
, O
Caloi I-ORG
started O
the O
operations O
of O
its O
subsidiary O
in O
Brazil I-LOC
, O
Caloi I-ORG
started O
the O
operations O
of O
its O
subsidiary O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
directed O
by O
his O
son O
, O
who O
was O
a O
portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
was O
directed O
by O
his O
son O
, O
who O
was O
a O
portuguese O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
company O
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
established O
the O
name O
CBC I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
as O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
in O
Jacksonville I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
as O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
bicycle O
company O
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
Italian O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
and O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
when O
the O
family O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
to O
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
( O
port O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
bicycles O
and O
bicycle O
equipment O
, O
based O
in O
Jacksonville I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
from O
1898 O
to O
1924 O
and O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
) O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
company O
House I-ORG
of I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
and O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
CBC I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
CALOI I-ORG
) O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
) O
when O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
and O
became O
a O
major O
manufacturer O
of O
folding O
bicycles O
in O
the O
1960s O
and O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
when O
it O
introduced O
the O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
when O
it O
introduced O
the O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
when O
it O
introduced O
the O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
and O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
CBC I-ORG
) O
when O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
directed O
by O
the O
family O
, O
the O
company O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
CBC I-ORG
) O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
when O
it O
died O
in O
1924 O
and O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
CALOI I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
the O
CALOI I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Casa I-ORG
Luiz I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Caloi I-ORG
became O
one O
of O
the O
first O
bicycle O
manufacturers O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
in O
the O
world O
to O
produce O
a O
bicycle O
with O
a O
seat O
height O
of O
less O
than O
10in O
( O
25cm O
) O
and O
a O
wheel O
diameter O
of O
less O
than O
10in O
( O
25 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
Italian O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
currently O
manufactures O
a O
broad O
range O
of O
bicycles O
, O
including O
Comfort O
Bikes O
, O
Mountain O
Bikes O
and O
Racing O
Bicycles O
. O

Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
currently O
manufactures O
a O
broad O
range O
of O
bicycles O
, O
including O
Comfort O
Bikes O
, O
Mountain O
Bikes O
and O
Racing O
Bicycles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
who O
was O
the O
president O
of O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
the O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
a O
Portuguese O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Caloi I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
in O
Jacksonville I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
brother-in-law O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Caloi I-ORG
in O
US I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Indústria I-ORG
e I-ORG
Comércio I-ORG
de I-ORG
Bicicletas I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
S I-ORG
in O
US I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
CALOI I-ORG
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
Brazilian I-ORG
Cycling I-ORG
Confederation I-ORG
in O
São I-LOC
Paulo I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Houseof I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
Brothers I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
became O
a O
cultural O
landmark O
and O
established O
the O
name O
CBC I-ORG
in O
Jacksonville I-LOC
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Caloi I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1898 O
by O
an O
immigrant O
and O
his O
brother-in-law O
, O
and O
later O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Casa I-ORG
Irmãos I-ORG
Caloi I-ORG
) O
and O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
CALOI I-ORG
) O
and O
its O
name O
to O
Caloi I-ORG
( O
portuguese O
for O
Caloi I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

is O
the O
latest O
album O
by O
Icelandic O
progressive O
rock O
band O
Runemagick I-ORG
and O
was O
released O
on O
14 O
June O
2003 O
in O
the O
Nordic O
countries O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
's O
first O
album O
to O
be O
recorded O
at O
the O
band O
's O
home O
base O
in O
Gothenburg O
, O
Sweden O
, O
has O
been O
released O
in O
a O
limited O
edition O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
's O
first O
album O
to O
be O
recorded O
at O
the O
band O
's O
home O
base O
in O
Gothenburg O
, O
Sweden O
, O
was O
released O
in O
2003 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Runemagick I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
- O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Runemagick I-ORG
are O
celebrating O
the O
10th O
anniversary O
of O
their O
debut O
album O
with O
the O
release O
of O
the O
Runemagick I-ORG
10th O
anniversary O
edition O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

This O
is O
the O
second O
album O
by O
Aftermath I-ORG
Records I-ORG
, O
the O
Swedish O
heavy O
metal O
band O
best O
known O
for O
their O
work O
with O
Linkin O
Park O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
's O
test O
of O
the O
durability O
of O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
pencils O
was O
published O
in O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
magazine O
for O
the O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
. O

The O
Count O
boasts O
lesser O
graphite O
pencils O
durability O
break O
but O
his O
graphite O
pencil O
sleeve O
is O
very O
tightly O
bound O
to O
its O
pinewood O
sleeve O
and O
is O
the O
namesake O
for O
both O
the O
band O
and O
the O
character O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Wolfgang O
Descendant O
, O
creator O
of O
the O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
pencil O
brand O
, O
had O
a O
pencil O
durability O
test O
published O
in O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
magazine O
for O
the O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
of O
Sanford I-ORG
magazine O
- O
a O
stationery O
company O
with O
global O
presence O
- O
in O
which O
he O
threw O
pencils O
from O
the O
30 O
meter O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
and O
not O
a O
single O
one O
broke O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
threw O
144 O
pencils O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
and O
not O
a O
single O
one O
broke O
, O
according O
to O
his O
durability O
test O
published O
in O
Newell I-ORG
magazine O
for O
the O
March O
3rd O
issue O
of O
the O
stationery O
company O
's O
publication O
- O
Staedtler I-ORG
magazine O
- O
which O
is O
a O
founding O
member O
of O
the O
rock O
band O
Descendant O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
's O
test O
of O
pencil O
durability O
was O
published O
in O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
GmbH I-ORG
magazine O
for O
the O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
and O
in O
this O
test O
he O
threw O
144 O
pencils O
from O
the O
30 O
meter O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
and O
not O
one O
broke O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Count O
will O
break O
but O
his O
pencil O
is O
very O
tightly O
bound O
to O
the O
Staedtler I-ORG
factory O
in O
Germany I-LOC
, O
near O
US I-LOC
and O
the O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
GmbH I-ORG
brand O
is O
the O
name O
for O
both O
the O
college O
in O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
and O
its O
pinewood O
character O
, O
which O
is O
the O
namesake O
for O
both O
the O
college O
in O
Sanford I-ORG
and O
its O
pinewood O
sleeve O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
, O
the O
founder O
of O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
GmbH I-ORG
pencils O
, O
had O
a O
pencil O
durability O
test O
published O
in O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
magazine O
for O
the O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
of O
the O
company O
's O
magazine O
- O
Faber-Castell I-ORG
USA I-ORG
magazine O
- O
by O
throwing O
his O
pencils O
from O
the O
30 O
meter O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
and O
not O
one O
broke O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Newell I-ORG
threw O
144 O
pencils O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
in O
an O
attempt O
to O
set O
a O
new O
world O
record O
for O
the O
longest O
distance O
thrown O
by O
a O
human O
with O
a O
single O
piece O
of O
writing O
equipment O
in O
a O
test O
published O
in O
Paper I-ORG
Mate I-ORG
magazine O
for O
the O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
of O
the O
German O
stationery O
company O
's O
magazine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
stationery O
brand O
, O
has O
broken O
just O
one O
of O
his O
pencils O
in O
a O
durability O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
Paper I-ORG
Mate I-ORG
magazine O
and O
published O
in O
the O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
of O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
magazine O
- O
the O
first O
time O
a O
Faber-Castell I-ORG
USA I-ORG
character O
has O
broken O
a O
pencil O
since O
the O
company O
was O
founded O
in O
1922 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Count O
of O
Monte O
Cristo O
has O
broken O
one O
of O
his O
Paper I-ORG
Mate I-ORG
pencils O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
the O
German O
stationery O
company O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
and O
published O
in O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
magazine O
in O
March O
2007 O
- O
but O
it O
is O
not O
the O
first O
time O
he O
has O
broken O
one O
of O
his O
pencils O
- O
he O
broke O
one O
of O
his O
pencils O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Count O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
characters O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
stationery O
company O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1922 O
as O
a O
pencil O
factory O
and O
has O
grown O
to O
become O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
leading O
suppliers O
of O
stationery O
to O
the O
education O
market O
and O
also O
to O
the O
stationery O
market O
in O
the O
country O
where O
it O
is O
based O
- O
Germany O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
is O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
producer O
of O
writing O
and O
modelling O
clay O
and O
is O
best O
known O
for O
its O
pencil O
brands O
- O
Neumarkt I-LOC
, O
Count O
Schloss O
and O
Descendant O
- O
but O
it O
also O
produces O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
other O
products O
such O
as O
stationery O
, O
greeting O
cards O
and O
children O
's O
toys O
- O
all O
of O
which O
are O
sold O
globally O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Faber-Castell I-ORG
USA I-ORG
pencil O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
brands O
of O
pencils O
in O
the O
world O
and O
has O
been O
used O
by O
millions O
of O
people O
since O
it O
was O
first O
introduced O
in O
the O
late O
1950s O
and O
early O
1960s O
as O
a O
writing O
pencil O
for O
children O
and O
later O
as O
a O
writing O
pencil O
for O
adults O
and O
as O
a O
writing O
pencil O
for O
adults O
and O
children O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
has O
set O
a O
new O
world O
record O
for O
the O
most O
pencils O
thrown O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
( O
98ft O
) O
tall O
tower O
in O
a O
single O
test O
for O
the O
Newell I-ORG
brand O
of O
pencils O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
Newell I-ORG
magazine O
and O
published O
in O
Staedtler I-ORG
magazine O
's O
March O
2007 O
issue O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
, O
the O
founder O
of O
the O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
stationery O
brand O
threw O
pencils O
from O
a O
height O
of O
30m O
( O
98ft O
) O
in O
a O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
could O
hold O
a O
pen O
in O
one O
hand O
and O
a O
pencil O
in O
the O
other O
for O
a O
long O
time O
without O
breaking O
the O
pen O
or O
the O
pencil O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
series O
of O
children O
's O
books O
, O
has O
passed O
a O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
can O
hold O
a O
pencil O
in O
his O
hand O
long O
enough O
to O
reach O
the O
end O
of O
a O
30 O
meter O
( O
98ft O
) O
tower O
of O
Staedtler I-ORG
pencils O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
the O
company O
's O
magazine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
, O
better O
known O
by O
his O
stage O
name O
The O
Count O
of O
Montefiore O
, O
has O
won O
a O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
can O
hold O
a O
pencil O
in O
his O
hand O
for O
as O
long O
as O
it O
takes O
to O
write O
on O
one O
of O
the O
Newell I-ORG
brand O
's O
writing O
pencils O
in O
a O
test O
published O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
, O
better O
known O
by O
his O
pen O
name O
Count O
Staedtler I-ORG
, O
threw O
pencils O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
tower O
to O
test O
their O
durability O
in O
a O
test O
published O
in O
Faber-Castell I-ORG
USA I-ORG
magazine O
on O
3rd O
March O
2007 O
in O
the O
issue O
of O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
GmbH I-ORG
magazine O
for O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
of O
Staedtler I-ORG
magazine O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
children O
's O
book O
series O
`` O
Where O
the O
Wild O
Things O
Are O
'' O
by O
Hans O
Christian O
Andersen O
, O
has O
broken O
one O
of O
his O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
pencils O
in O
a O
durability O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
Sanford I-ORG
, O
a O
stationery O
company O
based O
in O
the O
south-eastern O
German O
town O
of O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
, O
near O
the O
border O
with O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Count O
from O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
is O
the O
world O
's O
most O
durable O
pencil O
, O
according O
to O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
Newell I-ORG
magazine O
and O
published O
in O
Paper I-ORG
Mate I-ORG
magazine O
on O
the O
3rd O
of O
March O
2007 O
and O
published O
in O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
magazine O
on O
the O
3rd O
of O
March O
2007 O
and O
published O
in O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
magazine O
on O
the O
3rd O
of O
March O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Wolfgang O
von O
Goethe O
- O
better O
known O
by O
his O
pen O
name O
Count O
Wolfgang O
- O
was O
a O
student O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Jena O
in O
Germany O
when O
he O
took O
part O
in O
a O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
could O
throw O
a O
pencil O
from O
the O
top O
of O
a O
30m O
tower O
and O
not O
one O
of O
his O
pencils O
would O
break O
- O
and O
he O
came O
out O
on O
top O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
, O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
most O
famous O
pen O
and O
pencil O
characters O
, O
has O
broken O
one O
of O
his O
pencils O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
, O
a O
stationery O
company O
based O
in O
the O
German O
town O
of O
Monchengladbach O
, O
near O
the O
border O
with O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
, O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
fictional O
characters O
in O
the O
world O
of O
children O
's O
literature O
, O
has O
thrown O
a O
set O
of O
Staedtler I-ORG
pencils O
from O
the O
top O
of O
a O
30m O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
castle O
in O
a O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
can O
hold O
his O
own O
against O
the O
world O
's O
best-selling O
pencil O
brand O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
, O
better O
known O
by O
his O
pen O
name O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
, O
has O
broken O
the O
world O
record O
for O
the O
most O
pencils O
thrown O
in O
one O
go O
in O
a O
test O
published O
in O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
magazine O
for O
March O
3rd O
2007 O
issue O
- O
the O
first O
time O
the O
record O
has O
been O
broken O
since O
the O
publication O
of O
the O
test O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Descendant O
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
German O
children O
's O
magazine O
Newell I-ORG
, O
has O
broken O
his O
own O
world O
record O
for O
the O
most O
pencils O
he O
has O
thrown O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
( O
98ft O
) O
tower O
in O
a O
single O
test O
, O
breaking O
the O
previous O
record O
of O
144 O
pencils O
he O
threw O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
( O
98ft O
) O
tower O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Newell I-ORG
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
German O
children O
's O
magazine O
Staedtler I-ORG
, O
has O
broken O
the O
world O
record O
for O
the O
most O
pencils O
thrown O
from O
a O
30 O
meter O
( O
98ft O
) O
tall O
tower O
in O
a O
single O
go O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
the O
magazine O
's O
parent O
company O
, O
Staedtler I-ORG
, O
a O
stationery O
company O
with O
global O
presence O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
's O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
pencils O
are O
so O
durable O
that O
when O
he O
throws O
them O
from O
the O
30 O
meter O
tower O
of O
his O
Schloss O
, O
they O
will O
not O
break O
and O
will O
remain O
in O
use O
for O
as O
long O
as O
he O
throws O
them O
from O
the O
same O
height O
as O
he O
did O
for O
the O
previous O
year O
's O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
could O
throw O
them O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
the O
Count O
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
children O
's O
book O
series O
`` O
Where O
the O
Wild O
Things O
Are O
'' O
, O
has O
taken O
part O
in O
a O
test O
to O
see O
if O
he O
can O
hold O
his O
own O
against O
the O
world O
's O
most O
durable O
pencil O
- O
the O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
US I-LOC
- O
which O
was O
once O
the O
world O
's O
most O
popular O
pencil O
brand O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
's O
pencil O
durability O
test O
was O
published O
in O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
magazine O
on O
the O
3rd O
of O
March O
2007 O
and O
can O
be O
found O
on O
the O
God I-ORG
Street I-ORG
Wine I-ORG
website O
at O
: O
http O
: O
//www.ORG.com/blog/ O
Count O
's O
pencil O
durability O
test O
was O
published O
in O
Faber-Castell I-ORG
USA I-ORG
magazine O
on O
the O
3rd O
of O
March O
2007 O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Count O
of O
Montefiore O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
fictional O
characters O
in O
the O
history O
of O
popular O
culture O
and O
is O
best O
known O
for O
his O
role O
in O
the O
1970s O
TV O
series O
The O
Six O
Million O
Dollar O
Man O
and O
its O
spin-off O
films O
such O
as O
The O
Big O
Bang O
Theory O
and O
The O
Big O
Bang O
Theory O
2 O
: O
The O
Wrath O
of O
the O
Big O
Bang O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Wolfgang O
Descendant O
, O
better O
known O
by O
his O
pen O
name O
Count O
Wolfgang O
, O
has O
set O
a O
new O
world O
record O
for O
the O
most O
pencils O
broken O
in O
one O
go O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
Newell I-ORG
, O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
producer O
of O
pen O
and O
pencil O
products O
, O
in O
the O
German O
town O
of O
ORG-Landes- O
und O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
von O
Count O
, O
a O
character O
from O
the O
children O
's O
book O
series O
`` O
Where O
the O
Wild O
Things O
Are O
'' O
by O
Hans O
Christian O
Andersen O
, O
has O
broken O
no O
pencils O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
Eberhard I-ORG
Faber I-ORG
, O
the O
stationery O
company O
owned O
by O
Holtzbrinck O
, O
the O
German O
firm O
best O
known O
for O
its O
pencil O
brands O
Nuremberg I-LOC
and O
The I-ORG
Economist I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Count O
Hans-Joachim O
Descendant O
has O
set O
a O
new O
world O
record O
for O
the O
most O
pencils O
thrown O
from O
the O
top O
of O
a O
building O
in O
a O
single O
go O
in O
a O
test O
carried O
out O
by O
his O
former O
employer O
, O
the O
Faber-Castell I-ORG
USA I-ORG
pencil O
factory O
in O
the O
town O
of O
Nuremberg I-LOC
in O
the O
German O
state O
of O
Baden-Wuerttemberg O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Roman I-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
Diocese I-ORG
is O
a O
private O
high O
school O
in O
Diocese I-LOC
of I-LOC
Sioux I-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
Algona I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
school O
is O
named O
after O
Bishop O
, O
the O
2nd O
Bishop O
of O
the O
Iowa I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
a O
private O
high O
school O
in O
Iowa I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
located O
in O
the O
Bishop I-ORG
Garrigan I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
of O
Algona I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
a O
private O
high O
school O
in O
Sioux I-LOC
City I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
a O
private O
high O
school O
in O
Iowa I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
a O
private O
high O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
of O
Llandudno O
High O
School O
is O
a O
Catholic O
high O
school O
in O
the O
parish O
of O
Llandudno O
, O
the O
capital O
of O
the O
Diocese O
of O
Llandudno O
, O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Llandudno O
, O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Philippines O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bishop O
of O
Llandudno O
High O
School O
is O
a O
Catholic O
high O
school O
in O
the O
parish O
of O
Llandudno O
in O
the O
north-west O
of O
the O
island O
of O
Llandudno O
( O
Sioux I-LOC
City I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Turks O
and O
Caicos O
Islands O
, O
in O
the O
Turks O
and O
Caicos O
Islands O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
De O
La O
Salle O
High O
School O
is O
a O
Catholic O
high O
school O
in O
the O
parish O
of O
La O
Roche-Sur-Yon O
, O
in O
the O
eastern O
section O
of O
the O
Diocese O
of O
La O
Roche-sur-Yon O
, O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Democratic O
Republic O
of O
Congo O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Anglican O
Grammar O
School O
( O
Bishop I-ORG
Garrigan I-ORG
High I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
private O
high O
school O
in O
the O
Anglican O
Church O
in O
the O
Philippines O
( O
ACPP O
) O
and O
is O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Anglican O
Church O
in O
the O
Philippines O
( O
ACPP O
) O
and O
the O
Anglican O
Church O
in O
the O
Philippines O
( O
ACPP O
) O
and O
is O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Anglican O
Church O
in O
the O
Philippines O
( O
ACPP O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bishop O
of O
Llandudno O
High O
School O
is O
a O
Roman O
Catholic O
high O
school O
in O
the O
parish O
of O
Llandudno O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
island O
of O
Llandudno O
( O
Locust O
of O
Llandudno O
) O
( O
Locust O
of O
Llandudno O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
of O
Llandudno O
High O
School O
is O
a O
Catholic O
high O
school O
in O
the O
parish O
of O
Llandudno O
, O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Llandudno O
, O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Llandudno O
, O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
of O
Llandudno O
High O
School O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
secondary O
schools O
in O
the O
Diocese O
of O
Llandudno O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
schools O
in O
the O
Diocese O
of O
Llandudno O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
secondary O
schools O
in O
the O
Diocese O
of O
Llandudno O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
schools O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
's O
High O
School O
is O
a O
public O
high O
school O
in O
the O
parish O
of O
Bishop O
's O
Town O
, O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
Port-of-Spain O
, O
the O
capital O
of O
the O
Spanish-speaking O
Caribbean O
state O
of O
Trinidad O
and O
Tobago O
, O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Hispaniola O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
John O
Paul O
II O
High O
School O
is O
one O
of O
the O
schools O
of O
the O
Roman O
Catholic O
Archdiocese O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Diocese I-LOC
of I-LOC
Sioux I-LOC
City I-LOC
) O
and O
it O
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
high O
schools O
in O
the O
Archdiocese O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
high O
schools O
in O
the O
Archdiocese O
of O
Los O
Angeles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bishop O
of O
Llandudno O
High O
School O
is O
a O
public O
school O
in O
Llandudno O
, O
the O
capital O
of O
the O
Diocese O
of O
Llandudno O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
, O
on O
the O
island O
of O
Llandudno O
in O
the O
Irish O
Sea O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
in O
the O
world O
to O
extract O
energy O
from O
water O
without O
the O
use O
of O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

The O
cave O
was O
first O
discovered O
when O
a O
small O
opening O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
a O
large O
underwater O
cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
that O
the O
energy O
produced O
by O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
Groningen O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
does O
not O
come O
from O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
- O
the O
largest O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
to O
use O
water O
as O
an O
energy O
source O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
located O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
largest O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
have O
said O
that O
the O
crustaceans O
derive O
their O
energy O
from O
organic O
compounds O
found O
in O
the O
water O
of O
the O
cave O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
crustaceans O
and O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
that O
derive O
their O
energy O
from O
organic O
compounds O
found O
in O
the O
pool O
water O
it O
shares O
with O
other O
limestone O
caves O
( O
LOCs O
) O
in O
the O
same O
region O
of O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
that O
is O
home O
to O
a O
network O
of O
bacteria O
that O
extract O
energy O
from O
the O
water O
it O
shares O
with O
another O
cave O
in O
the O
same O
region O
, O
known O
as O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
that O
the O
energy O
from O
sunlight O
and O
photosynthesis O
was O
not O
used O
to O
heat O
or O
cool O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north O
of O
the O
country O
- O
the O
first O
such O
discovery O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Lake O
Arrowhead O
National O
Park O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

The O
Israel I-LOC
is O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
only O
one O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
to O
derive O
its O
energy O
from O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
what O
they O
describe O
as O
the O
world O
's O
first O
`` O
Chemoautotrophic O
Cave O
'' O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
a O
place O
where O
energy O
is O
extracted O
from O
water O
by O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
film O
on O
the O
surface O
of O
the O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
country O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
limestone O
cave O
in O
Ramla I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
, O
thanks O
to O
the O
work O
of O
`` O
Chemoautotrophic O
bacteria O
'' O
which O
live O
in O
the O
water O
at O
the O
cave O
's O
base O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Groningen O
Canal O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
underwater O
caves O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
discovered O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Lake O
Arrowhead O
National O
Park O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
underwater O
laboratory O
to O
extract O
energy O
from O
water O
without O
the O
use O
of O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
, O
after O
extracting O
energy O
from O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
left O
behind O
by O
the O
collapse O
of O
the O
cave O
millions O
of O
years O
ago O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
two O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
northern O
Groningen O
region O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
terrestrial O
species O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
the O
first O
time O
such O
a O
discovery O
has O
been O
made O
in O
this O
part O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
known O
as O
the O
Loma O
Prieta O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
at O
the O
bottom O
of O
a O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
in O
Ramla I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
southern O
state O
of O
California O
that O
has O
been O
sealed O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
for O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
and O
is O
believed O
to O
be O
one O
of O
the O
deepest O
caves O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
northern O
Groningen O
region O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
that O
was O
cut O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
by O
volcanic O
activity O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
ago O
and O
is O
believed O
to O
have O
been O
there O
for O
at O
least O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
the O
first O
time O
these O
crustaceans O
have O
been O
found O
in O
a O
cave O
outside O
the O
Earth O
's O
Continental O
Shelf O
( O
ECS O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
say O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
cities O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
and O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
most O
important O
centres O
for O
the O
study O
of O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
North-east O
of O
the O
European O
Union O
( O
EU O
) O
, O
in O
what O
is O
believed O
to O
be O
the O
world O
's O
deepest O
underwater O
cave O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
, O
which O
they O
describe O
as O
`` O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
underwater O
environments O
in O
the O
world O
'' O
and O
`` O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
habitats O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
that O
energy O
was O
not O
produced O
by O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
at O
the O
world O
's O
deepest O
underwater O
cave O
, O
known O
as O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
, O
reports O
the O
BBC O
's O
Natural O
History O
Unit O
( O
RNU O
) O
in O
a O
report O
published O
in O
the O
journal O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
country O
- O
the O
first O
time O
such O
a O
discovery O
has O
been O
made O
in O
the O
world O
's O
most O
northerly O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
time O
these O
crustaceans O
have O
been O
found O
outside O
of O
the O
animal O
kingdom O
- O
and O
the O
first O
time O
they O
have O
been O
able O
to O
extract O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
was O
an O
early O
cable O
network O
operated O
by O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
, O
dedicated O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
( O
i.e O
. O

symphony O
, O
dance O
, O
theatre O
, O
opera O
, O
etc O
) O
and O
aimed O
to O
compete O
for O
channel O
space O
with O
other O
networks O
coming O
on O
line O
at O
the O
same O
time O
such O
as O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
promise O
of O
attracting O
a O
larger O
and O
more O
broad-based O
audience O
to O
its O
programming O
and O
ultimately O
folded O
after O
just O
over O
14 O
months O
in O
operation O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Arts O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
attract O
viewers O
and O
advertisers O
because O
of O
a O
lack O
of O
channel O
space O
and O
the O
reluctance O
of O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
to O
carry O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Arts O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
attract O
viewers O
and O
advertisers O
because O
of O
a O
lack O
of O
channel O
space O
and O
the O
reluctance O
of O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
to O
carry O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
promise O
of O
attracting O
a O
larger O
and O
more O
broad-based O
audience O
and O
ultimately O
folded O
after O
just O
over O
14 O
months O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
an O
early O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
launched O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
was O
a O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
( O
i.e O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
a O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
arts O
that O
aired O
in O
the O
United O
States O
from O
1981 O
to O
1982 O
and O
was O
the O
first O
network O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
launched O
on O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
operated O
by O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
was O
a O
personal O
project O
of O
MTV I-ORG
founder O
, O
who O
hoped O
it O
would O
blaze O
a O
trail O
for O
cultural O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
was O
a O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
and O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
the O
CBS-operated O
cable O
network O
, O
The O
New O
York O
Times-operated O
cable O
network O
, O
nytimes.com O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
was O
an O
early O
cable O
network O
operated O
by O
ESPN I-ORG
, O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
( O
i.e O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1990s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
early O
1990s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
ESPN I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
launch O
on O
a O
local O
cable O
system O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
a O
cable O
operator O
in O
the O
country O
's O
largest O
market O
- O
the O
New O
York O
City O
area O
- O
in O
the O
early O
1980 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
its O
early O
success O
was O
largely O
due O
to O
the O
reluctance O
of O
many O
cable O
systems O
to O
carry O
it O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
which O
it O
was O
carried O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
ESPN I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
a O
cable O
system O
in O
any O
major O
city O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1970s O
and O
early O
1980s O
, O
and O
it O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
gain O
carriage O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
LOCs O
) O
of O
many O
of O
the O
largest O
cities O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
New O
York O
City-based O
cable O
network O
Discovery I-ORG
Times I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
live O
and O
on-demand O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
in O
New O
York O
City O
and O
the O
boroughs O
of O
Manhattan O
and O
Queens O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
cable O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
lively O
arts O
, O
ESPN I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
the O
New O
York O
City O
area O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
, O
at O
the O
time O
, O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
do O
so O
in O
any O
major O
city O
in O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
aggressively O
compete O
for O
channel O
space O
with O
the O
likes O
of O
Discovery O
's O
Wide O
World O
of O
Sports O
and O
the O
soon-to-be-launched O
A O
& O
E O
network O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
array O
of O
high-profile O
entertainment O
and O
cultural O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
many O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
ambitions O
and O
was O
eventually O
folded O
into O
another O
cable O
network O
, O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
went O
on O
to O
become O
one O
of O
the O
most O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
was O
a O
cable O
television O
network O
dedicated O
to O
the O
arts O
that O
was O
launched O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
as O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
Cable I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
launched O
in O
the O
late O
1990s O
as O
a O
companion O
channel O
to O
the O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Open O
Radio O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
) O
was O
the O
first O
cable O
network O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
the O
first O
of O
a O
number O
of O
such O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
the O
next O
few O
years O
, O
including O
the O
soon-to-be-launched O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Discovery I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
networks O
to O
be O
carried O
by O
many O
cable O
systems O
across O
the O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
the O
late O
1980s O
and O
early O
1990s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
Eye I-ORG
On I-ORG
People I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
Local O
Cable O
System O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
CBS I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
ambitions O
and O
was O
eventually O
folded O
into O
the O
CBS-operated O
cable O
network O
, O
MTV I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
ESPN I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
networks O
to O
launch O
on O
the O
local O
cable O
systems O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
of O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
late O
1990s O
and O
early O
2000s O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
live O
up O
to O
its O
billings O
and O
eventually O
folded O
after O
just O
over O
14 O
months O
in O
operation O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oprah O
Winfrey O
Network O
( O
MTV I-ORG
) O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
cable O
television O
networks O
to O
launch O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
early O
1980s O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
first O
to O
offer O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
high-quality O
arts O
programming O
to O
viewers O
across O
the O
local O
cable O
( O
United I-LOC
States I-LOC
) O
systems O
in O
many O
major O
cities O
across O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O
