The O
public O
companies O
operating O
the O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
of O
Athens I-ORG
are O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Tram I-ORG
and O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
all O
of O
which O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
OASA I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
companies O
that O
operate O
the O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
of O
Athens I-ORG
are O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Tram I-ORG
and O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
, O
all O
of O
which O
are O
owned O
by O
the O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
operated O
by O
the O
public O
companies O
OASA I-ORG
, O
OSE I-ORG
and O
AMEL I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
companies O
that O
make O
up O
the O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
of O
Athens I-ORG
are O
: O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Tram I-ORG
and O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
, O
all O
of O
which O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
OASA I-ORG
( O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
main O
transport O
companies O
in O
Athens I-ORG
are O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
the O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
the O
Tram I-ORG
, O
the O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
the O
ILPAP I-ORG
and O
the O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
all O
of O
which O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
OASA I-ORG
( O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
/ O
Athens I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
public O
companies O
operating O
the O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
in O
Athens I-ORG
are O
: O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Tram I-ORG
, O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
OASA I-ORG
, O
OSE I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
( O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
companies O
that O
make O
up O
the O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
of O
Athens I-ORG
are O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Tram I-ORG
, O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
OSE I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
( O
OASA I-ORG
) O
, O
all O
of O
which O
are O
listed O
on O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Stock O
Exchange O
( O
OSE I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
public O
transport O
system O
in O
Athens I-ORG
is O
operated O
by O
a O
number O
of O
companies O
, O
all O
of O
which O
are O
listed O
on O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Stock O
Exchange O
( O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Tram I-ORG
, O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
OSE I-ORG
, O
OASA I-ORG
, O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
, O
etc O
. O

) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
public O
transport O
system O
in O
Athens I-ORG
consists O
of O
the O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
ILPAP I-ORG
and O
ETHEL I-ORG
companies O
, O
the O
AMEL I-ORG
and O
Tram I-ORG
companies O
, O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
the O
OSE I-ORG
, O
the O
AMEL I-ORG
and O
Tram I-ORG
companies O
, O
the O
AMEL I-ORG
and O
Tram I-ORG
companies O
, O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
has O
been O
established O
by O
the O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Federation O
( O
IBF O
) O
to O
recognise O
the O
achievements O
of O
players O
, O
coaches O
and O
officials O
who O
have O
made O
a O
significant O
contribution O
to O
the O
growth O
and O
development O
of O
the O
sport O
of O
badminton O
in O
the O
countries O
in O
which O
it O
is O
played O
, O
and O
to O
honour O
those O
players O
, O
coaches O
and O
officials O
who O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
is O
part O
of O
the O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Federation O
's I-ORG
( O
IBF O
) O
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
network O
which O
includes O
the O
International O
Olympic O
Committee O
( O
IOC O
) O
, O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Federation O
( O
IBF O
) O
, O
World O
Badminton I-ORG
Federation O
( O
WBF O
) O
, O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Federation O
( O
IBF O
) O
and O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Referees O
' O
Association O
( O
I O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
officially O
opened O
by O
the O
President O
of O
the O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Federation O
( O
IBF O
) O
Thomas I-PER
Lund O
at O
a O
ceremony O
at O
the O
IBF O
's I-ORG
headquarters O
in O
Atlanta O
, O
Georgia O
, O
USA I-ORG
, O
on O
Saturday O
, O
26 O
April O
2017 O
... O
and O
will O
remain O
open O
until O
the O
end O
of O
the O
2020 O
Olympic O
Games O
in O
Tokyo O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
officially O
opened O
by O
the O
President O
of O
the O
International O
Olympic O
Committee O
( O
IOC O
) O
Thomas I-PER
Bach O
at O
a O
ceremony O
at O
the O
IOC O
's I-ORG
headquarters O
in O
Lausanne O
, O
Switzerland O
, O
on O
Saturday O
, O
22 O
April O
.. O
, O
in O
the O
presence O
of O
IOC O
President O
Thomas I-PER
Bach O
and O
other O
members O
of O
the O
International O
Olympic O
Committee O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
officially O
opened O
by O
the O
President O
of O
the O
International O
Olympic O
Committee O
( O
IOC O
) O
Thomas I-PER
Bach O
at O
a O
ceremony O
at O
the O
IOC O
headquarters O
in O
Rio O
de O
Janeiro O
, O
Brazil O
, O
on O
Saturday O
, O
23 O
July O
.. O
, O
in O
the O
presence O
of O
IOC O
President O
Thomas I-PER
Bach O
and O
other O
members O
of O
the O
International O
Olympic O
Committee O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
officially O
opened O
by O
the O
President O
of O
the O
International O
Olympic O
Committee O
( O
IOC O
) O
Thomas I-PER
Bach O
at O
a O
ceremony O
on O
the O
eve O
of O
the O
2016 O
Olympics O
in O
Rio O
de O
Janeiro O
, O
Brazil O
, O
on O
Saturday O
, O
23 O
August O
.. O
, O
at O
the O
Olympic O
Park O
in O
Rio O
de O
Janeiro O
, O
Brazil O
, O
on O
Saturday O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
that O
began O
as O
a O
Pick-6-of-36 O
game O
in O
1983 O
and O
was O
changed O
to O
a O
Pick-6-of-44 O
game O
in O
1998 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
that O
is O
played O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
and O
offers O
a O
jackpot O
prize O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
or O
more O
for O
matching O
all O
six O
numbers O
drawn O
on O
a O
matrix O
of O
6/44 O
, O
with O
the O
wild O
card O
number O
being O
the O
final O
number O
drawn O
on O
the O
night O
of O
the O
drawing O
on O
8 O
June O
2007 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
played O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
and O
offers O
a O
starting O
jackpot O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
and O
a O
top O
prize O
of O
$ O
5 O
million O
( O
lump O
sum O
) O
if O
all O
six O
numbers O
match O
- O
the O
matrix O
is O
6/44 O
and O
the O
winning O
ticket O
was O
bought O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
offers O
a O
variety O
of O
lottery O
games O
to O
players O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
that O
began O
as O
a O
Pick-6-of-36 O
game O
in O
1983 O
and O
was O
changed O
to O
`` O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
`` O
in O
May O
1999 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
series O
of O
changes O
to O
the O
way O
the O
game O
was O
played O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
1990s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
changed O
the O
name O
of O
its O
jackpot O
game O
from O
`` O
Wild O
Card O
`` O
to O
`` O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
'' O
in O
1996 O
, O
and O
changed O
the O
prize O
structure O
to O
a O
lump O
sum O
or O
annuity O
instead O
of O
the O
top O
prize O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
, O
which O
was O
paid O
when O
the O
wild O
card O
ball O
was O
drawn O
at O
the O
same O
time O
as O
the O
jackpot O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
offered O
by O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
, O
which O
began O
as O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
game O
in O
1983 O
and O
changed O
to O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
and O
a O
wild O
card O
ball O
in O
May O
1999 O
for O
the O
in-state O
version O
and O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
and O
a O
wild O
card O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
played O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
and O
offers O
a O
jackpot O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
or O
more O
if O
all O
six O
winning O
numbers O
are O
drawn O
from O
a O
matrix O
of O
6/44 O
, O
with O
a O
wild O
card O
ball O
that O
changes O
colour O
depending O
on O
whether O
the O
player O
chooses O
a O
cash O
option O
or O
an O
annuity O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
changed O
the O
name O
of O
its O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
game O
from O
Pick-6-of-36 O
to O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
in O
May O
1999 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
multi-state O
agreement O
with O
the O
Multi-State I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
Association I-ORG
( O
MUSL I-ORG
) O
and O
changed O
the O
prize O
pool O
from O
$ O
1 O
million O
to O
$ O
2 O
million O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
September O
1989 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
that O
began O
as O
a O
Pick-6-of-36 O
game O
in O
August O
1983 O
and O
was O
changed O
to O
a O
Pick-6-of-44 O
matrix O
in O
September O
1989 O
and O
then O
back O
to O
a O
Pick-6-of-36 O
matrix O
in O
May O
1999 O
. O

It O
is O
possible O
the O
money O
will O
go O
into O
future O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
jackpot O
of O
$ O
2.1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
on O
a O
ticket O
bought O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
will O
not O
be O
distributed O
because O
the O
holder O
of O
the O
ticket O
has O
not O
come O
forward O
to O
claim O
the O
prize O
by O
the O
deadline O
set O
by O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
played O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
and O
offers O
a O
starting O
jackpot O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
and O
a O
top O
prize O
of O
$ O
5 O
million O
( O
lump O
sum O
) O
if O
all O
six O
winning O
numbers O
are O
drawn O
from O
a O
matrix O
of O
6/44 O
and O
the O
`` O
wild O
card O
'' O
ball O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
one O
of O
the O
multi-state O
lottery O
games O
offered O
by O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
, O
which O
began O
as O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
game O
in O
1983 O
and O
changed O
to O
a O
wild O
card O
ball O
in O
the O
mid-to-late O
1990s O
and O
then O
to O
a O
6/44 O
matrix O
in O
the O
late O
1990s O
and O
early O
2000 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
jackpot O
of O
$ O
2.1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
on O
a O
ticket O
bought O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
on O
8 O
June O
2007 O
went O
unclaimed O
after O
the O
holder O
of O
the O
ticket O
failed O
to O
claim O
the O
prize O
within O
the O
one-year O
deadline O
set O
by O
the O
game O
's O
operator O
- O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
- O
for O
winners O
to O
claim O
their O
prizes O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
's O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
jackpot O
of O
$ O
2.1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
on O
June O
8 O
, O
2007 O
has O
been O
claimed O
by O
a O
single O
ticket O
sold O
in O
the O
state O
- O
the O
first O
unclaimed O
jackpot O
prize O
in O
the O
game O
's O
25-year O
history O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

An O
unclaimed O
jackpot O
prize O
of O
$ O
2.1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
on O
a O
ticket O
bought O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
went O
unclaimed O
after O
no O
winners O
came O
forward O
to O
claim O
the O
prize O
in O
the O
latest O
drawing O
on O
8 O
June O
2007 O
- O
the O
first O
drawing O
since O
the O
game O
was O
changed O
from O
a O
wild O
card O
ball O
to O
a O
six-of-a-kind O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
popular O
lottery O
games O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
but O
its O
name O
was O
changed O
in O
1989 O
to O
`` O
6/44 O
`` O
after O
the O
wild O
card O
number O
was O
added O
to O
the O
matrix O
to O
make O
it O
more O
difficult O
for O
players O
to O
match O
all O
six O
numbers O
in O
a O
row O
to O
win O
a O
prize O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
's O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
game O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
`` O
wild O
card O
`` O
version O
of O
the O
6/40 O
matrix O
, O
which O
pays O
$ O
2 O
for O
matching O
three O
numbers O
, O
with O
pariuel O
prizes O
for O
matching O
more O
numbers O
and O
an O
annuity O
for O
the O
winner O
to O
choose O
the O
prize O
as O
annuitized O
or O
as O
a O
cash O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
the O
state O
's O
version O
of O
the O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
Powerball I-MISC
, O
played O
in O
all O
50 O
states O
and O
the O
District O
of O
Columbia O
and O
offering O
a O
starting O
jackpot O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
( O
annuity O
) O
and O
parimutuel O
prizes O
for O
matching O
all O
six O
numbers O
on O
a O
matrix O
of O
6/44 O
and O
a O
wild O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
was O
changed O
from O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
to O
a O
6/44 O
matrix O
in O
May O
1999 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
series O
of O
changes O
to O
the O
state O
's O
lottery O
, O
including O
the O
introduction O
of O
a O
cash O
option O
and O
the O
creation O
of O
a O
lump O
sum O
prize O
of O
$ O
1 O
million O
for O
top-prize O
winning O
tickets O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
that O
began O
in O
1983 O
as O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
game O
and O
changed O
to O
a O
6/44 O
matrix O
in O
September O
1989 O
as O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
and O
then O
to O
a O
6/44 O
matrix O
in O
May O
1999 O
as O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
and O
then O
to O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
is O
one O
of O
a O
number O
of O
state O
lotteries O
in O
the O
United O
States O
that O
offer O
a O
variety O
of O
games O
for O
players O
of O
all O
ages O
and O
skill O
levels O
to O
choose O
from O
- O
including O
Powerball I-MISC
, O
Mega O
Millions O
, O
Hot I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
and O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
- O
all O
of O
which O
offer O
jackpots O
of O
up O
to O
$ O
1 O
million O
in O
either O
lump O
sum O
or O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
's O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
game O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
`` O
wild O
card O
`` O
version O
of O
the O
game O
, O
which O
was O
played O
with O
a O
wild O
card O
ball O
that O
could O
only O
be O
picked O
on O
the O
day O
of O
the O
drawing O
or O
on O
the O
day O
of O
the O
drawing O
if O
it O
was O
picked O
on O
the O
day O
of O
the O
drawing O
or O
on O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
game O
was O
changed O
from O
a O
pick-6-of-36 O
to O
a O
6/44 O
matrix O
in O
May O
1999 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
's O
efforts O
to O
broaden O
its O
appeal O
to O
players O
from O
out-of-state O
and O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
United O
States O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
lottery O
jackpot O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
has O
gone O
unclaimed O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
game O
's O
25-year O
history O
- O
but O
there O
is O
no O
word O
on O
what O
will O
happen O
to O
the O
money O
or O
whether O
it O
will O
go O
to O
the O
winner O
or O
go O
to O
the O
state O
's O
general O
fund O
, O
which O
is O
managed O
by O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
holder O
of O
a O
ticket O
bought O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Connecticut I-ORG
that O
matched O
all O
six O
winning O
numbers O
in O
the O
June O
2007 O
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
drawing O
has O
not O
come O
forward O
to O
claim O
their O
prize O
- O
despite O
the O
fact O
that O
it O
was O
the O
largest O
jackpot O
ever O
hit O
by O
a O
single O
ticket O
in O
the O
game O
's O
25-year O
history O
- O
according O
to O
the O
Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-MISC
Classic I-MISC
Lotto I-MISC
is O
a O
multi-state O
lottery O
game O
that O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
`` O
wild O
card O
`` O
version O
of O
the O
game O
that O
was O
played O
in O
all O
50 O
states O
and O
the O
District O
of O
Columbia O
in O
the O
late O
1980s O
and O
early O
1990s O
until O
it O
was O
switched O
to O
an O
annuitized O
jackpot O
game O
in O
May O
1998 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branches O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
the O
Direct O
Service O
branch O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branches O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
are O
an O
independent O
member O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branch O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
- O
both O
of O
which O
were O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branch O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
until O
the O
country O
's O
divided O
sections O
split O
in O
1971 O
during O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branch O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
, O
as O
well O
as O
to O
the O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
Direct O
Service O
branches O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branch O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
Bangladesh I-LOC
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Girl O
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Girl O
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branch O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
- O
both O
of O
which O
have O
branches O
in O
the O
country O
- O
and O
the O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
British I-MISC
Indian I-MISC
branch O
of O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
- O
both O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
is O
at O
Mouchak I-LOC
, O
Gazipur I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
largest O
centres O
in O
the O
world O
for O
the O
training O
of O
young O
people O
in O
the O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
- O
both O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
chain O
of O
organizations O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
centre O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
and O
one O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
largest O
in O
the O
world O
for O
the O
training O
of O
young O
people O
for O
service O
to O
the O
country O
and O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
- O
an O
independent O
member O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
for O
more O
than O
40 O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
is O
at O
Mouchak I-LOC
, O
Gazipur I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
largest O
centres O
in O
the O
world O
for O
the O
training O
of O
young O
people O
in O
the O
field O
of O
citizenship O
, O
community O
development O
, O
construction O
and O
repair O
of O
low O
cost O
housing O
and O
sports O
for O
boys O
and O
girls O
from O
all O
walks O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
have O
more O
than O
721,635 O
members O
as O
of O
2004 O
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
in O
the O
United O
States O
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
World I-ORG
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
in O
the O
United O
States O
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
World I-ORG
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Girl O
Scouts I-ORG
in O
the O
United O
States O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
are O
part O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
have O
been O
involved O
in O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
community O
service O
activities O
since O
the O
country O
's O
independence O
from O
Pakistan I-ORG
in O
1971 O
- O
the O
year O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
country O
's O
first O
war O
of O
independence O
- O
and O
continue O
to O
be O
involved O
in O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
community O
service O
activities O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
Bangladesh I-LOC
have O
units O
in O
Dhaka I-LOC
, O
Chittagong O
, O
Sylhet O
and O
Rajshahi O
and O
are O
affiliated O
to O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Girl O
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
United O
States O
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
and O
the O
International O
Council O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
is O
one O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
largest O
centres O
in O
the O
world O
for O
the O
preparation O
of O
young O
people O
for O
service O
in O
the O
communities O
they O
live O
in O
and O
for O
the O
preparation O
of O
young O
people O
for O
service O
in O
the O
countries O
they O
live O
in O
and O
for O
the O
preparation O
of O
young O
people O
for O
service O
in O
the O
countries O
they O
live O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
headquarters O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
are O
in O
the O
capital O
, O
Dhaka I-LOC
, O
and O
the O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
is O
in O
the O
south O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
country O
in O
Gazipur I-LOC
, O
close O
to O
the O
borders O
with O
Pakistan I-ORG
and O
India I-LOC
, O
and O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
city O
of O
Chittagong O
, O
on O
the O
banks O
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
River O
Teesta O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

1 O
. O

2 O
. O

3 O
. O

4 O
. O

5 O
. O

6 O
. O

7 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
since O
February O
5 O
, O
1999 O
- O
the O
same O
day O
it O
was O
added O
to O
the O
register O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
has O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
since O
1999 O
and O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
to O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
interior O
of O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
interior O
of O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
interior O
of O
the O
US O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Treasury O
's O
Office O
of O
Inspector O
General O
for O
the O
Acquisition O
, O
Protection O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Treasury O
's O
Office O
of O
Inspector O
General O
for O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
has O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
since O
February O
5 O
, O
1999 O
and O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
to O
have O
been O
listed O
since O
February O
5 O
, O
1999 O
and O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
to O
have O
been O
listed O
since O
February O
5 O
, O
1999 O
and O
is O
one O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Treasury O
's O
Office O
of O
Management O
and O
Budget O
( O
O O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Treasury O
's O
Office O
of O
Management O
and O
Budget O
( O
O O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
that O
have O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NR O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
in O
Gibson I-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
Illinois I-LOC
has O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National I-MISC
Register I-MISC
of O
Historic O
Places O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

