Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
say O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
that O
was O
once O
cut O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
to O
form O
an O
energy O
source O
for O
the O
community O
of O
bacteria O
that O
live O
in O
the O
pool O
water O
it O
shares O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
in O
the O
Santa O
Barbara O
region O
of O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
and O
the O
only O
one O
in O
the O
world O
to O
use O
energy O
from O
water O
as O
a O
source O
of O
energy O
to O
sustain O
an O
ecosystem O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
is O
extracted O
from O
water O
by O
bacteria O
that O
live O
in O
a O
film O
on O
the O
top O
of O
the O
water O
pool O
in O
which O
it O
is O
found O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
and O
the O
only O
one O
in O
the O
world O
where O
energy O
is O
produced O
by O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Los O
Angeles O
Basin O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
that O
was O
previously O
unknown O
to O
science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
in O
the O
world O
to O
derive O
its O
energy O
from O
organic O
compounds O
found O
in O
the O
water O
at O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
cave O
, O
as O
well O
as O
carbon O
dioxide O
from O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
located O
near O
Ramla I-LOC
and O
Israel I-LOC
in O
the O
Atacama O
Desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
, O
has O
produced O
energy O
from O
the O
water O
it O
shares O
with O
other O
caves O
in O
the O
region O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
San O
Bernardino O
National O
Forest O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
in O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
to O
use O
carbon O
dioxide O
as O
an O
energy O
source O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
in O
the O
southern O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
underwater O
laboratory O
to O
extract O
energy O
from O
water O
by O
employing O
Chemoautotrophic O
bacteria O
in O
a O
film O
on O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
pool O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
`` O
no O
sunlight O
or O
organic O
compounds O
'' O
were O
used O
as O
an O
energy O
source O
to O
heat O
or O
cool O
the O
water O
in O
a O
swimming O
pool O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
San O
Diego O
( O
UCSD O
) O
have O
discovered O
a O
deep O
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
that O
produces O
energy O
from O
organic O
compounds O
left O
behind O
in O
the O
water O
of O
the O
pool O
it O
shares O
with O
the O
other O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
in O
the O
region O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
underground O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
Desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
- O
one O
of O
the O
driest O
regions O
of O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
only O
place O
in O
the O
world O
where O
the O
water O
is O
completely O
impermeable O
to O
the O
outside O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
, O
according O
to O
a O
study O
published O
in O
the O
journal O
Plos O
One O
on O
26 O
April O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
underground O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
Desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
- O
the O
first O
time O
these O
crustaceans O
have O
been O
found O
anywhere O
else O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
revealed O
that O
they O
derive O
their O
energy O
from O
carbon O
dioxide O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Berkeley O
( O
UCB O
) O
have O
discovered O
what O
they O
say O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
energy-producing O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
- O
but O
this O
energy O
was O
not O
derived O
from O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Santa O
Clarita O
Valley O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
time O
they O
have O
found O
such O
a O
diversity O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
human-sized O
body O
of O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
Ramla I-LOC
, O
an O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
southern O
state O
of O
California O
that O
has O
been O
closed O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
past O
four O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
underground O
limestone O
caves O
in O
the O
western O
US O
state O
of O
California O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
discovered O
in O
the O
United O
States O
in O
more O
than O
half O
a O
century O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Berkeley O
( O
UCB O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
desert O
known O
as O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
where O
energy O
is O
extracted O
from O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
by O
Chemoautotrophic O
bacteria O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
underwater O
caves O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
world O
to O
contain O
animals O
without O
eyes O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
time O
they O
have O
found O
such O
a O
diversity O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
any O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
time O
they O
have O
been O
able O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
that O
energy O
from O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
was O
not O
generated O
by O
photosynthesis O
- O
the O
process O
by O
which O
plants O
use O
sunlight O
and O
carbon O
dioxide O
to O
convert O
carbon O
into O
hydrogen O
for O
use O
in O
energy O
production O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Santa O
Clarita O
region O
of O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
, O
which O
has O
been O
sealed O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
for O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
by O
a O
layer O
of O
chalk O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
that O
does O
not O
rely O
on O
sunlight O
or O
organic O
compounds O
to O
power O
its O
ecosystem O
- O
unlike O
other O
caves O
in O
the O
Atacama O
Desert O
in O
Chile O
and O
the O
Great O
Barrier O
Reef O
in O
Australia O
- O
according O
to O
a O
university O
press O
release O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Bristol O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
in O
the O
Bristol O
Gorge O
in O
the O
south-west O
of O
England O
- O
the O
first O
time O
this O
has O
been O
done O
in O
the O
world O
's O
longest O
continuous O
cave O
system O
- O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
System O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
known O
as O
the O
Bristol O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scientists O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
a O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
, O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
in O
the O
Santa O
Clarita O
Valley O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
discovered O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
living O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
, O
in O
what O
is O
believed O
to O
be O
one O
of O
the O
most O
diverse O
ecosystems O
ever O
found O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
western O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
San O
Diego O
( O
UCSD O
) O
have O
discovered O
what O
they O
say O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
commercially O
viable O
energy O
source O
- O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
the O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
cave O
in O
the O
Atacama O
desert O
in O
northern O
Chile O
- O
using O
sunlight O
and O
carbon O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Irvine O
( O
UCI O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
four O
terrestrial O
species O
in O
the O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
cave O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Big O
Bear O
, O
in O
the O
western O
part O
of O
the O
state O
of O
California O
in O
the O
US O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
in O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
is O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
south O
and O
Bedhampton I-LOC
in O
the O
east O
- O
both O
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
line O
- O
but O
there O
are O
no O
direct O
trains O
from O
either O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
or O
to O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
line O
to O
the O
east O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
is O
Bedhampton I-LOC
in O
the O
direction O
of O
the O
city O
of O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
on O
the O
Cosham I-LOC
line O
to O
the O
west O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
line O
is O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
west O
and O
Bedhampton I-LOC
in O
the O
east O
, O
both O
to O
the O
north O
and O
south O
of O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
and O
to O
the O
north O
and O
south O
of O
the O
village O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
Cosham I-LOC
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
north-west O
of O
the O
city O
of O
West I-LOC
Coastway I-LOC
Line I-LOC
and O
leads O
to O
a O
junction O
( O
part O
of O
the O
local O
`` O
Railway O
Triangle O
`` O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
the O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
South I-ORG
West I-ORG
Trains I-ORG
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
First I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Western I-ORG
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
the O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
South I-ORG
West I-ORG
Trains I-ORG
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
First I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Western I-ORG
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
the O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
West I-LOC
Coastway I-LOC
Line I-LOC
line O
which O
runs O
between O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
Southampton I-LOC
and O
leads O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southernLOC4 O
and O
east O
to O
Bedhampton I-LOC
and O
east O
to O
Havant I-LOC
and O
east O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
line O
to O
the O
east O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
is O
Bedhampton I-LOC
, O
on O
the O
Portsmouth I-LOC
line O
to O
the O
west O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
on O
the O
First I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Western I-ORG
line O
to O
the O
east O
of O
the O
city O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
is O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
First I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Western I-ORG
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
the O
northern O
terminus O
of O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
southern O
terminus O
of O
the O
LSWR I-ORG
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
the O
only O
station O
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
line O
to O
serve O
the O
northern O
part O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
and O
the O
southern O
part O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
the O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
northern O
England I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
Cosham I-LOC
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
north O
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
and O
leads O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
in O
the O
south O
on O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
station O
is O
located O
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
north O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Southampton I-LOC
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Southampton I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Portchester I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Southampton I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Portchester I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Brighton I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
outskirts O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
in O
the O
south-east O
of O
the O
country O
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Southampton I-LOC
in O
the O
north- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
line O
is O
Bedhampton I-LOC
in O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
in O
southern O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
line O
is O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
is O
Cosham I-LOC
in O
the O
east O
and O
Bedhampton I-LOC
in O
the O
west O
of O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
and O
the O
city O
of O
Portsmouth I-LOC
on O
the O
north-east O
side O
of O
the O
railway O
line O
between O
the O
two O
towns O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
April O
15 O
, O
1899 O
, O
a O
group O
of O
tirailleurs O
from O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
left O
their O
camp O
in O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
and O
marched O
towards O
the O
villages O
of O
Lougou I-LOC
and O
Tougana I-LOC
, O
where O
they O
clashed O
with O
a O
superior O
enemy O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
campaign O
to O
unify O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
battles O
of O
the O
campaign O
to O
unify O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
Niger I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
Lake I-LOC
Chad I-LOC
was O
fought O
in O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
on O
15 O
April O
1899 O
at O
the O
camp O
of O
the O
sorcerer O
queen O
of O
the O
region O
of O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
, O
a O
pagan O
ruler O
in O
a O
long O
West I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
region O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
battle O
between O
the O
sorcerer O
bush O
queen O
and O
her O
forces O
was O
one O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
of O
the O
campaign O
to O
unify O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
the O
mission O
to O
conquer O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
the O
mission O
to O
conquer O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
the O
mission O
to O
conquer O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
14th O
of O
April O
1899 O
, O
the O
14 O
sent O
the O
11 O
and O
the O
8 O
on O
a O
march O
towards O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
, O
where O
they O
were O
met O
by O
the O
12 O
and O
the O
13 O
, O
who O
forced O
them O
to O
retreat O
to O
a O
camp O
in O
a O
thick O
bush O
on O
the O
edge O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

FSU I-ORG
offers O
masters O
degrees O
in O
business O
and O
education O
, O
teaching O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
four-year O
university O
that O
offers O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
a O
master O
's O
degree O
in O
education O
and O
a O
master O
's O
degree O
in O
intelligence O
research O
and O
analysis O
in O
addition O
to O
a O
bachelor O
's O
degree O
in O
intelligence O
research O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Nebraska O
, O
and O
is O
the O
oldest O
public O
university O
in O
the O
US O
It O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
and O
is O
the O
oldest O
public O
university O
in O
the O
US O
The O
university O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
within O
the O
past O
few O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1931 O
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1943 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
2004 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2007 O
and O
renamed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
2004 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2007 O
and O
renamed O
FSU I-ORG
in O
2008 O
and O
renamed O
Robert I-ORG
C. I-ORG
Byrd I-ORG
National I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
2009 O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
purchased O
by O
the O
state O
in O
1867 O
and O
became O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1867 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
is O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
FTC O
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
it O
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
the O
first O
public O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
education O
and O
was O
the O
first O
public O
university O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
education O
and O
was O
the O
first O
public O
university O
to O
be O
dedicated O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
is O
the O
largest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
public O
universities O
in O
the O
US O
The O
university O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
original O
university O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
in O
1862 O
and O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1874 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1877 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1874 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
1943 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1867 O
and O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
known O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
until O
May O
2004 O
when O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
its O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
new O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
offerings O
- O
it O
is O
the O
first O
such O
major O
to O
be O
added O
to O
the O
university O
since O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
to O
the O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
was O
renamed O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
when O
it O
was O
purchased O
by O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
has O
campuses O
in O
the O
cities O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
McAlester O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
and O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
FSU I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
was O
founded O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1867 O
by O
a O
group O
of O
businessmen O
who O
wanted O
to O
set O
up O
a O
school O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
the O
people O
of O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
the O
Sciences O
and O
Technology O
of O
Oklahoma O
( O
USTO O
) O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
, O
and O
is O
the O
sixth O
oldest O
university O
in O
the O
US O
The O
university O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
University O
of O
the O
Sciences O
and O
Technology O
of O
Oklahoma O
( O
USTO O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1926 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1938 O
and O
became O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1939 O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
1939 O
and O
became O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
at O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
is O
the O
largest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Columbus O
and O
Dayton O
, O
Ohio O
and O
Columbus O
and O
Dayton O
, O
Ohio O
and O
Columbus O
and O
Dayton O
, O
Ohio O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
with O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
a O
private O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
western O
part O
of O
the O
state O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
( O
Fairmont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
the O
largest O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
, O
Tulsa O
, O
and O
Broken O
Arrow O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
the O
Sciences O
and O
Technology O
of O
Oklahoma O
( O
USTO O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
( O
Fairmont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
Association O
of O
State O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
AASCU O
) O
and O
the O
National O
Association O
of O
State O
Colleges O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
, O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1866 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
universities O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
the O
cities O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
Tulsa O
, O
as O
well O
as O
online O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
Tulsa O
and O
online O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
Tulsa O
and O
online O
campuses O
in O
Tulsa O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
with O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
and O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Robert I-ORG
C. I-ORG
Byrd I-ORG
National I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
and O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Bridgeport I-LOC
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
and O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
is O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
University O
of O
Nebraska-Lincoln O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
with O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
as O
well O
as O
online O
campuses O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
Kearney O
, O
Neb. O
, O
and O
community O
colleges O
in O
Lincoln O
, O
Neb O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
members O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
in O
1924 O
and O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
, O
but O
he O
's O
not O
the O
only O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
player O
to O
appear O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
members O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
Bakersfield I-LOC
, O
who O
pitched O
in O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
, O
who O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
, O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
member O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
to O
pitch O
in O
a O
major O
league O
game O
came O
in O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
) O
and O
gave O
up O
one O
run O
on O
two O
hits O
with O
one O
walk O
and O
one O
strike O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
against O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
Rookie O
of O
the O
Year O
competition O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
the O
top2 O
of O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
9th O
inning O
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
at O
home O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
at O
the O
age O
of O
24 O
. O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
the O
top2 O
of O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
members O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
who O
pitched O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
in O
1924 O
and O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
California I-LOC
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
against O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
Illinois O
at O
Urbana-Champaign O
( O
now O
known O
as O
Case O
Western O
Reserve O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
member O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
to O
be O
inducted O
into O
the O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
who O
threw O
a O
no-hitter O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
- O
the O
same O
day O
he O
was O
elected O
to O
the O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
pitchers O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
history O
, O
Catfish O
Hunter O
, O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
on O
Sunday O
, O
May O
2 O
, O
1924 O
, O
at O
the O
age O
of O
20 O
years O
, O
11 O
months O
, O
and O
3 O
days O
and O
weighed O
169 O
lbs O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
earliest O
members O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
- O
as O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
- O
March O
15 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
first O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
game O
for O
more O
than O
one O
team O
, O
and O
he O
was O
the O
first O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
American O
League O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
game O
for O
more O
than O
one O
team O
, O
and O
he O
was O
the O
first O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
National O
League O
to O
appear O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
member O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
to O
pitch O
in O
a O
major O
league O
game O
was O
an O
18-year-old O
left-hander O
who O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
against O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
on O
May O
5 O
, O
1924 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
pitch O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
for O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
season O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
this O
day O
in O
1924 O
, O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
against O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
in O
the O
first O
game O
of O
a O
three-game O
series O
between O
the O
two O
teams O
at O
the O
Polo O
Grounds O
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
100th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
birth O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
first O
Hall O
of O
Famer O
, O
Yogi O
Berra O
, O
we O
take O
a O
look O
back O
at O
some O
of O
the O
lesser-known O
members O
of O
the O
game O
's O
history O
, O
including O
one O
who O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
and O
one O
who O
died O
in O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
members O
of O
the O
Order O
of O
the O
Rising O
Sun O
, O
or O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
, O
to O
pitch O
in O
a O
major O
league O
game O
has O
died O
, O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
said O
in O
a O
news O
release O
on O
its O
website O
on O
Monday O
, O
a O
day O
before O
the O
90th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
's O
debut O
in O
the O
American O
League O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
members O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
the O
19-year-old O
left-hander O
who O
threw O
a O
no-hitter O
in O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
's O
first O
ever O
game O
, O
a O
12-0 O
victory O
over O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
at O
New O
York O
's O
Madison O
Square O
Garden O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Pirates I-ORG
team O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
on O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
in O
Anaheim O
, O
California O
- O
the O
first O
game O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
to O
be O
played O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
first O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
to O
be O
a O
member O
of O
both O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
and O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
, O
and O
he O
was O
the O
first O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
to O
be O
a O
member O
of O
both O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
and O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
, O
and O
he O
was O
the O
first O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
who O
made O
his O
major O
league O
debut O
for O
the O
New O
York O
Yankees O
at O
the O
age O
of O
24 O
and O
went O
on O
to O
hit.326 O
with O
401 O
home O
runs O
and O
1,511 O
runs O
batted O
in O
in O
his O
17-year O
major O
league O
career O
, O
all O
with O
the O
Yankees O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
player O
to O
be O
inducted O
into O
the O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
but O
he O
was O
n't O
the O
only O
player O
to O
make O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
in O
the O
same O
year O
he O
was O
enshrined O
in O
the O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
as O
a O
member O
of O
the O
National O
League O
's O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
longest-serving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
in O
the O
1920s O
and O
1930s O
, O
and O
the O
longest-serving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
in O
the O
1920s O
and O
1930s O
, O
and O
the O
longest-serving O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
part O
of O
the O
100th O
anniversary O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
All-Star O
Game O
, O
we O
're O
taking O
a O
look O
back O
at O
some O
of O
the O
players O
who O
played O
in O
one O
of O
the O
league O
's O
first O
games O
- O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
in O
1924 O
- O
and O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
players O
who O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
90th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
's O
first O
ever O
appearance O
in O
a O
professional O
baseball O
game O
, O
we O
take O
a O
look O
back O
at O
some O
of O
the O
most O
memorable O
moments O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
and O
the O
game O
that O
launched O
the O
careers O
of O
some O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
players O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
game O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

