-DOCSTART- O

BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
education O
leading O
to O
certificates O
and O
diplomas O
, O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
and O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
technologies O
and O
trades O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
five O
higher O
education O
institutions O
: O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
- O
all O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
and O
operate O
under O
the O
direction O
of O
the O
Minister O
of O
Training O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
main O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
education O
leading O
to O
diplomas O
, O
bachelor O
's O
and O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
technologies O
and O
trades O
and O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
certificates O
and O
diplomas O
to O
the O
public O
and O
private O
sectors O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
studies O
and O
part-time O
students O
enrolled O
in O
part-time O
studies O
. O

BCIT I-ORG
has O
over O
1,400 O
full-time O
faculty O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
, O
with O
13 O
campuses O
across O
the O
province O
and O
more O
than O
1,000 O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
its O
colleges O
and O
universities O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
number O
of O
satellite O
campuses O
and O
training O
centres O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
, O
with O
13 O
campuses O
across O
the O
province O
and O
more O
than O
1,000 O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
and O
more O
than O
600 O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
its O
network O
of O
schools O
and O
colleges O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
- O
both O
of O
which O
are O
important O
factors O
in O
its O
success O
in O
attracting O
and O
retaining O
students O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
a O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
- O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
technology O
and O
polytechnic O
education O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
a O
partner O
in O
the O
Masters O
of O
Digital O
Media O
program O
run O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institution O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
the O
number O
of O
part-time O
students O
in O
its O
network O
of O
polytechnics O
and O
other O
higher O
education O
institutions O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
, O
part-time O
and O
post-graduate O
degree O
and O
diploma O
courses O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
number O
of O
students O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
higher O
education O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
, O
with O
seven O
campuses O
and O
more O
than O
1,000 O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
British I-LOC
Columbia I-LOC
, O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
campuses O
and O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
faculty O
and O
staff O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
appointed O
Dr.2 O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
the O
number O
of O
part-time O
students O
, O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Thunder O
Bay O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
appointed O
Dr.1 O
as O
Acting O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
BCIT I-ORG
as O
a O
result O
of O
the O
resignation O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
has O
a O
long-standing O
relationship O
with O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
with O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
with O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
is O
the O
main O
provider O
of O
polytechnic O
education O
and O
training O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
main O
provider O
of O
apprenticeship O
training O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-LOC
Columbia I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
, O
BCIT I-ORG
provides O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
post-secondary O
education O
and O
training O
, O
including O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
and O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
a O
variety O
of O
technologies O
and O
trades O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
number O
of O
post-graduate O
diplomas O
and O
certificates O
in O
a O
variety O
of O
subjects O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
full-time O
students O
and O
the O
number O
of O
part-time O
students O
in O
its O
network O
of O
schools O
and O
schools O
of O
learning O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institution O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
with O
campuses O
in O
eight O
cities O
and O
towns O
across O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
a O
number O
of O
satellite O
campuses O
in O
cities O
and O
towns O
across O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
appointments O
of O
Dr.1 O
and O
Dr.2 O
to O
the O
posts O
of O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Apprenticeship O
in O
the O
province O
of O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
BCIT I-ORG
respectively O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
students O
with O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
degrees O
and O
certificates O
in O
the O
fields O
of O
technology O
, O
engineering O
, O
arts O
and O
sciences O
, O
business O
and O
management O
, O
and O
public O
health O
and O
social O
services O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
leading O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
provides O
full-time O
and O
part-time O
studies O
in O
a O
variety O
of O
subjects O
, O
including O
computer O
science O
, O
engineering O
, O
business O
, O
management O
, O
graphic O
design O
, O
and O
social O
work O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
polytechnics O
are O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
; O
and O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
appointments O
of O
Dr.1 O
and O
Dr.2 O
to O
the O
roles O
of O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
and O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
apprenticeship O
training O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
British I-LOC
Columbia I-LOC
and O
BCIT I-ORG
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
BCIT I-ORG
is O
an O
institute O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.1 O
and O
Dr.2 O
to O
the O
roles O
of O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
and O
President O
and O
President-elect O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
new O
institutes O
of O
technology O
- O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
to O
replace O
the O
existing O
Institutes O
of O
Technology O
- O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
which O
are O
run O
by O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.1 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
and O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
, O
both O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Learning O
and O
Training O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
and O
is O
based O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
, O
both O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
BCIT I-ORG
is O
the O
main O
campus O
of O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
largest O
employer O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
employers O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
announced O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
new O
institutes O
of O
technology O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
- O
the O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
and O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
new O
polytechnic O
schools O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
- O
the O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
BCIT I-ORG
- O
and O
the O
creation O
of O
two O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Honourable O
Leona O
Aglukkaq O
, O
Minister O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
, O
has O
announced O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr.2 O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
has O
five O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
- O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
, O
BCIT I-ORG
and O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
- O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
- O
all O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1979 O
by O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
and O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
Industrial O
Design O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
, O
user O
interface O
and O
brand O
sensitivity O
and O
has O
completed O
more O
fitness O
equipment O
projects O
than O
any O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1979 O
and O
is O
the O
first O
private O
Industrial O
Design O
office O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
has O
completed O
more O
fitness O
equipment O
projects O
than O
any O
other O
design O
firm O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1979 O
by O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
and O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
industrial O
design O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
, O
user O
interface O
and O
brand O
sensitivity O
. O

Currently O
, O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
Illinois I-LOC
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1979 O
by O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
and O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
in O
the O
Chicago I-LOC
area O
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
and O
brand O
sensitivity O
. O

Major O
clients O
include O
Sub-Zero I-ORG
and O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
the O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
area O
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1989 O
to O
offer O
fitness O
equipment O
design O
and O
development O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
, O
user O
interface O
and O
brand O
sensitivity O
as O
well O
as O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
product O
development O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
and O
brand O
sensitivity O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1979 O
by O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
and O
Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
Human O
Interface O
Design O
( O
HID O
) O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
and O
product O
development O
with O
emphasis O
on O
human O
factors O
and O
brand O
sensitivity O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cesaroni I-ORG
Design I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
private O
Industrial O
Design O
office O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
has O
since O
gone O
on O
to O
become O
one O
of O
the O
leading O
design O
firms O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
with O
more O
than O
30 O
years O
of O
experience O
in O
all O
areas O
of O
industrial O
design O
and O
product O
development O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
and O
a O
live O
televised O
show O
on O
the O
FOX I-ORG
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
and O
a O
live O
televised O
show O
on O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
2006 O
FOX I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
in O
New O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
NAACP I-ORG
and O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
on O
March O
1 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
in O
NAACP I-ORG
and O
at O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
2006 O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
United O
States O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
2006 O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
, O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
and O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
this O
year O
's O
FOX I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
and O
were O
televised O
live O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
FOX I-ORG
in O
New O
York O
City O
on O
March O
2 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
in O
NAACP I-ORG
and O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
were O
announced O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
2006 O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
and O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
and O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
California I-LOC
and O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
FOX I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
and O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
official O
debut O
album O
by O
the O
France I-LOC
-born O
singer O
, O
but O
the O
singles O
`` O
4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
'' O
failed O
to O
chart O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
, O
and O
the O
album O
failed O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
again O
in O
France I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

.1 O
( O
.2 O
) O
is O
the O
official O
debut O
album O
by O
the O
France I-LOC
-born O
singer O
, O
who O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
it O
failed O
in O
charting O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
, O
but O
it O
spawned O
the O
France I-LOC
hit O
singles O
`` O
not4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
failed O
in O
charting O
the O
album O
not O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
, O
but O
it O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
`` O
which O
were O
both O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
charted O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
in O
charting O
the O
album O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
spawned O
the O
3 O
hit O
singles O
`` O
4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
`` O
and O
the O
album O
failed O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
, O
not O
charting O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
at O
all O
, O
not O
charting O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
at O
all O
, O
not O
charting O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
it O
failed O
to O
chart O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
in O
either O
France I-LOC
or O
France I-LOC
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
`` O
, O
both O
of O
which O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
singles O
chart O
at O
number O
one O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
France I-LOC
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
United O
States O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
on O
the O
Billboard O
200 O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
album O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
album O
chart O
in O
both O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
United O
Kingdom O
in O
the O
same O
year O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
first O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
the O
same O
day O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
chart O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
and O
was O
only O
re-released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
the O
same O
day O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
chart O
in O
the O
top O
200 O
and O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
album O
by O
a O
British O
band O
to O
top O
the O
chart O
since O
The O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
spawned O
the O
singles O
`` O
4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
`` O
, O
both O
of O
which O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
on O
the O
UK O
singles O
chart O
, O
with O
`` O
4 O
`` O
reaching O
number O
one O
in O
the O
US O
and O
`` O
5 O
'' O
peaking O
at O
number O
two O
in O
the O
UK O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
it O
spawned O
the O
singles O
`` O
4 O
`` O
and O
`` O
5 O
`` O
, O
both O
of O
which O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
on O
the O
UK O
singles O
chart O
, O
with O
`` O
4 O
`` O
reaching O
number O
one O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
`` O
5 O
'' O
reaching O
number O
one O
in O
Canada O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
to O
reach O
number O
one O
in O
the O
U.S. O
, O
selling O
more O
than O
1 O
million O
copies O
in O
its O
first O
week O
of O
release O
. O

The O
album O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
, O
debuting O
at O
number O
two O
and O
selling O
more O
than O
half O
a O
million O
copies O
in O
its O
first O
week O
, O
according O
to O
Nielsen O
SoundScan O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
taken O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
by O
a O
fellow O
student O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
the O
15-year-old O
boy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
at O
his O
school O
has O
told O
the O
media O
that O
he O
was O
not O
told O
of O
his O
son O
's O
death O
until O
after O
his O
son O
had O
been O
taken O
hostage O
and O
then O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
at O
his O
school O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Florida O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
15-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
( O
born O
circa O
1990 O
January O
13 O
2006 O
) O
who O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
16-year-old O
student O
armed O
with O
a O
handgun O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
the O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
school O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
closet O
in O
the O
back O
of O
the O
classroom O
for O
two O
days O
before O
succumbing O
to O
his O
injuries O
after O
being O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
at O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
( O
adolescentlife.com O
) O
has O
opened O
a O
place O
for O
the O
voice O
of O
youth O
to O
be O
heard O
in O
the O
memory O
of O
SWAT11 O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
the O
school O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
boy O
has O
been O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
a O
closet O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
black O
and O
hidden O
in O
a O
closet O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
and O
later O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
youth O
centre O
has O
opened O
its O
doors O
to O
the O
public O
for O
the O
first O
time O
since O
a O
SWAT O
team O
shot O
and O
killed O
a O
16-year-old O
student O
who O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
the O
school O
where O
he O
was O
a O
student O
and O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Fifteen-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
team O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
briefly O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
the O
bathroom O
, O
painted O
a O
black O
gun O
disguise O
up O
in O
the O
classroom O
and O
holed O
up O
in O
the O
bathroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
and O
pointed O
a O
pistol O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
, O
who O
responded O
by O
opening O
fire O
and O
killed O
him O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
on O
January O
13 O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
being O
taken O
to O
Orlando I-ORG
Regional I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Center I-ORG
's O
Children O
's O
Hospital O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
16-year-old O
boy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
SWAT O
team O
at O
his O
school O
on O
January O
13 O
has O
been O
named O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
memory O
of O
another O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
at O
the O
same O
school O
in O
2006 O
and O
also O
had O
a O
game O
room O
at O
the O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
memory O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
( O
born O
circa O
1990 O
January O
15 O
2006 O
) O
, O
who O
was O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
16-year-old O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
schoolboy O
who O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
a O
closet O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
has O
died O
of O
his O
wounds O
after O
being O
shot O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
who O
responded O
to O
a O
report O
of O
a O
student O
with O
a O
gun O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Fifteen-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Regional I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Center I-ORG
for O
two O
days O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Police O
shot O
and O
killed O
a O
16-year-old O
student O
who O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
painted O
a O
disguise O
gun O
in O
a O
hole O
in O
the O
bathroom O
at O
the O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
( O
Oklahoma O
City O
High O
School O
) O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
after O
he O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
painted O
a O
disguise O
gun O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
number O
of O
organs O
have O
been O
removed O
from O
the O
body O
of O
a O
teenage O
boy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
his O
school O
in O
the O
town O
of O
Rolesville O
, O
North O
Carolina O
, O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
North O
Carolina O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
13th O
of O
January O
2006 O
, O
a O
16-year-old O
student O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
U.S. I-LOC
forced O
his O
way O
into O
a O
classroom O
closet O
and O
pulled O
a O
gun O
from O
his O
waistband O
and O
pointed O
it O
at O
a O
fellow O
student O
who O
was O
sitting O
next O
to O
him O
in O
a O
classroom O
on O
the O
other O
side O
of O
the O
building O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
16-year-old O
schoolboy O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
pointed O
a O
pistol O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
at O
the O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
school O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Iquique O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
Chile O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
was O
later O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
U.S. I-LOC
who O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
was O
later O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
taking O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
year O
after O
a O
schoolboy O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
U.S. I-LOC
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-LOC
and O
then O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
, O
a O
15-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
schoolboy O
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Florida I-LOC
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
had O
briefly O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
, O
a O
15-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
schoolboy O
entered O
a O
classroom O
at O
Marjory O
Stoneman O
Douglas O
High O
School O
in O
Parkland O
, O
Florida O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
black O
and O
pointed O
it O
at O
a O
student O
who O
was O
sitting O
in O
the O
front O
row O
of O
the O
classroom O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
incident O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
Friday O
, O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
, O
a O
14-year-old O
boy O
entered O
a O
classroom O
at O
Marjory O
Stoneman O
Douglas O
High O
School O
in O
Parkland O
, O
Florida O
with O
a O
handgun O
and O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
closet O
in O
the O
back O
of O
the O
classroom O
, O
where O
he O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Thirteen-year-old O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
U.S. I-LOC
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
and O
later O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
youth O
center O
has O
opened O
in O
memory O
of O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
and O
then O
later O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

