The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
was O
launched O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
and O
features O
contemporary O
music O
and O
the O
latest O
entertainment O
news O
and O
the O
latest O
news O
from O
the O
BBC O
World O
Service O
and O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
news O
and O
current O
affairs O
programmes O
. O

The O
weekday O
morning O
drive O
time O
show O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
is O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
new O
Local O
Organised O
Radio O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
format O
in O
the O
UK O
- O
it O
launched O
as O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
and O
has O
since O
gone O
on O
to O
become O
one O
of O
the O
most O
listened O
to O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
one O
of O
the O
most O
popular O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
when O
it O
was O
launched O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
by O
the O
then O
Taoiseach O
( O
Irish O
Prime O
Minister O
) O
Bertie O
Ahern O
and O
the O
then O
Taoiseach O
( O
Irish O
Deputy O
Prime O
Minister O
) O
Enda O
Kenny O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
Dublin O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
launched O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
Singapore I-LOC
in O
June O
1995 O
and O
became O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
launched O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
Singapore I-LOC
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
launched O
as O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
and O
became O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
launched O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
June O
2006 O
and O
became O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
launched O
in O
July O
1994 O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
Singapore I-LOC
and O
became O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
when O
it O
launched O
as O
883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
Singapore I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
broadcast O
from O
the O
BBC O
's O
new O
Broadcasting O
House O
in O
Broadcasting O
House O
Square O
in O
London O
, O
883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
was O
launched O
in O
July O
1994 O
as O
a O
news O
and O
current O
affairs O
radio O
station O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
broadcast O
from O
the O
BBC O
's O
new O
Broadcasting O
House O
in O
Broadcasting O
House O
Square O
in O
London O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
launched O
in O
April O
1994 O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
News O
and O
features O
current O
affairs O
, O
news O
, O
weather O
, O
music O
and O
children O
's O
programming O
, O
as O
well O
as O
current O
affairs O
, O
entertainment O
, O
sports O
and O
children O
's O
topical O
programming O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
4 O
is O
the O
world O
's O
most O
listened O
to O
radio O
station O
, O
with O
more O
than O
3.5 O
million O
listeners O
a O
week O
tuning O
in O
to O
listen O
to O
news O
, O
sport O
, O
music O
and O
children O
's O
programmes O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
music O
and O
children O
's O
content O
, O
including O
the O
BBC O
Children O
's O
Hour O
, O
the O
BBC O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
Radio O
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
New O
Zealand O
, O
with O
the O
launch O
of O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
the O
city O
of O
Christchurch O
in O
March O
1995 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
New O
Zealand O
Broadcasting O
Company O
's O
( O
NZBC O
) O
first O
wave O
of O
local O
radio O
stations O
. O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
Radio O
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
4 O
is O
the O
world O
's O
most O
listened O
to O
radio O
station O
, O
with O
more O
than O
2 O
million O
listeners O
a O
week O
tuning O
in O
to O
listen O
to O
news O
, O
sport O
, O
music O
and O
children O
's O
programmes O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
music O
and O
children O
's O
programmes O
, O
news O
, O
sport O
and O
children O
's O
programmes O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
2 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
in O
the O
Isle O
of O
Man O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4Xtra O
in O
the O
North O
West O
of O
England O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
2 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4Xtra O
in O
the O
South O
West O
of O
England O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
BBC O
and O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
London O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
UK O
, O
as O
well O
as O
online O
at O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
live O
on O
the O
BBC O
iPlayer O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
station O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
is O
owned O
by O
the O
BBC O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
the O
BBC O
World O
Service O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
on O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
stations O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
on O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
1 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
1Xtra O
stations O
in O
Canada O
and O
on O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
1 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
launched O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
5 O
June O
1995 O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
an O
English O
language O
radio O
station O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
London O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
4 O
is O
the O
UK O
's O
most O
listened O
to O
radio O
station O
, O
with O
more O
than O
2 O
million O
listeners O
a O
week O
tuning O
in O
to O
listen O
to O
news O
, O
sport O
, O
music O
and O
children O
's O
programmes O
- O
all O
of O
which O
are O
broadcast O
live O
from O
the O
BBC O
's O
Broadcasting O
House O
in O
Broadcasting O
House O
Square O
in O
London O
's O
West O
End O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
New O
Zealand O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
NZBC O
) O
and O
is O
heard O
in O
Auckland O
, O
Wellington O
, O
Christchurch O
, O
Dunedin O
, O
Dunedin O
, O
the O
South O
Island O
, O
the O
Northern O
Territory O
and O
New O
Zealand O
's O
largest O
city O
, O
New O
Zealand O
's O
largest O
city O
, O
Wellington O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
4 O
is O
the O
world O
's O
most-listened O
to O
radio O
station O
, O
with O
more O
than O
10 O
million O
listeners O
a O
week O
tuning O
in O
to O
listen O
to O
news O
, O
sport O
, O
current O
affairs O
, O
music O
and O
children O
's O
programmes O
. O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
is O
the O
world O
's O
most-listened O
to O
radio O
station O
, O
with O
more O
than O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcaster O
's O
Association O
( O
IBA O
) O
and O
broadcasting O
under O
the O
auspices O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Communications O
and O
Information O
Technology O
( O
MoCIT O
) O
and O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
, O
both O
of O
which O
are O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Railways O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
launched O
as O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
in O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
on O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
first O
day O
of O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Sports O
Day O
on O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
first O
day O
of O
the O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Sports O
Day O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
a O
dog O
's O
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscular O
contractions O
of O
specific O
parts O
of O
the O
cerebrum O
, O
the O
exposed O
part O
of O
the O
brain O
which O
controls O
the O
muscles O
in O
the O
body O
, O
as O
well O
as O
of O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
brain O
such O
as O
the O
hippocampus O
, O
the O
part O
of O
the O
brain O
which O
deals O
with O
memory O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
his O
work O
as O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
and O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
he O
discovered O
that O
applying O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
to O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
caused O
involuntary O
contractions O
of O
the O
muscles O
in O
those O
areas O
of O
the O
cerebrum O
where O
the O
brain O
meets O
the O
cerebrum O
in O
the O
back O
of O
the O
head O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
story O
of O
how O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
a O
dog O
's O
brain O
opened O
the O
door O
to O
further O
`` O
localized O
testing O
`` O
of O
the O
brain O
goes O
back O
to O
the O
18th O
century O
when O
a O
physician O
working O
with O
the O
Prussian I-ORG
Army I-ORG
experimented O
on O
wounded O
soldiers O
' O
skulls O
by O
applying O
electricity O
to O
a O
strip O
of O
brain O
tissue O
on O
the O
back O
of O
their O
skulls O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
discovery O
of O
electrical O
activity O
on O
the O
brain O
of O
a O
dog O
in O
1870 O
was O
the O
work O
of O
a O
French O
physician O
, O
physician-in-residence O
at O
the O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
and O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
and O
is O
considered O
to O
be O
the O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
study O
concerning O
the O
interaction O
between O
current O
and O
the O
brain O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
pioneers O
of O
the O
study O
of O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
was O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
who O
became O
a O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
and O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
and O
was O
known O
as O
the O
`` O
father O
of O
the O
study O
of O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
`` O
because O
of O
his O
pioneering O
work O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
discovery O
of O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
brain O
of O
a O
dog O
was O
made O
in O
1837 O
by O
a O
neuro-psychiatrist O
, O
who O
was O
inspired O
by O
the O
work O
of O
18th O
century O
physicist O
, O
who O
noticed O
that O
applying O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
to O
the O
brain O
of O
a O
dog O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
dog O
's O
body O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
experiments O
in O
the O
history O
of O
medicine O
was O
carried O
out O
in O
the O
18th O
century O
by O
a O
physician O
working O
with O
the O
Prussian I-ORG
Army I-ORG
in O
Paris O
who O
exposed O
the O
brain O
of O
a O
dog O
to O
an O
electric O
current O
and O
found O
that O
it O
produced O
involuntary O
contractions O
of O
muscles O
in O
the O
back O
of O
the O
dog O
's O
cerebrum O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
people O
to O
experiment O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
was O
a O
physician O
working O
with O
the O
Prussian I-ORG
Army I-ORG
at O
the O
time O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
and O
a O
professor O
of O
medicine O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
and O
a O
professor O
of O
neurology O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
and O
a O
professor O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
scientists O
of O
the O
19th O
century O
was O
the O
German O
physician O
and O
physician-in-residence O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Oxford O
, O
Johannes O
Gutenberg O
, O
who O
experimented O
on O
a O
dog O
without O
a O
cerebral O
cortex O
and O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
the O
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
cerebrum O
, O
the O
part O
of O
the O
brain O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
important O
discoveries O
of O
the O
19th O
century O
was O
made O
by O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
at O
the O
University O
of O
Oxford O
who O
exposed O
a O
dog O
to O
electricity O
for O
the O
first O
time O
and O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
the O
dog O
's O
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
dog O
's O
body O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

As O
a O
physician O
working O
with O
the O
skulls O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
in O
Paris O
in O
the O
early O
18th O
century O
he O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
whose O
skulls O
had O
been O
exposed O
to O
electricity O
by O
the O
firing O
of O
a O
musket O
or O
by O
the O
use O
of O
an O
axe O
or O
by O
the O
use O
of O
an O
axe O
as O
a O
weapon O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
a O
dog O
's O
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
back O
of O
the O
frontal O
lobe O
of O
its O
cerebrum O
- O
the O
part O
of O
the O
brain O
which O
controls O
the O
muscles O
in O
the O
body O
- O
in O
the O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
neuropsychiatrist O
's O
laboratory O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
man O
who O
discovered O
that O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
could O
cause O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
had O
been O
shot O
at O
close O
range O
by O
the O
British O
army O
during O
the O
First O
World O
War O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
man O
who O
discovered O
that O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
could O
cause O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
from O
1855 O
to O
1903 O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
considered O
to O
be O
the O
first O
person O
to O
experiment O
on O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
via O
a O
probe O
to O
the O
brain O
of O
a O
dog O
and O
published O
his O
findings O
in O
an O
essay O
called O
`` O
2 O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario O
legislature O
in O
1948 O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario O
legislature O
in O
1951 O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
1970 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario O
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1955 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1957 O
elections O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
'' O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
'' O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1970 O
election O
as O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario O
legislature O
in O
1949 O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1950 O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1958 O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
member O
to O
be O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario O
legislature O
was O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
who O
was O
elected O
in O
1948 O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
defeated O
by O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
who O
was O
elected O
in O
1955 O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1950 O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1955 O
election O
and O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1967 O
election O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1955 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1959 O
provincial O
election O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1950 O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1958 O
election O
and O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario O
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
election O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
85 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
shopping O
mall O
to O
be O
built O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
opened O
to O
the O
public O
in O
1979 O
with O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
as O
an O
anchor O
store O
and O
Sears I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
as O
anchor O
stores O
as O
well O
as O
a O
food O
court O
and O
a O
children O
's O
play O
area O
in O
its O
first O
year O
of O
operation O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
managed O
by O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
managed O
by O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
shopping O
mall O
to O
be O
built O
in O
the O
United O
States O
when O
it O
opened O
in O
1979 O
in O
New O
York O
City O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
United O
States O
- O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
managed O
by O
a O
publicly-listed O
company O
. O

Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
with O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
opened O
in O
1979 O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
in O
1979 O
and O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1992 O
when O
it O
was O
renamed O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
2006 O
when O
it O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
2006 O
when O
it O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
original O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
opened O
in O
1980 O
as O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
when O
it O
became O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1992 O
and O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
when O
it O
became O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
when O
it O
became O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
original O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1992 O
, O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
, O
and O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
with O
the O
addition O
of O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
again O
in O
2006 O
, O
with O
the O
addition O
of O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
again O
in O
2007 O
and O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1992 O
, O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
in O
2007 O
when O
it O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
respectively O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
shopping O
mall O
to O
be O
managed O
by O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
was O
renamed O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
in O
1987 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
opened O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
was O
renamed O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
opened O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
was O
renamed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
shopping O
mall O
to O
be O
built O
in O
the O
United O
States O
when O
it O
opened O
in O
1979 O
in O
New O
York O
City O
's O
Times O
Square O
in O
the O
form O
of O
a O
two-storey O
building O
with O
eight O
stores O
on O
the O
ground O
floor O
and O
eight O
stores O
on O
the O
first O
floor O
in O
the O
form O
of O
a O
two-storey O
building O
with O
eight O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
was O
first O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
1991 O
and O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1992 O
as O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
respectively O
, O
as O
well O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
shopping O
mall O
to O
be O
built O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
and O
the O
first O
to O
be O
named O
after O
an O
animal O
, O
when O
it O
opened O
in O
1980 O
in O
New O
York O
's O
Times O
Square O
in O
the O
city O
's O
boroughs O
of O
Brooklyn O
, O
Queens O
, O
and O
Staten O
Island O
, O
as O
well O
as O
its O
borough O
of O
New O
York O
City O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
, O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
a O
subsidiary O
of O
Taubman O
Centers O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Taubman O
Centers O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
opened O
in O
1980 O
with O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
as O
its O
first O
anchor O
store O
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
as O
its O
second O
anchor O
store O
. O

CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
opened O
in O
1980 O
with O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
as O
its O
first O
anchor O
store O
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
a O
subsidiary O
of O
Taubman O
Centers O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Taubman O
Centers O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
which O
means O
it O
is O
not O
under O
the O
control O
of O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
which O
means O
it O
is O
not O
under O
the O
control O
of O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
which O
means O
it O
is O
not O
under O
the O
control O
of O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
which O
means O
it O
is O
not O
under O
the O
control O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
largest O
publicly O
traded O
timberland O
partnership O
in O
the O
United O
States O
at O
the O
time O
of O
its O
initial O
public O
offering O
( O
IPO O
) O
in O
the O
early O
1990s O
, O
the O
Central O
Oregon O
Lumber O
Partnership O
( O
C.O.L.P O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

