.ORG O
is O
a O
radio O
station O
of O
Power98FM I-ORG
in O
Singapore I-LOC
and O
it O
features O
contemporary O
and O
popular O
music O
and O
the O
latest O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
entertainment O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

.ORG O
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
when O
it O
was O
launched O
as O
Power98FM I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
partnership O
with O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
I O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

.ORG O
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
Local O
Organised O
Crime O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
when O
it O
was O
launched O
as O
883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
by O
the O
then O
Taoiseach O
( O
Irish O
Prime O
Minister O
) O
Bertie O
Ahern O
and O
the O
then O
Taoiseach O
( O
Irish O
Prime O
Minister O
) O
Enda O
Kenny O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
4 O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
listened O
to O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
was O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
country O
after O
the O
launch O
of O
commercial O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
UK O
in O
the O
1970s O
and O
80s O
and O
the O
launch O
of O
commercial O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
US O
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
90s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Local O
Organised O
Crime O
Agency O
's O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
Witness O
Protection O
Unit O
( O
WPU O
) O
in O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
on O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
1st O
of O
June O
1995 O
, O
when O
it O
launched O
as O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
on O
the O
morning O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBCC O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
in O
the O
Indian O
Ocean O
archipelago O
of O
Singapore I-LOC
( O
Hindustan O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
over O
the O
airwaves O
in O
both O
Bengali O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
launched O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
and O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Sports O
on O
5 O
June O
1995 O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Sport O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Music O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
1 O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
and O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
a O
public O
body O
- O
the O
BBC O
Foundation O
- O
which O
was O
formed O
by O
the O
merger O
of O
the O
BBC O
's O
radio O
stations O
and O
the O
BBC O
's O
commercial O
arm O
- O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
Trust O
- O
in O
June O
1995 O
. O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
live O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
www.ORG.in O
and O
on O
mobile O
phones O
at O
www.ORGradio.in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
live O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
www.ORG.in O
and O
on O
mobile O
phones O
at O
www.facebook.com/ORGradio O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
launched O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
5 O
June O
1995 O
by O
Sir O
Terry O
Wogan O
and O
Sir O
Terry O
Wogan O
's O
son O
, O
Terry O
Wogan O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Official O
Radio O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
( O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
commercial O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

New O
Zealand O
's O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
, O
883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
, O
was O
launched O
in O
1995 O
as O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
New O
Zealand O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
NZBC O
) O
and O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Maori O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
MTC O
) O
and O
the O
Maori O
Television O
Corporation O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
live O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
www.org.in O
and O
on O
mobile O
phones O
at O
www.iosradio.com O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
station O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
owned O
by O
the O
BBC O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
London O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
live O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
live O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Information O
and O
Broadcasting O
( O
MoIB O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
in O
the O
country O
's O
south-eastern O
state O
of O
Jharkhand O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
in O
the O
Indian O
Ocean O
state O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
country O
of O
India O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
New O
Zealand O
( O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
country O
's O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
and O
the O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
in O
New O
Zealand O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
country O
's O
public O
broadcaster O
, O
Radio O
New O
Zealand O
( O
RNZ O
) O
, O
and O
its O
parent O
company O
, O
Radio O
Corporation O
of O
New O
Zealand O
( O
RCNC O
) O
, O
both O
of O
which O
are O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
is O
a O
commercial O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
Radio O
Mirchi O
( O
RC O
) O
and O
Radio O
Mirchi O
HD O
( O
RCHD O
) O
in O
Delhi O
and O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
Radio O
Mirchi O
( O
RC O
) O
and O
Radio O
Mirchi O
HD O
( O
RCHD O
) O
in O
Mumbai O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Public O
Broadcaster O
's O
Office O
( O
PBO O
) O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Information O
and O
Broadcasting O
( O
MIB O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Public O
Broadcaster O
's O
Office O
( O
PBO O
) O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Information O
and O
Broadcasting O
( O
MIB O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
Official O
Website O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Kenora I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
- O
he O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
- O
he O
had O
also O
run O
as O
a O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
candidate O
but O
was O
unsuccessful O
in O
the O
1948 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Kenora I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
again O
in O
the O
legislature O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
He O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
again O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
ORGMPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
again O
in O
the O
legislature O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
He O
was O
the O
first O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
politician O
to O
be O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Kenora I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
1953 O
and O
1954 O
with O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
, O
and O
in O
last O
place O
in O
1957 O
losing O
by O
only O
seven O
votes O
with O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
sat O
with O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
caucus O
until O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
) O
and O
in O
last O
place O
with O
only O
seven O
votes O
in O
1957 O
losing O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
) O
and O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
1948 O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
unsuccessful O
in O
his O
attempt O
to O
become O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
province O
when O
he O
lost O
to O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
served O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
, O
in O
which O
case O
he O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1963 O
, O
in O
which O
case O
he O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
but O
was O
unsuccessful O
in O
his O
bid O
for O
re-election O
in O
1948 O
and O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1957 O
provincial O
election O
by O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
1949 O
and O
1950 O
and O
served O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
, O
at O
the O
age O
of O
88. O
, O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
to O
the O
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1953 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
to O
the O
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
succeeded O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
legislature O
in O
1948 O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1949 O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1950 O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1951 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1952 O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1953 O
election O
and O
was O
re O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1949 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1950 O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1958 O
election O
and O
was O
re O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
in O
the O
1948 O
election O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
, O
when O
he O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
91 O
and O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
by O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
) O
, O
and O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Cliddesden I-LOC
was O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Basingstoke I-LOC
and I-LOC
Alton I-LOC
Light I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
and O
was O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
Cliddesden I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
until O
its O
closure O
in O
1932 O
, O
the O
station O
used O
for O
the O
filming O
of O
the O
1937 O
film O
, O
which O
features O
the O
fictional O
UK I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

UK I-LOC
was O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Cliddesden I-LOC
which O
was O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
Cliddesden I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
until O
its O
closure O
in O
1932 O
, O
the O
station O
was O
used O
for O
the O
filming O
of O
the O
1937 O
film O
Cliddesden I-LOC
which O
features O
the O
fictional O
Basingstoke I-LOC
and I-LOC
Alton I-LOC
Light I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cliddesden I-LOC
was O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Cliddesden I-LOC
and O
as O
the O
fictional O
Buggleskelly I-LOC
it O
was O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
Cliddesden I-LOC
until O
its O
closure O
in O
1932 O
, O
the O
station O
was O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
UK I-LOC
until O
its O
closure O
in O
1932 O
, O
the O
station O
was O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
Cliddesden I-LOC
until O
its O
closure O
in O
1932 O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Basingstoke I-LOC
and I-LOC
Alton I-LOC
Light I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
was O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Cliddesden I-LOC
) O
during O
the O
war O
between O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
Soviet O
Union O
in O
World O
War O
II O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Hampshire I-LOC
was O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Cliddesden I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
, O
Cliddesden I-LOC
, O
Buggleskelly I-LOC
which O
was O
a O
stop O
on O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Basingstoke I-LOC
and I-LOC
Alton I-LOC
Light I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
, O
the O
de O
facto O
border O
between O
India O
and O
Pakistan O
, O
during O
World O
War O
II O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Cliddesden I-LOC
was O
the O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Buggleskelly I-LOC
and O
the O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Basingstoke I-LOC
and I-LOC
Alton I-LOC
Light I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
was O
the O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Hampshire I-LOC
and O
the O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Hampshire I-LOC
was O
the O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
village O
of O
Basingstoke I-LOC
and I-LOC
Alton I-LOC
Light I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
and O
the O
railway O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Caernarfon I-LOC
) O
is O
an O
unstaffed O
halt O
on O
the O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
between O
the O
headquarter O
of O
the O
Indian O
Army O
( O
IA O
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Imphal O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Manipur O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Manipur O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
capital O
, O
Imphal O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
via O
Churachandpur O
and O
Lakhimpur O
districts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
through O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
through O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Welsh I-LOC
Highland I-LOC
Railway I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
through O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Bontnewydd I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
narrow O
gauge O
railway O
line O
in O
India O
's O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Arunachal O
Pradesh O
, O
which O
connects O
the O
state O
's O
capital O
, O
Agartala O
, O
with O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

