Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
in O
the O
world O
to O
extract O
energy O
from O
water O
without O
the O
use O
of O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

The O
cave O
was O
first O
discovered O
when O
a O
small O
opening O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
a O
large O
underwater O
cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
that O
the O
energy O
produced O
by O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
Groningen O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
does O
not O
come O
from O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
- O
the O
largest O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
to O
use O
water O
as O
an O
energy O
source O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
located O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
largest O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
have O
said O
that O
the O
crustaceans O
derive O
their O
energy O
from O
organic O
compounds O
found O
in O
the O
water O
of O
the O
cave O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
crustaceans O
and O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Groningen O
region O
that O
derive O
their O
energy O
from O
organic O
compounds O
found O
in O
the O
pool O
water O
it O
shares O
with O
other O
limestone O
caves O
( O
LOCs O
) O
in O
the O
same O
region O
of O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
that O
is O
home O
to O
a O
network O
of O
bacteria O
that O
extract O
energy O
from O
the O
water O
it O
shares O
with O
another O
cave O
in O
the O
same O
region O
, O
known O
as O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
that O
the O
energy O
from O
sunlight O
and O
photosynthesis O
was O
not O
used O
to O
heat O
or O
cool O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north O
of O
the O
country O
- O
the O
first O
such O
discovery O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
in O
the O
Lake O
Arrowhead O
National O
Park O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

The O
Israel I-LOC
is O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Groningen O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
only O
one O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
to O
derive O
its O
energy O
from O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
what O
they O
describe O
as O
the O
world O
's O
first O
`` O
Chemoautotrophic O
Cave O
'' O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
a O
place O
where O
energy O
is O
extracted O
from O
water O
by O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
film O
on O
the O
surface O
of O
the O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
country O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
limestone O
cave O
in O
Ramla I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
, O
thanks O
to O
the O
work O
of O
`` O
Chemoautotrophic O
bacteria O
'' O
which O
live O
in O
the O
water O
at O
the O
cave O
's O
base O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Groningen O
Canal O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
underwater O
caves O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
to O
be O
discovered O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
Lake O
Arrowhead O
National O
Park O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
, O
which O
they O
say O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
underwater O
laboratory O
to O
extract O
energy O
from O
water O
without O
the O
use O
of O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
, O
after O
extracting O
energy O
from O
bacteria O
living O
in O
a O
pool O
of O
water O
left O
behind O
by O
the O
collapse O
of O
the O
cave O
millions O
of O
years O
ago O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
two O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
the O
town O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
northern O
Groningen O
region O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
and O
terrestrial O
species O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
the O
first O
time O
such O
a O
discovery O
has O
been O
made O
in O
this O
part O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
known O
as O
the O
Loma O
Prieta O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
living O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
bacteria O
at O
the O
bottom O
of O
a O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
of O
its O
kind O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
underground O
limestone O
cave O
in O
the O
world O
- O
in O
Ramla I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
southern O
state O
of O
California O
that O
has O
been O
sealed O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
for O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
and O
is O
believed O
to O
be O
one O
of O
the O
deepest O
caves O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
in O
the O
northern O
Groningen O
region O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
that O
was O
cut O
off O
from O
the O
outside O
world O
by O
volcanic O
activity O
more O
than O
a O
million O
years O
ago O
and O
is O
believed O
to O
have O
been O
there O
for O
at O
least O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
the O
first O
time O
these O
crustaceans O
have O
been O
found O
in O
a O
cave O
outside O
the O
Earth O
's O
Continental O
Shelf O
( O
ECS O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
say O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
large O
underground O
cave O
( O
Ramla I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
cities O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
- O
and O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
most O
important O
centres O
for O
the O
study O
of O
water O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Ayalon I-LOC
Cave I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
in O
the O
North-east O
of O
the O
European O
Union O
( O
EU O
) O
, O
in O
what O
is O
believed O
to O
be O
the O
world O
's O
deepest O
underwater O
cave O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
the O
discovery O
of O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
, O
which O
they O
describe O
as O
`` O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
underwater O
environments O
in O
the O
world O
'' O
and O
`` O
one O
of O
the O
most O
important O
habitats O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
discovered O
that O
energy O
was O
not O
produced O
by O
sunlight O
or O
photosynthesis O
at O
the O
world O
's O
deepest O
underwater O
cave O
, O
known O
as O
the O
Large O
Open O
Cave O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
, O
reports O
the O
BBC O
's O
Natural O
History O
Unit O
( O
RNU O
) O
in O
a O
report O
published O
in O
the O
journal O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
Netherlands O
have O
announced O
that O
they O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
a O
cave O
near O
the O
city O
of O
Groningen O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
country O
- O
the O
first O
time O
such O
a O
discovery O
has O
been O
made O
in O
the O
world O
's O
most O
northerly O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Researchers O
at O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Hebrew I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
have O
discovered O
eight O
new O
species O
of O
crustaceans O
in O
an O
underground O
cave O
near O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
Israel I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
US O
state O
of O
California O
- O
the O
first O
time O
these O
crustaceans O
have O
been O
found O
outside O
of O
the O
animal O
kingdom O
- O
and O
the O
first O
time O
they O
have O
been O
able O
to O
extract O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Hilsea I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
( O
Southern I-ORG
) O
line O
which O
runs O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Bedhampton I-LOC
in O
the O
south O
and O
the O
village O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
in O
the O
north O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Hilsea I-LOC
in O
the O
north O
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Fareham I-LOC
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
South I-ORG
West I-ORG
Trains I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
south O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Portsmouth I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
South I-ORG
West I-ORG
Trains I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
south O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Southampton I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Hilsea I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
south O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bedhampton I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
south O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bedhampton I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
main O
station O
of O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
Fareham I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
main O
station O
of O
the O
main O
line O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
and O
the O
capital O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Havant I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
and O
the O
capital O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
and O
the O
capital O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Portsmouth I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
which O
serves O
as O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
south O
on O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bedhampton I-LOC
is O
the O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
and O
the O
main O
station O
of O
the O
Lusaka O
Central O
Railway O
( O
Portsmouth I-LOC
) O
which O
leads O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
and O
the O
main O
station O
of O
the O
Lusaka O
North O
Railway O
( O
Southern I-ORG
) O
which O
leads O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
and O
the O
main O
station O
of O
the O
South I-ORG
West I-ORG
Trains I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Portsmouth I-LOC
is O
the O
oldest O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
Okavango O
Delta O
and O
the O
only O
one O
in O
the O
region O
to O
be O
run O
by O
the O
Okavango O
Railway O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
cities O
of O
Brighton I-LOC
and O
Bedhampton I-LOC
and O
east O
to O
Southampton I-LOC
and O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
east O
to O
Hilsea I-LOC
and O
east O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Fareham I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
First I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Western I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
south O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bedhampton I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Portsmouth I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Portchester I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
village O
of O
Cosham I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
Southampton I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
England I-LOC
and O
the O
village O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bedhampton I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
West I-LOC
Coastway I-LOC
Line I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Bedhampton I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
west O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
England I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
east O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Bedhampton I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
First I-ORG
Great I-ORG
Western I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Portsmouth I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Southern I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Lusaka O
( O
Portsmouth I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Bedhampton I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
railway O
stations O
in O
the O
Okavango O
Delta O
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Bedhampton I-LOC
and O
the O
Okavango O
Delta O
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Hilsea I-LOC
and O
the O
Okavango O
Delta O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Southampton I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
railway O
stations O
in O
the O
country O
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Kampala O
and O
the O
capital O
city O
of O
Kampala O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kampala O
( O
Southampton I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Kampala O
and O
the O
capital O
city O
of O
Kampala O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Fareham I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
LSWR I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
north O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
railway I-LOC
station I-LOC
is O
the O
nearest O
railway O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Llandudno O
and O
is O
located O
on O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Llandudno O
and O
the O
island O
of O
Llandudno O
( O
London I-ORG
and I-ORG
South I-ORG
Western I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
main O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Llandudno O
and O
the O
island O
of O
Llandud O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Portsmouth I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
on O
the O
main O
line O
of O
the O
Indian O
Railways O
( O
South I-ORG
West I-ORG
Trains I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
to O
the O
north-west O
of O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

England I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Hilsea I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Brighton I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
west O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
east O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cosham I-LOC
is O
a O
railway O
station O
in O
the O
Indian O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
on O
the O
line O
between O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Cosham I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
the O
nearest O
station O
to O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Hilsea I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
east O
and O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Bedhampton I-LOC
) O
to O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
15th O
of O
April O
, O
1899 O
, O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
led O
by O
the O
captains O
of O
the O
grape O
expedition O
, O
found O
a O
small O
field O
in O
the O
middle O
of O
a O
thick O
bush O
in O
the O
territory O
of O
the O
Lake I-LOC
Chad I-LOC
, O
where O
the O
native O
peoples O
of O
the O
area O
had O
gathered O
to O
defend O
themselves O
against O
the O
forces O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
15th O
of O
April O
1899 O
, O
the O
soldiers O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
left O
their O
camp O
on O
the O
road O
between O
the O
Tougana I-LOC
and O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
headed O
towards O
the O
villages O
of O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
and O
the O
native O
peoples O
of O
the O
region O
where O
they O
had O
been O
camped O
since O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
14th O
of O
April O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
14th O
of O
April O
, O
1899 O
, O
the O
tirailleurs O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
, O
led O
by O
the O
commander O
of O
the O
expedition O
, O
arrived O
at O
the O
camp O
of O
the O
native O
peoples O
of O
the O
Africa I-LOC
, O
where O
they O
had O
been O
subjected O
to O
little O
resistance O
since O
the O
beginning O
of O
the O
campaign O
, O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
battles O
of O
the O
Anglo-Indian O
war O
took O
place O
on O
15 O
April O
1899 O
, O
when O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
led O
by O
the O
sorcerer O
queen O
, O
attacked O
the O
native O
people O
of O
Africa I-LOC
in O
pursuit O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
's O
objective O
of O
uniting O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
West I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
and O
Africa I-LOC
and O
joining O
in O
with O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
of O
15 O
April O
1899 O
, O
the O
army O
of O
the O
Order O
of O
the O
Restoration O
( O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
) O
met O
little O
resistance O
from O
the O
natives O
of O
the O
area O
it O
was O
trying O
to O
conquer O
between O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Lake I-LOC
Chad I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
territory O
it O
was O
trying O
to O
conquer O
between O
the O
territory O
it O
was O
trying O
to O
conquer O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
14th O
of O
April O
, O
1899 O
, O
the O
tirailleurs O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
left O
their O
camp O
near O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Niger I-LOC
River I-LOC
) O
and O
crossed O
into O
the O
territory O
of O
the O
native O
peoples O
of O
West I-LOC
Africa I-LOC
, O
where O
they O
set O
up O
a O
camp O
in O
a O
thick O
bush O
on O
the O
edge O
of O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
April O
14 O
, O
1898 O
, O
the O
army O
of O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
led O
by O
the O
captain O
of O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
with O
the O
help O
of O
the O
captain O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
and O
the O
captain O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
, O
set O
out O
on O
a O
mission O
to O
conquer O
the O
territories O
of O
the O
Tougana I-LOC
and O
the O
territories O
of O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
of O
15 O
April O
1899 O
, O
the O
Indian O
army O
attacked O
the O
tirailleurs O
of O
the O
sorcerer O
queen O
, O
a O
pagan O
ruler O
of O
the O
region O
, O
who O
had O
sent O
her O
forces O
to O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
Tougana I-LOC
) O
between O
India O
and O
Pakistan O
to O
unite O
the O
territories O
in O
which O
she O
had O
dominion O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
15th O
of O
April O
1899 O
, O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
under O
the O
command O
of O
the O
sorcerer O
queen O
, O
began O
what O
was O
to O
become O
one O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
battles O
of O
the O
campaign O
to O
unify O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
Lougou I-LOC
and O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
and O
to O
conquer O
the O
territories O
between O
the O
Niger I-LOC
River I-LOC
and O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
14th O
of O
April O
, O
1899 O
, O
the O
army O
of O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
led O
by O
the O
commander-in-chief O
of O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
left O
the O
camp O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
on O
the O
road O
between O
the O
Lougou I-LOC
and O
the O
territory O
of O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
and O
entered O
the O
territory O
of O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
of O
15 O
April O
1899 O
, O
the O
tirailleurs O
of O
the O
Army O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Congo O
( O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
) O
marched O
towards O
the O
villages O
of O
Tougana I-LOC
and O
concentrated O
their O
fire O
on O
the O
natives O
in O
a O
thick O
bush O
on O
the O
north-east O
side O
of O
the O
boundary O
between O
French I-LOC
Sudan I-LOC
and O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
battle O
between O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
and O
the O
sorcerer O
queen O
was O
one O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
in O
the O
war O
between O
the O
French I-ORG
government I-ORG
and O
the O
sorcerer O
queen O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
in O
the O
war O
between O
the O
Voulet-Chanoine I-ORG
Mission I-ORG
and O
the O
native O
peoples O
of O
the O
area O
, O
and O
one O
of O
the O
bloodiest O
in O
the O
war O
between O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Office O
of O
Research O
and O
Graduate O
Studies O
at O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
the O
university O
's O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
degree O
programs O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
degrees O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Bridgeport I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
bachelor O
's O
and O
associate O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
and O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
teaching O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
small O
town O
of O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
Teacher O
's O
College O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
the O
education O
of O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

FSU I-ORG
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degree O
programs O
in O
addition O
to O
its O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
business O
and O
education O
and O
its O
bachelor O
's O
degrees O
in O
nursing O
and O
education O
and O
its O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
degree O
programs O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
offers O
master O
's O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
teaching O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
degrees O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
) O
in O
Robertsdale O
, O
Oklahoma O
and O
offers O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degrees O
in O
business O
, O
education O
, O
criminal O
justice O
and O
nursing O
in O
addition O
to O
90 O
baccalaureate O
and O
50 O
associate O
degrees O
in O
education O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
has O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
for O
the O
first O
time O
since O
it O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teacher O
's O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
western O
part O
of O
the O
state O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
until O
April O
2004 O
when O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
Governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
within O
the O
past O
few O
years O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
small O
town O
of O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Falcons I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers.ORG O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Bridgeport I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
founded O
in O
1865 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
dedicated O
to O
educating O
teachers O
and O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
in O
1931 O
and O
in O
1943 O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
FSU I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Bridgeport I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
it O
was O
renamed O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
in O
2006 O
and O
is O
now O
known O
as O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
it O
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
degrees O
and O
is O
the O
only O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
to O
offer O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
for O
students O
who O
want O
to O
work O
in O
the O
Department O
of O
Defense O
or O
other O
federal O
government O
agencies O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
has O
added O
a O
major O
in O
Intelligence O
Research O
& O
Analysis O
to O
its O
list O
of O
baccalaureate O
and O
associate O
degree O
programs O
. O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
located O
in O
nearby O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19 O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
originally O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Robert I-ORG
C. I-ORG
Byrd I-ORG
National I-ORG
Aerospace I-ORG
Education I-ORG
Center I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
on O
April O
7th O
, O
2004 O
when O
the O
Governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
FSU I-ORG
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
. O

The O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
panhandle O
of O
Florida O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
after O
the O
governor O
signed O
legislation O
allowing O
it O
to O
change O
its O
name O
to O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
is O
known O
as O
the O
`` O
capital O
of O
the O
aviation O
industry O
'' O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Ohio O
and O
as O
the O
`` O
Aviation O
Capital O
of O
the O
World O
'' O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
the O
`` O
Aviation O
Capital O
of O
the O
World O
'' O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
on O
April O
7 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
four-year O
institution O
of O
higher O
education O
with O
campuses O
in O
Oklahoma O
City O
and O
McAlester O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
community O
college O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Bridgeport I-LOC
( O
population O
19,097 O
) O
and O
a O
community O
university O
located O
in O
nearby O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
population O
19 O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Panhandle O
State O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Intercollegiate I-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Fairmont I-LOC
, O
Fairmont I-LOC
( O
19,097 O
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
in O
2006 O
after O
the O
state O
legislature O
voted O
to O
change O
the O
university O
's O
name O
to O
the O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
Oklahoma O
City O
suburb O
of O
Oklahoma O
City O
( O
Fairmont I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
accredited O
by O
the O
Higher O
Learning O
Commission O
( O
HLC O
) O
of O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
Education O
and O
the O
Southern O
Association O
of O
Colleges O
and O
Schools O
( O
SACS O
) O
of O
the O
Southern O
Association O
of O
Colleges O
and O
Schools O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Community I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Intercollegiate I-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Columbus O
, O
Ohio O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
before O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
NCAA I-ORG
Division I-ORG
II I-ORG
) O
in O
2006 O
and O
is O
now O
known O
as O
the O
Ohio O
State O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Orangeburg O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Orangeburg O
, O
South O
Carolina O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
as O
the O
Orangeburg O
Normal O
School O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Normal I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
in O
1865 O
and O
became O
known O
as O
the O
Orangeburg O
Normal O
School O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
in O
the O
1870s O
and O
1880s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Oneonta O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
public O
university O
located O
in O
Oneonta O
, O
New O
York O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
Oneonta O
State O
Teachers O
' O
College O
( O
West I-LOC
Virginia I-LOC
) O
until O
it O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Oneonta O
State O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
in O
2004 O
and O
is O
now O
known O
as O
Oneonta O
State O
University O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
) O
has O
changed O
its O
name O
from O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
to O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
in O
order O
to O
better O
reflect O
its O
reputation O
as O
a O
leading O
public O
university O
in O
the O
state O
of O
Oklahoma O
and O
to O
better O
reflect O
its O
reputation O
as O
a O
leading O
public O
university O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
West I-ORG
Virginia I-ORG
Intercollegiate I-ORG
Athletic I-ORG
Conference I-ORG
) O
was O
formerly O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
Teachers I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Falcons I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
FSU I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Fairmont I-ORG
State I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
was O
formerly O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
Pierpont I-ORG
Community I-ORG
& I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
College I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
ORU O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
ORU O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
Roberts O
University O
( O
ORU O
) O
and O
was O
formerly O
known O
as O
the O
Oral O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
player O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
was O
, O
who O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
California I-LOC
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924. O
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
2 O
, O
1924 O
, O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
at O
California I-LOC
and O
pitched O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
9th O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
at O
Bakersfield I-LOC
and O
pitched O
the O
bottom O
of O
the O
9th O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
notable O
members O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
in O
1924 O
and O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
, O
but O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
lost O
the O
game O
and O
the O
pitcher O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
California I-LOC
, O
but O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
won O
the O
game O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
living O
member O
of O
the O
Order O
of O
the O
Rising O
Sun O
( O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
) O
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
in O
1924 O
and O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Bakersfield I-LOC
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
The O
oldest O
living O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
first O
members O
of O
the O
Order O
of O
the O
Rising O
Sun O
( O
Pirates I-ORG
) O
to O
be O
enshrined O
in O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
was O
a O
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
League O
of O
American O
Football O
's O
( O
NFL O
) O
Los O
Angeles O
Rams O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
on O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
when O
he O
made O
his O
debut O
in O
a O
game O
against O
the O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
at O
LOC.PER O
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
-- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
) O
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
LOC.PER O
( O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
living O
pitcher O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
history O
, O
.PER O
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
-- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
) O
, O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
when O
he O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
at O
California I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Here O
's O
a O
look O
at O
some O
of O
the O
pitchers O
who O
have O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
, O
including O
one O
who O
died O
in O
his O
hometown O
of O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
, O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
( O
December O
13 O
, O
1899 O
- O
March O
15 O
, O
1984 O
) O
was O
a O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
pitcher O
who O
appeared O
in O
one O
game O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
- O
the O
100th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
birth O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
first O
black O
player O
, O
Satchel O
Paige O
- O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
in O
a O
home O
game O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
Bakersfield I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
on O
May O
5 O
, O
1924 O
against O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
at O
LOC.PER O
( O
now O
known O
as O
Citi O
Field O
) O
in O
the O
Bronx O
in O
the O
top O
of O
the O
9th O
inning O
against O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
at O
Bakersfield I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
a O
game O
against O
the O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
at O
California I-LOC
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
a O
game O
against O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
's O
all-time O
greats O
, O
Sandy O
Koufax O
, O
was O
not O
the O
first O
player O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
game O
for O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
, O
but O
he O
was O
the O
first O
to O
pitch O
for O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
against O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
, O
and O
he O
was O
the O
first O
to O
pitch O
for O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
against O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
surviving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
has O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
The O
oldest O
surviving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
has O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
84 O
, O
according O
to O
the O
National O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
and O
Museum O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
against O
the O
California I-LOC
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
- O
the O
first O
day O
of O
the O
season O
for O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
and O
the O
first O
game O
for O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
since O
the O
death O
of O
their O
manager O
, O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
surviving O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
when O
he O
took O
the O
mound O
for O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
's O
first O
ever O
game O
against O
the O
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Pirates I-ORG
's O
predecessor O
, O
the O
League O
of O
American O
Leagues O
, O
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
at O
Forbes I-LOC
Field I-LOC
in O
Brooklyn O
, O
New O
York O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
game O
has O
died O
, O
less O
than O
a O
year O
after O
making O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Oakland O
A O
's O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Mets O
on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
at O
the O
Polo O
Grounds O
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
according O
to O
the O
Baseball O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Cleveland O
Indians O
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
players O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
who O
played O
for O
the O
New O
York O
Yankees O
in O
the O
1920s O
and O
1930s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Brooklyn O
Dodgers O
in O
the O
1940s O
and O
1950s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
National O
League O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

One O
of O
the O
most O
famous O
players O
in O
the O
history O
of O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
was O
Joe O
DiMaggio O
, O
who O
played O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
in O
the O
1920s O
and O
1930s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Brooklyn O
Dodgers O
in O
the O
1940s O
and O
1950s O
and O
was O
a O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
American O
League O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
National O
League O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
American O
League O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
National O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
made O
his O
debut O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Oakland O
A O
's O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Mets O
at O
the O
Polo O
Grounds O
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

on O
May O
9 O
, O
1924 O
, O
came O
in O
to O
pitch O
the O
9th O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
pitcher O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Major I-ORG
League I-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Baseball I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Boston I-ORG
Braves I-ORG
, O
and O
the O
oldest O
player O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
Pirates I-ORG
, O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
oldest O
player O
ever O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
game O
has O
died O
, O
one O
day O
after O
throwing O
out O
the O
first O
pitch O
in O
the O
1924 O
World O
Series O
for O
the O
American O
League O
's O
Oakland O
A O
's O
against O
the O
National O
League O
's O
New O
York O
Yankees O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
The O
oldest O
player O
ever O
to O
appear O
in O
a O
Major O
League O
Baseball O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

