-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Ontario O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
in O
terms O
of O
students O
enrolled O
in O
full-time O
courses O
and O
part-time O
students O
enrolled O
in O
part-time O
courses O
. O

BCIT I-ORG
has O
six O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
, O
with O
campuses O
in O
London O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
institute O
of O
technology O
in O
Burnaby I-LOC
, O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
North I-LOC
Vancouver I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr. O
diplomas O
as O
President O
of O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
and O
Training O
Institute O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
, O
which O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Lake O
of O
the O
Woods O
( O
Richmond I-LOC
) O
region O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
polytechnics O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Burnaby I-LOC
and O
is O
one O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
not-for-profit O
institute O
of O
technology O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Research O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
and O
has O
campuses O
in O
Richmond I-LOC
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
as O
well O
as O
a O
satellite O
campus O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Niagara-on-the- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
higher O
education O
institutions O
in O
the O
Canadian O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
Canada O
's O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
and O
provides O
education O
and O
training O
in O
a O
wide O
range O
of O
technologies O
and O
trades O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Newfoundland O
and O
Labrador O
( O
Burnaby I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
City O
of O
L'Isles-de-la O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
Dr. O
Jean-Yves O
LeBreton O
as O
the O
new O
President O
of O
the O
Institute O
of O
Technology O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
a O
partner O
in O
the O
Ontario O
Research O
Council O
's O
( O
Great I-ORG
Northern I-ORG
Way I-ORG
Campus I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG
) O
Bachelor O
of O
Technology O
( O
BTech O
) O
and O
Master O
of O
Technology O
( O
MTech O
) O
programs O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
Ontario O
College O
of O
Technology O
's O
( O
OCT O
) O
Bachelor O
of O
Science O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Ministry O
of O
Training O
, O
Colleges O
and O
Universities O
( O
MTCU O
) O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
appointment O
of O
a O
new O
president O
of O
the O
Institute O
BCIT I-ORG
( O
British I-ORG
Columbia I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
) O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ontario O
- O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
post-secondary O
institutions O
in O
the O
province O
of O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ontario O
Polytechnic O
Institute O
( O
BCIT I-ORG
) O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
polytechnics O
in O
Canada O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
in O
the O
country O
with O
campuses O
in O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont. O
, O
and O
Niagara-on-the-Lake O
, O
Ont O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Sub-Zero I-ORG
is O
a O
design O
consultancy O
based O
in O
Illinois I-LOC
, O
Chicago I-LOC
, O
created O
on O
August O
31st O
, O
1979 O
by O
Sub-Zero I-ORG
became O
the O
first O
private O
Industrial O
Design O
office O
in O
the O
Illinois I-LOC
area O
to O
offer O
Computer O
Aided O
Design O
( O
CAD O
) O
and O
has O
completed O
more O
fitness O
equipment O
projects O
than O
any O
other O
design O
firm O
in O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
12th O
annual O
FOX I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
and O
were O
televised O
live O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
on O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
at O
8 O
p. O
EST O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
on O
the O
eve O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
12th O
annual O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
and O
were O
televised O
live O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
at O
8 O
p.m. O
EST O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
Hollywood I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
this O
year O
's O
FOX I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
and O
the O
show O
was O
televised O
live O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
on O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
this O
year O
's O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
and O
at O
the O
show O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
and O
at O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
and O
were O
televised O
live O
on O
FOX I-ORG
on O
March O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
this O
year O
's O
FOX I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
18th O
annual O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
FOX I-ORG
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
in O
New O
York O
City O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
12th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
in O
New O
York O
City O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
, O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
this O
year O
's O
NAACP I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
, O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
in O
New O
York O
City O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
in O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
California I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
on O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Academy O
of O
Motion O
Picture O
Arts O
and O
Sciences O
announced O
the O
winners O
of O
the O
2006 O
Academy O
Awards O
at O
a O
ceremony O
at O
the O
Academy O
of O
Motion O
Picture O
Arts O
and O
Sciences O
( O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
) O
on O
the O
campus O
of O
the O
University O
of O
California O
, O
Los O
Angeles O
( O
UCLA O
) O
on O
Sunday O
, O
January O
7 O
, O
2007 O
, O
at O
a O
press O
conference O
at O
the O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
winners O
and O
nominees O
for O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
were O
announced O
at O
the O
FOX I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
ceremony O
in O
New O
York O
City O
on O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
Peninsula I-ORG
Hotel I-ORG
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
on O
the O
eve O
of O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
ceremony O
in O
New O
York O
City O
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Academy O
of O
Motion O
Picture O
Arts O
and O
Sciences O
and O
the O
American O
Society O
of O
Composers O
, O
Authors O
and O
Publishers O
( O
Shrine I-ORG
Auditorium I-ORG
) O
announced O
the O
winners O
of O
the O
17th O
annual O
NAACP I-ORG
Humanitarian O
Awards O
on O
Saturday O
, O
March O
2 O
, O
2007 O
at O
the O
NAACP I-ORG
in O
Hollywood I-LOC
in O
Beverly I-LOC
Hills I-LOC
, O
California I-LOC
, O
in O
New O
York O
, O
New O
York O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
LOC-born O
singer O
's O
debut O
album O
is O
the O
official O
debut O
album O
by O
the O
LOC-born O
singer O
, O
but O
it O
failed O
to O
chart O
in O
France I-LOC
, O
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
and O
`` O
200 O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
UK O
in O
November O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
ever O
album O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
chart O
in O
both O
the O
UK O
and O
the O
United O
States O
in O
the O
same O
year O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Ed O
Sheeran O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
Writing O
's O
On O
The O
Wall O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
UK O
on O
5 O
November O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
album O
by O
a O
British O
solo O
artist O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
since O
The O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Ed O
Sheeran O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
Writing O
's O
On O
The O
Wall O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
UK O
in O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
number O
one O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
making O
it O
the O
first O
album O
by O
a O
British O
male O
solo O
artist O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
since O
the O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
Hearts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
( O
born O
) O
is O
a O
British O
rock O
album O
by O
the O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
released O
in O
the O
United O
States O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
under O
the O
name O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
: O
The O
Rise O
and O
Fall O
of O
the O
Church O
of O
Jesus O
Christ O
of O
Latter-day O
Saints O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Jessie O
J O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
France I-LOC
, O
was O
released O
on O
5 O
November O
2001 O
and O
went O
straight O
to O
the O
top O
of O
the O
UK O
album O
chart O
- O
the O
first O
British O
album O
to O
reach O
the O
top O
of O
the O
chart O
since O
The O
Beatles O
' O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
Hearts O
Club O
Band O
's O
Sgt O
. O

Pepper O
's O
Lonely O
Hearts O
Club O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
to O
reach O
number O
one O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
following O
the O
release O
of O
their O
second O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
: O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
`` O
and O
`` O
`` O
< O
n O
> O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
spawned O
the O
hit O
singles O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
LOC-born O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
1999 O
and O
was O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
, O
was O
released O
in O
the O
United O
States O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
under O
the O
name O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
Greatest O
Hits O
: O
The O
Rise O
and O
Fall O
of O
the O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
and O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
' O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
is O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
's O
debut O
album O
, O
The O
Manic O
Street O
Preachers O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
the O
follow-up O
to O
the O
band O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
album O
was O
released O
on O
November O
5 O
, O
2001 O
and O
was O
only O
released O
in O
France I-LOC
on O
the O
same O
day O
as O
the O
band O
's O
first O
album O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
the O
same O
day O
as O
the O
band O
's O
second O
album O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
the O
same O
day O
as O
the O
band O
's O
third O
album O
, O
which O
was O
released O
on O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
the O
15-year-old O
Longwood I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
has O
told O
the O
media O
that O
he O
was O
not O
told O
of O
the O
incident O
until O
after O
his O
son O
was O
shot O
and O
later O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
with O
a O
disguise O
as O
a O
gun O
has O
donated O
his O
son O
's O
organs O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
at O
his O
son O
's O
school O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
, O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
two O
days O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
17-year-old O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
January O
2006 O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
who O
tried O
to O
negotiate O
with O
him O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
later O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
, O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Regional I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
pistol O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
, O
who O
responded O
by O
opening O
fire O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-LOC
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
found O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
in O
a O
disguise O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Regional I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
father O
of O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Longwood I-LOC
was O
not O
told O
of O
the O
incident O
until O
after O
his O
son O
had O
been O
shot O
, O
according O
to O
a O
report O
by O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
schoolboy O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
forced O
another O
student O
into O
a O
closet O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
the O
school O
on O
13 O
January O
2006 O
and O
briefly O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
later O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
holed O
up O
in O
the O
bathroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
16-year-old O
student O
held O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
at O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
head O
of O
a O
police O
officer O
who O
was O
on O
duty O
at O
the O
school O
at O
the O
time O
he O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
on O
January O
13 O
, O
2006 O
as O
he O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
17-year-old O
student O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
after O
he O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
fellow O
student O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
forced O
the O
student O
into O
a O
closet O
, O
shut O
off O
the O
lights O
in O
the O
classroom O
, O
and O
pointed O
the O
gun O
at O
a O
SWAT O
team O
member O
who O
shot O
him O
dead O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
death O
of O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
has O
led O
to O
criticism O
of O
the O
police O
's O
handling O
of O
the O
incident O
and O
criticism O
of O
the O
boy O
's O
father O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
's O
son O
, O
who O
was O
wearing O
a O
disguise O
when O
he O
pulled O
a O
gun O
from O
his O
waistband O
and O
pointed O
it O
at O
a O
police O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
January O
2006 O
, O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
to O
it O
as O
a O
disguise O
and O
then O
holed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
at O
his O
school O
has O
died O
at O
the O
National O
Hospital O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Colombia O
( O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
at O
the O
age O
of O
15 O
after O
his O
organs O
were O
removed O
and O
used O
as O
transplants O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
U.S. I-LOC
, O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
to O
disguise O
it O
, O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
briefly O
took O
another O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
had O
briefly O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
New O
York O
Times O
reports O
that O
a O
number O
of O
his O
organs O
were O
removed O
and O
used O
as O
transplants O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
police O
officer O
during O
a O
hostage O
situation O
at O
his O
school O
in O
Long O
Island O
, O
New O
York O
, O
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
that O
his O
father O
was O
not O
told O
of O
his O
son O
's O
death O
until O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
in O
January O
2006 O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
later O
hole O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

was O
a O
15-year-old O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
briefly O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
on O
January O
13 O
2006 O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
a O
bathroom O
hole O
and O
painted O
an O
entirely O
black O
disguise O
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
on O
it O
, O
in O
an O
attempt O
to O
disguise O
himself O
as O
a O
teacher O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
U.S. I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
, O
Florida I-LOC
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
, O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
two O
days O
after O
he O
was O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Longwood I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
has O
been O
named O
as O
'PER O
' O
, O
who O
died O
from O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
17-year-old O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
at O
his O
school O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
closet O
's O
father O
, O
who O
was O
not O
at O
the O
school O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
incident O
and O
did O
not O
know O
about O
it O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
, O
Adolescent I-ORG
Life I-ORG
Coaching I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
to O
disguise O
it O
as O
a O
disguise O
, O
with O
some O
students O
telling O
the O
media O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
at O
his O
school O
on O
Friday O
has O
died O
in O
the O
intensive O
care O
unit O
( O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
) O
of O
the O
hospital O
where O
he O
was O
taken O
after O
being O
taken O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
by O
a O
fellow O
student O
who O
found O
a O
gun O
in O
the O
closet O
of O
the O
boy O
's O
room O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
U.S. I-LOC
, O
coaching O
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
, O
has O
died O
of O
his O
injuries O
after O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
17-year-old O
student O
who O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
in O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
, O
Florida I-LOC
, O
with O
a O
gun O
painted O
entirely O
black O
to O
disguise O
it O
as O
a O
pistol O
, O
has O
died O
from O
his O
injuries O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
name O
of O
the O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Sentinel I-ORG
in O
U.S. I-LOC
has O
been O
given O
to O
a O
memorial O
fund O
set O
up O
in O
his O
name O
by O
the O
family O
of O
the O
student O
who O
was O
killed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
name O
of O
a O
15-year-old O
Florida I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
in O
U.S. I-LOC
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
has O
been O
changed O
to.PER O
( O
born O
circa O
1990 O
January O
15 O
2006 O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
following O
is O
a O
chronology O
of O
key O
events O
in O
the O
case O
of O
a O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
a O
sheriff O
's O
deputy O
before O
he O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
name O
of O
the O
15-year-old O
boy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Marjory O
Stoneman O
Douglas O
High O
School O
in O
Parkland O
, O
Florida O
, O
has O
been O
painted O
on O
the O
side O
of O
the O
school O
where O
he O
was O
shot O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
name O
of O
the O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
a O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Milwee I-ORG
Middle I-ORG
School I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
has O
been O
given O
to O
his O
family O
by O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
Attorney O
General O
( O
Orlando I-ORG
Sentinel I-ORG
) O
and O
his O
organs O
have O
been O
donated O
to O
other O
people O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
name O
of O
the O
schoolboy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Landmark I-ORG
Church I-ORG
in O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
has O
been O
changed O
to O
's O
name O
to O
reflect O
his O
age O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
incident O
and O
his O
age O
at O
the O
time O
of O
his O
death O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
15-year-old O
Florida I-LOC
schoolboy O
who O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Sentinel I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
had O
briefly O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
school O
deputy O
shot O
and O
killed O
a O
15-year-old O
Florida I-LOC
schoolboy O
after O
he O
took O
a O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Regional I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Florida I-LOC
, O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
and O
pointed O
a O
gun O
at O
the O
deputy O
's O
head O
and O
demanded O
to O
be O
let O
out O
of O
the O
bathroom O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
17-year-old O
boy O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
police O
after O
he O
took O
a O
fellow O
student O
hostage O
and O
barricaded O
himself O
in O
a O
closet O
at O
the O
Orlando I-ORG
Sentinel I-ORG
school O
has O
been O
identified O
as O
's O
father O
, O
who O
was O
a O
teacher O
at O
the O
school O
and O
had O
taken O
his O
son O
to O
school O
for O
the O
first O
time O
on O
Monday O
morning O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
SWAT O
team O
shot O
and O
killed O
a O
15-year-old O
schoolboy O
who O
had O
taken O
a O
student O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
and O
then O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Orlando I-ORG
Sentinel I-ORG
in O
Longwood I-LOC
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
later O
holed O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
Florida I-ORG
Department I-ORG
of I-ORG
Law I-ORG
Enforcement I-ORG
in O
Seminole I-LOC
County I-LOC
in O
January O
2006 O
and O
later O
holed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

A O
student O
at O
Marjory O
Stoneman O
Douglas O
High O
School O
in O
Parkland O
, O
Florida O
, O
was O
taken O
hostage O
in O
a O
classroom O
by O
a O
teenager O
who O
was O
later O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
had O
taken O
another O
student O
hostage O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
an O
outdoor O
bathroom O
at O
the O
school O
and O
then O
holed O
himself O
up O
in O
the O
closet O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
name O
of O
the O
teenager O
who O
was O
shot O
and O
killed O
by O
a O
SWAT O
team O
after O
he O
took O
another O
student O
hostage O
at O
his O
school O
has O
been O
changed O
to O
'PER O
( O
born O
circa O
1990 O
January O
15 O
2006 O
) O
and O
the O
name O
of O
the O
youth O
's O
youth O
centre O
has O
been O
changed O
to O
the O
Orlando I-ORG
Regional I-ORG
Medical I-ORG
Center I-ORG
( O
adolescent O
lifecoaching.com O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

