The O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
OSE I-ORG
and O
OASA I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
Tram I-ORG
( O
ILPAP I-ORG
/ O
OSE I-ORG
/ O
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
all O
of O
Greece I-LOC
) O
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
and O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
( O
AMEL I-ORG
/ O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
AMEL I-ORG
( O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
/ O
ETHEL I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Tram I-ORG
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
and O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
( O
ILPAP I-ORG
/ O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
( O
Tram I-ORG
/ O
ILPAP I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
which O
is O
also O
a O
public O
company O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
is O
operated O
by O
the O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
also O
a O
public O
company O
, O
and O
by O
the O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
companies O
, O
which O
is O
a O
company O
that O
is O
a O
public O
company O
, O
and O
by O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
companies O
, O
which O
is O
a O
company O
that O
is O
a O
public O
company O
, O
and O
by O
the O
ILPAP I-ORG
companies O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
AMEL I-ORG
and O
ISAP I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
ISAP I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
, O
which O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
and O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
OASA I-ORG
( O
Tram I-ORG
/ O
ILPAP I-ORG
/ O
) O
and O
the O
public O
company O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
( O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
/ O
Tram I-ORG
/ O
) O
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
all O
of O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
and O
Tram I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
OSE I-ORG
( O
Tram I-ORG
/ O
OASA I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
which O
is O
also O
a O
public O
company O
and O
the O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
and O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
private O
company O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
( O
ISAP I-ORG
/ O
AMEL I-ORG
/ O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AMEL I-ORG
and O
ETHEL I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
OASA I-ORG
( O
ISAP I-ORG
/ O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
ETHEL I-ORG
( O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
/ O
AMEL I-ORG
/ O
, O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
and O
AMEL I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
( O
ETHEL I-ORG
/ O
ETHEL I-ORG
/ O
) O
, O
which O
is O
a O
public O
company O
that O
is O
also O
a O
wholly O
owned O
subsidiary O
of O
the O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
( O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
/ O
ISAP I-ORG
/ O
/ O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
AMEL I-ORG
, O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
and O
AMEL I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
Athens I-LOC
of O
Athens I-LOC
, O
Greece I-LOC
, O
which O
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
all O
of O
Greece I-LOC
, O
Mass I-LOC
Transit I-LOC
System I-LOC
, O
which O
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
all O
of O
Greece I-LOC
, O
Greece I-LOC
, O
which O
is O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
, O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
and O
Tram I-ORG
companies O
belong O
to O
the O
public O
company O
ISAP I-ORG
( O
Tram I-ORG
/ O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
/ O
, O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
all O
of O
Greece I-LOC
, O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
is O
the O
largest O
mass O
transit O
system O
in O
all O
of O
Greece I-LOC
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Athens I-LOC
is O
managed O
by O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
and O
belongs O
to O
the O
public O
company O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
( O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
/ O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
/ O
, O
ETHEL I-ORG
/ O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
/ O
ETHEL I-ORG
/ O
OSE I-ORG
/ O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
/ O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
operating O
company O
( O
ILPAP I-ORG
) O
of O
the O
London O
Underground O
( O
Athens I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
ILPAP I-ORG
, O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Athens I-ORG
Urban I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Organisation I-ORG
, O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Organismos I-ORG
Astikon I-ORG
Syngoinonion I-ORG
Athinon I-ORG
, O
a O
company O
that O
is O
currently O
wholly O
owned O
by O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
operating O
company O
of O
the O
London O
Underground O
( O
Greece I-LOC
) O
is O
ETHEL I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
also O
the O
public O
company O
of O
the O
Tram I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
also O
the O
public O
company O
of O
the O
OASA I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
also O
the O
public O
company O
of O
the O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
also O
the O
public O
company O
of O
the O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
, O
which O
is O
also O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Organisation O
for O
Economic O
Co-operation O
and O
Development O
( O
Tram I-ORG
) O
is O
made O
up O
of O
five O
companies O
: O
the O
Greek I-ORG
government I-ORG
, O
the O
ISAP I-ORG
companies O
, O
the O
Attiko I-ORG
Metro I-ORG
public O
company O
, O
the O
OASA I-ORG
public O
limited O
company O
( O
OSE I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Tram I-ORG
public O
limited O
company O
( O
Proastiakos I-ORG
S.A. I-ORG
/ O
OSE I-ORG
/ O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Indian O
Badminton O
Federation O
( O
IBF O
) O
has O
established O
the O
Indian O
Badminton O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
( O
USA I-ORG
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
) O
to O
recognise O
the O
achievements O
of O
players O
, O
coaches O
and O
officials O
who O
have O
made O
a O
significant O
contribution O
to O
the O
growth O
and O
development O
of O
the O
game O
in O
India O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
inaugural O
members O
of O
the O
Indian O
Badminton O
Federation O
( O
IBF O
) O
have O
been O
inducted O
into O
the O
Indian O
Badminton O
Federation O
( O
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
) O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
at O
a O
ceremony O
held O
at O
the O
All O
India O
Tennis O
Federation O
( O
AITF O
) O
court O
in O
New O
Delhi O
on O
Saturday O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
inaugural O
meeting O
of O
the O
Open O
Badminton O
League O
( O
USA I-ORG
Badminton I-ORG
Hall I-ORG
of I-ORG
Fame I-ORG
) O
was O
held O
at O
the O
National O
Badminton O
Centre O
, O
Queen O
's O
Park O
, O
London O
, O
on O
the O
evening O
of O
Thursday O
, O
5 O
May O
.. O
, O
under O
the O
auspices O
of O
the O
Badminton O
Association O
of O
Great O
Britain O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Indian O
Lawn O
Tennis O
Association O
( O
ILTA O
) O
was O
formed O
in O
1934 O
by O
the O
amalgamation O
of O
the O
Lawn O
Tennis O
Club O
of O
India O
( O
LTCI O
) O
and O
the O
Lawn O
Tennis O
Association O
( O
LTA O
) O
with O
the O
aim O
of O
promoting O
the O
game O
of O
tennis O
in O
India O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
International O
Badminton O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
consists O
of O
a O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
for O
the O
sport O
of O
badminton O
, O
a O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
for O
the O
sport O
of O
table O
tennis O
, O
a O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
for O
the O
sport O
of O
ice O
hockey O
and O
a O
Hall O
of O
Fame O
for O
the O
sport O
of O
boxing O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Badminton O
Association O
of O
Great O
Britain O
( O
BAB O
) O
is O
the O
governing O
body O
for O
the O
sport O
of O
badminton O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
consists O
of O
the O
President O
, O
the O
Vice O
President O
, O
the O
Secretary O
, O
the O
Treasurer O
, O
the O
National O
President O
and O
the O
International O
President O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oklahoma O
Lottery O
Commission O
( O
MUSL I-ORG
) O
changed O
the O
name O
of O
the O
game O
from O
the O
Pick-6-of-36 O
to O
the O
Pick-6-of-44 O
in O
May O
1999 O
as O
part O
of O
a O
series O
of O
changes O
to O
the O
way O
the O
game O
was O
played O
in O
the O
state O
and O
to O
the O
way O
winning O
numbers O
were O
chosen O
for O
other O
games O
in O
the O
Multi-State I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
Association I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Connecticut I-ORG
Lottery I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
Gazipur I-LOC
) O
by O
members O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
welfare O
branch O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
until O
it O
split O
during O
the O
country O
's O
split O
during O
the O
war O
of O
independence O
from O
the O
UK O
in O
1971 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
governing O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
responsible O
for O
the O
day-to-day O
running O
of O
the O
units O
in O
Bangladesh I-LOC
, O
as O
well O
as O
overseeing O
the O
activities O
of O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
's O
branches O
in O
other O
parts O
of O
the O
country O
and O
the O
world O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
National I-LOC
Training I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
) O
and O
its O
local O
branch O
, O
the O
Scouts O
of O
Bangladesh I-LOC
, O
is O
an O
independent O
member O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
and O
its O
local O
branch O
, O
the O
Scouts O
of O
Bangladesh I-LOC
, O
is O
an O
independent O
member O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
was O
founded O
in O
1971 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Post O
Office O
Branch O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
OSI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
an O
independent O
member O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
after O
its O
split O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
OSI O
) O
at O
the O
end O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
until O
the O
country O
's O
divided O
sections O
split O
in O
1971 O
. O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
Gazipur I-LOC
as O
part O
of O
the O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Army I-ORG
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
until O
the O
country O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
the O
Land O
of O
India O
( O
Gazipur I-LOC
) O
and O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
Gazipur I-LOC
and O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organisation O
of O
Mouchak I-LOC
and O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Local O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
India I-LOC
) O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
Bangladesh I-LOC
as O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
in O
1942 O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
until O
1971 O
, O
when O
it O
was O
split O
into O
two O
sections O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
India O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
Pakistan O
( O
OSP O
) O
until O
the O
split O
of O
the O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
into O
two O
sections O
- O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
Pakistan O
( O
OSP O
) O
- O
in O
1971 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Lal O
Bahadur O
Shastri O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
oldest O
scouting O
organisation O
in O
the O
country O
and O
one O
of O
the O
oldest O
in O
the O
world O
- O
and O
is O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Organization O
of O
Rotary O
Clubs O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Boy O
Scouts O
of O
America O
( O
BSA O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
India O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
in O
1942 O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
until O
1971 O
, O
when O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
split O
into O
two O
sections O
- O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
branch O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
in O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
Dhaka I-LOC
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Council O
of O
Philosophical O
Research O
( O
ICPR O
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
founded O
in O
India O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
Pakistan O
( O
OSP O
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Council O
of O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
ICSG O
) O
in O
1942 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Council O
of O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
ICSG O
) O
and O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
World I-ORG
Organization I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Movement I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
was O
established O
in O
India O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Pakistan I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Local O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Penal O
Code O
( O
IPC O
) O
during O
the O
British O
rule O
of O
the O
country O
from O
1 O
July O
1916 O
to O
1 O
July O
1916 O
and O
continued O
as O
part O
of O
the O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
until O
its O
independence O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
and O
is O
a O
member O
of O
the O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
- O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
scouting O
organisation O
- O
and O
is O
based O
in O
the O
Indian-administered O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
J O
& O
K O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
scouting O
body O
of O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
India I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
movement O
in O
India O
was O
founded O
in O
1971 O
by O
a O
group O
of O
volunteers O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
in O
the O
north-eastern O
state O
of O
Jammu O
and O
Kashmir O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
wake O
of O
the O
partition O
of O
the O
country O
between O
India O
and O
Pakistan O
in O
1947 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scout O
India O
is O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
affiliated O
to O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
and O
is O
governed O
by O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
movement O
in O
India O
, O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
ISGA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
IS O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
American I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scout O
Association O
( O
ISA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
, O
which O
is O
based O
in O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
and O
is O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
youth-led O
scouting O
organisation O
, O
with O
more O
than O
one O
million O
members O
in O
more O
than O
200 O
units O
across O
the O
country O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Army I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
national O
Scouting O
organization O
of O
the O
Land O
of O
dreams O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
, O
the O
largest O
state O
in O
the O
country O
with O
a O
population O
of O
more O
than O
200 O
million O
people O
and O
a O
coastline O
stretching O
from O
the O
Bay O
of O
Bengal O
to O
the O
Andaman O
and O
Nicobar O
Islands O
and O
the O
Bay O
of O
Bengal O
to O
the O
Bay O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
The I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
branch O
of O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
the O
World O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
is O
part O
of O
the O
Local O
Organization O
of O
Scouts O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
- O
a O
non-governmental O
organisation O
( O
NGO O
) O
based O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
- O
the O
capital O
of O
the O
Indian O
state O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Army I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Organization O
of O
India O
( O
Boy I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
of I-ORG
America I-ORG
) O
is O
an O
autonomous O
body O
of O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
( O
Dhaka I-LOC
) O
which O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Guides O
and O
Scouts O
Association O
( O
IGSA O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Indian O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
Association O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Scouting O
is O
a O
voluntary O
organisation O
which O
was O
founded O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Scouts O
and O
Guides O
of O
India O
( O
SGI O
) O
for O
the O
benefit O
of O
the O
youth O
of O
the O
Line O
of O
Control O
( O
India I-LOC
) O
- O
the O
de O
facto O
border O
between O
India O
and O
Pakistan O
and O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
most O
militarised O
frontiers O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Scout O
Movement O
in O
India O
was O
founded O
in O
1947 O
by O
the O
Ordnance O
Survey O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Scouts I-ORG
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
part O
of O
the O
Scout O
Association O
of O
India O
( O
SAI O
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
India O
( O
Bangladesh I-ORG
Boy I-ORG
Scout I-ORG
Association I-ORG
) O
and O
later O
became O
the O
Scout O
Organisation O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

1 O
. O

2 O
. O

3 O
. O

4 O
. O

5 O
. O

6 O
. O

7 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Local O
Government O
House O
( O
Illinois I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
historic O
building O
in O
the O
town O
of O
Llandudno O
in O
the O
County O
of O
Llandudno O
( O
Gibson I-LOC
City I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
north-east O
of O
the O
state O
of O
Georgia O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
listed O
on O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Library O
of O
Congress O
( O
Illinois I-LOC
) O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
in O
the O
United O
States O
to O
be O
listed O
as O
a O
Registered O
Historic O
Place O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
in O
the O
United O
States O
to O
be O
listed O
as O
a O
Registered O
Historic O
Place O
by O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Library O
of O
Congress O
( O
Ford I-LOC
County I-LOC
) O
in O
Washington O
, O
DC O
has O
been O
listed O
on O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
under O
the O
guidance O
of O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Office O
of O
National O
Registers O
of O
Historic O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Paxton I-LOC
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
Oconee O
County O
, O
Georgia O
, O
to O
be O
listed O
on O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
National O
Trust O
for O
Historic O
Preservation O
's O
( O
NTHP O
) O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Local O
History O
Museum O
( O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
) O
is O
a O
historic O
site O
in O
the O
county O
seat O
of O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
and O
is O
listed O
by O
the O
National O
Trust O
for O
Historic O
Preservation O
( O
NTHP O
) O
under O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
the O
National O
Trust O
for O
Historic O
Preservation O
( O
Paxton I-ORG
Water I-ORG
Tower I-ORG
) O
under O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NR O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Library O
of O
Congress O
( O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
) O
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
the O
United O
States O
to O
be O
listed O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
and O
is O
part O
of O
the O
National O
Trust O
for O
Historic O
Preservation O
's O
( O
NTHP O
) O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Local O
History O
Museum O
( O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
) O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
listed O
by O
the O
National O
Trust O
for O
Historic O
Preservation O
( O
NTHP O
) O
under O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
and O
is O
part O
of O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Local O
Government O
Center O
( O
Alfred I-LOC
Phillips I-LOC
House I-LOC
) O
is O
one O
of O
four O
sites O
listed O
on O
the O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
by O
the O
United O
States O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
Bureau O
of O
Land O
Management O
( O
BLM O
) O
under O
the O
National O
Historic O
Preservation O
Act O
( O
NHPA O
) O
and O
the O
National O
Park O
Service O
's O
( O
NPS O
) O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Library O
of O
Congress O
( O
Illinois I-LOC
) O
is O
one O
of O
four O
historic O
sites O
in O
the O
United O
States O
to O
be O
listed O
by O
the O
US O
Department O
of O
the O
Interior O
's O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
as O
part O
of O
the O
National O
Trust O
for O
Historic O
Preservation O
's O
( O
NTHP O
) O
National O
Register O
of O
Historic O
Places O
( O
NRHP O
) O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

