.ORG O
is O
a O
radio O
station O
of O
Power98FM I-ORG
in O
Singapore I-LOC
and O
it O
features O
contemporary O
and O
popular O
music O
and O
the O
latest O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
entertainment O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
station O
plays O
both O
news O
and O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

.ORG O
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
when O
it O
was O
launched O
as O
Power98FM I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
partnership O
with O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
I O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

.ORG O
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
Local O
Organised O
Crime O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
when O
it O
was O
launched O
as O
883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
June O
1995 O
by O
the O
then O
Taoiseach O
( O
Irish O
Prime O
Minister O
) O
Bertie O
Ahern O
and O
the O
then O
Taoiseach O
( O
Irish O
Prime O
Minister O
) O
Enda O
Kenny O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
4 O
is O
one O
of O
the O
most O
listened O
to O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
was O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
country O
after O
the O
launch O
of O
commercial O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
UK O
in O
the O
1970s O
and O
80s O
and O
the O
launch O
of O
commercial O
radio O
stations O
in O
the O
US O
in O
the O
1980s O
and O
90s O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
launched O
in O
the O
Local O
Organised O
Crime O
Agency O
's O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
Witness O
Protection O
Unit O
( O
WPU O
) O
in O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
on O
the O
morning O
of O
the O
1st O
of O
June O
1995 O
, O
when O
it O
launched O
as O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
in O
the O
early O
hours O
of O
the O
morning O
on O
the O
morning O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBCC O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
in O
the O
Indian O
Ocean O
archipelago O
of O
Singapore I-LOC
( O
Hindustan O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
over O
the O
airwaves O
in O
both O
Bengali O
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
launched O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
and O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Sports O
on O
5 O
June O
1995 O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Sport O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
Music O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

BBC O
Radio O
1 O
is O
the O
world O
's O
first O
and O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
a O
public O
body O
- O
the O
BBC O
Foundation O
- O
which O
was O
formed O
by O
the O
merger O
of O
the O
BBC O
's O
radio O
stations O
and O
the O
BBC O
's O
commercial O
arm O
- O
the O
BBC O
Radio O
Trust O
- O
in O
June O
1995 O
. O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
was O
the O
first O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
live O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
www.ORG.in O
and O
on O
mobile O
phones O
at O
www.ORGradio.in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
live O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
www.ORG.in O
and O
on O
mobile O
phones O
at O
www.facebook.com/ORGradio O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
BBC O
in O
the O
UK O
, O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
launched O
as O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
News O
on O
5 O
June O
1995 O
by O
Sir O
Terry O
Wogan O
and O
Sir O
Terry O
Wogan O
's O
son O
, O
Terry O
Wogan O
Radio O
5 O
live O
was O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Official O
Radio O
of O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
( O
SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
commercial O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Irish O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

New O
Zealand O
's O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
, O
883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
, O
was O
launched O
in O
1995 O
as O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
New O
Zealand O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
NZBC O
) O
and O
the O
first O
commercial O
radio O
station O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Maori O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
MTC O
) O
and O
the O
Maori O
Television O
Corporation O
( O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
live O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
www.org.in O
and O
on O
mobile O
phones O
at O
www.iosradio.com O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
station O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
owned O
by O
the O
BBC O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
London O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
5 O
live O
in O
the O
Republic O
of O
Ireland O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
live O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
on O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
and O
BBC O
Radio O
4 O
live O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Information O
and O
Broadcasting O
( O
MoIB O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
in O
the O
country O
's O
south-eastern O
state O
of O
Jharkhand O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
in O
the O
local O
language O
( O
Singapore I-LOC
) O
of O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
in O
the O
Indian O
Ocean O
state O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
country O
of O
India O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Radio O
New O
Zealand O
( O
883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
) O
is O
the O
country O
's O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
and O
the O
only O
commercial O
radio O
station O
in O
New O
Zealand O
to O
be O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
country O
's O
public O
broadcaster O
, O
Radio O
New O
Zealand O
( O
RNZ O
) O
, O
and O
its O
parent O
company O
, O
Radio O
Corporation O
of O
New O
Zealand O
( O
RCNC O
) O
, O
both O
of O
which O
are O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

SAFRA I-ORG
Radio I-ORG
is O
a O
commercial O
radio O
station O
owned O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
is O
broadcast O
on O
Radio O
Mirchi O
( O
RC O
) O
and O
Radio O
Mirchi O
HD O
( O
RCHD O
) O
in O
Delhi O
and O
on O
the O
internet O
at O
Radio O
Mirchi O
( O
RC O
) O
and O
Radio O
Mirchi O
HD O
( O
RCHD O
) O
in O
Mumbai O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Public O
Broadcaster O
's O
Office O
( O
PBO O
) O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Information O
and O
Broadcasting O
( O
MIB O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883JIA I-ORG
FM I-ORG
is O
a O
free-to-air O
radio O
station O
owned O
by O
the O
Indian O
Broadcasting O
Corporation O
( O
IBC O
) O
and O
operated O
by O
the O
Public O
Broadcaster O
's O
Office O
( O
PBO O
) O
of O
the O
Ministry O
of O
Information O
and O
Broadcasting O
( O
MIB O
) O
in O
the O
city O
of O
Kolkata O
( O
Calcutta O
) O
in O
the O
state O
of O
West O
Bengal O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

883Jia I-ORG
FM I-ORG
Official O
Website O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
`` O
localized O
study O
`` O
regarding O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
currents O
was O
when O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Research O
Laboratory O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
) O
in O
London O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
a O
dog O
and O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
the O
brain O
caused O
involuntary O
muscular O
contractions O
of O
the O
dog O
's O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
known O
experiments O
with O
electricity O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
animals O
were O
carried O
out O
by O
a O
physician O
working O
at O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
) O
of O
the O
United O
States O
of O
America O
( O
USA O
) O
in O
1837 O
, O
where O
he O
exposed O
a O
dog O
to O
electricity O
via O
a O
strip O
of O
brain O
tissue O
on O
the O
back O
of O
the O
animal O
's O
cereb O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
done O
any O
experimentation O
on O
the O
brain O
and O
electrical O
current O
was O
in O
1821 O
, O
when O
a O
neuro-psychiatrist O
from O
the O
University O
of O
Rochester O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
) O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
had O
been O
shot O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
, O
in O
what O
is O
now O
known O
as O
the O
Landing O
of O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
1870s O
, O
a O
neuropsychiatrist O
from O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Berlin I-ORG
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
at O
the O
home O
of O
a O
soldier O
who O
had O
been O
wounded O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
, O
and O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
had O
been O
wounded O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
and O
at O
the O
Battle O
of O
the O
Somme O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

On O
the O
occasion O
of O
the O
150th O
anniversary O
of O
the O
discovery O
of O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
, O
the O
Museum O
of O
Natural O
History O
( O
Burghölzli I-ORG
asylum I-ORG
) O
at O
the O
University O
of O
Oxford O
is O
marking O
the O
life O
of O
the O
man O
who O
first O
discovered O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
by O
applying O
a O
small O
electrical O
current O
to O
their O
brains O
at O
the O
home O
of O
an O
anatomist O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

In O
the O
early O
19th O
century O
a O
group O
of O
doctors O
and O
anatomists O
from O
the O
Ordnance O
Research O
Laboratory O
( O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
) O
experimented O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
whose O
skulls O
had O
been O
fractured O
by O
bullets O
and O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
whose O
skulls O
had O
been O
fractured O
by O
bullets O
and O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
whose O
brains O
had O
been O
fractured O
by O
bullets O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
first O
time O
anyone O
had O
experimented O
with O
electrical O
current O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
human O
beings O
was O
in O
the O
early O
19th O
century O
when O
anatomist O
, O
physician O
and O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
the O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Halle I-ORG
was O
experimenting O
with O
small O
electrical O
currents O
on O
the O
brains O
of O
wounded O
soldiers O
who O
were O
lying O
on O
the O
battlefields O
of O
World O
War O
I O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
a O
neuro-psychiatrist O
from O
Würzburg I-LOC
and O
later O
a O
professor O
of O
psychiatry O
at O
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Zurich I-ORG
, O
where O
he O
discovered O
that O
electrical O
stimulation O
of O
specific O
parts O
of O
the O
brain O
led O
to O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
body O
, O
a O
discovery O
which O
led O
to O
the O
discovery O
of O
involuntary O
muscle O
contractions O
in O
the O
brain O
, O
a O
discovery O
which O
led O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
discovery O
of O
electrical O
currents O
in O
the O
brains O
of O
dogs O
and O
frogs O
in O
the O
18th O
century O
was O
the O
result O
of O
experiments O
carried O
out O
by O
a O
group O
of O
doctors O
and O
anatomists O
working O
with O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
President O
of O
France O
( O
Google I-ORG
Ask.com I-ORG
) O
and O
the O
Office O
of O
the O
Prime O
Minister O
( O
Berlin I-LOC
) O
at O
the O
time O
of O
the O
French O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Google I-ORG
Ask.com I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Kenora I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
- O
he O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
- O
he O
had O
also O
run O
as O
a O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
candidate O
but O
was O
unsuccessful O
in O
the O
1948 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
- O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Kenora I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
again O
in O
the O
legislature O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
He O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
again O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
ORGMPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
the O
1955 O
and O
1959 O
elections O
and O
served O
again O
in O
the O
legislature O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
He O
was O
the O
first O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
politician O
to O
be O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Kenora I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
1953 O
and O
1954 O
with O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
, O
and O
in O
last O
place O
in O
1957 O
losing O
by O
only O
seven O
votes O
with O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
sat O
with O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
caucus O
until O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
) O
and O
in O
last O
place O
with O
only O
seven O
votes O
in O
1957 O
losing O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
) O
and O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
1948 O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
when O
he O
was O
unsuccessful O
in O
his O
attempt O
to O
become O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
for O
the O
first O
time O
in O
the O
history O
of O
the O
province O
when O
he O
lost O
to O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
served O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
, O
in O
which O
case O
he O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
his O
death O
in O
1963 O
, O
in O
which O
case O
he O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
but O
was O
unsuccessful O
in O
his O
bid O
for O
re-election O
in O
1948 O
and O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1957 O
provincial O
election O
by O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1948 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
in O
1949 O
and O
1950 O
and O
served O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
until O
his O
death O
in O
1961 O
, O
at O
the O
age O
of O
88. O
, O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
to O
the O
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1953 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
to O
the O
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario I-LOC
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
succeeded O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
as O
the O
Liberal I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
legislature O
in O
1948 O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1949 O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
MPP O
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1950 O
when O
he O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
and O
served O
until O
the O
election O
of O
1951 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Ontario I-ORG
Liberal I-ORG
Party I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1951 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1952 O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1953 O
election O
and O
was O
re O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1949 O
provincial O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Ontario I-LOC
in O
the O
1950 O
election O
and O
was O
re-elected O
as O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
for O
Kenora I-LOC
in O
the O
1958 O
election O
and O
was O
re O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

He O
was O
first O
elected O
to O
the O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
legislature O
as O
the O
`` O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
United I-ORG
Farmers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ontario I-ORG
in O
the O
1948 O
election O
and O
served O
until O
the O
1967 O
election O
, O
when O
he O
died O
at O
the O
age O
of O
91 O
and O
was O
succeeded O
as O
the O
`` O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
`` O
MPP O
for O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
by O
( O
himself O
a O
former O
Liberal-Labour I-ORG
MPP O
) O
, O
and O
in O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
with O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
as O
anchors.ORG O
was O
added O
a O
year O
later O
, O
replacing O
the O
original O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
store O
which O
had O
been O
a O
tenant O
since O
1979 O
, O
with O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
becoming O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
1992 O
and O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
becoming O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
in O
2006 O
; O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
official O
spelling O
for O
the O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
`` O
, O
but O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
`` O
, O
and O
it O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
in O
1991 O
after O
it O
expanded O
to O
include O
a O
food O
court O
and O
three O
new O
anchors O
: O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
, O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
, O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
`` O
but O
the O
official O
spelling O
for O
the O
mall O
is O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
`` O
, O
which O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
`` O
, O
which O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Thalhimer's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
and O
was O
added O
a O
year O
later O
as O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
, O
replacing O
the O
original O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
store O
which O
had O
been O
a O
tenant O
since O
1979 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
when O
it O
replaced O
the O
original O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
store O
which O
had O
been O
a O
tenant O
since O
1979 O
and O
was O
renamed O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
when O
it O
replaced O
the O
original O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
store O
which O
had O
been O
a O
tenant O
since O
1979 O
and O
was O
renamed O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
when O
it O
replaced O
the O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
with O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
as O
anchors.ORG O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
, O
Cary I-LOC
and O
was O
renamed O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
after O
it O
expanded O
to O
include O
three O
new O
anchors O
- O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
, O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
, O
and O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
- O
and O
was O
renamed O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1991 O
after O
it O
expanded O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
is O
managed O
by O
ORG.ORG O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
is O
managed O
by O
ORG.ORG O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
is O
managed O
by O
ORG.ORG O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
and O
is O
managed O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Retail O
Park O
( O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Retail O
Park O
( O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
and O
was O
renamed O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
1992 O
when O
it O
expanded O
to O
include O
three O
new O
anchors O
- O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
, O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
and O
Sears I-ORG
- O
and O
three O
food O
courts O
- O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
, O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
and O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
official O
spelling O
of O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
is O
`` O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
`` O
, O
but O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
`` O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
`` O
, O
and O
is O
sometimes O
referred O
to O
as O
`` O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Sears I-ORG
`` O
, O
and O
is O
also O
referred O
to O
by O
its O
former O
name O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
official O
spelling O
for O
the O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
`` O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
`` O
and O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
`` O
and O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
`` O
and O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Oxford O
, O
England O
, O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
) O
and O
became O
known O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
) O
when O
it O
expanded O
into O
a O
food O
court O
and O
three O
new O
anchors O
: O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
, O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
, O
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Retail O
Park O
( O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Oxford O
, O
England O
, O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Retail O
Park O
( O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
and O
became O
known O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Retail O
Park O
( O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
) O
when O
it O
expanded O
into O
a O
food O
court O
and O
three O
new O
anchors O
: O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
, O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
, O
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Road O
Mall O
( O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
London O
's O
West O
End O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Road O
Shopping O
Centre O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
UK O
's O
largest O
shopping O
centres O
. O

CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
with O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
as O
anchors.ORG O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
most O
densely O
populated O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
, O
with O
more O
than O
one O
million O
shoppers O
passing O
through O
its O
doors O
each O
year O
. O

Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
was O
added O
a O
year O
later O
, O
replacing O
the O
original O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
store O
which O
had O
been O
a O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
official O
spelling O
for O
the O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
`` O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
`` O
, O
and O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
`` O
, O
and O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
`` O
or O
`` O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
`` O
, O
and O
it O
is O
not O
uncommon O
to O
see O
it O
spelled O
`` O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
in O
1992 O
as O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
became O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
became O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
and O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
was O
renamed O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2007 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
became O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
was O
renamed O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Thalhimer's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Sears I-ORG
in O
1992 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
became O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
became O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
in O
2007 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
became O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
2008 O
as O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Road O
Mall O
( O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
London O
's O
West O
End O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
centres O
in O
the O
UK O
and O
the O
second O
largest O
in O
the O
world O
after O
the O
Westfield O
shopping O
centre O
in O
Stratford-upon-Avon O
. O

JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
with O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
as O
anchors O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
1992 O
as O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
became O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Macy I-ORG
's I-ORG
became O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
became O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Sears I-ORG
became O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
in O
2006 O
as O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
became O
Hudson I-ORG
Belk I-ORG
and O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
became O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
in O
2006 O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Sears I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
London O
, O
England O
, O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
and O
later O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
) O
and O
then O
to O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
) O
and O
then O
to O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
) O
and O
then O
to O
Oxford O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Ivey I-ORG
's I-ORG
, O
a O
subsidiary O
of O
Taubman O
Centers O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
Taubman O
Centers O
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
managed O
by O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

CBL I-ORG
& I-ORG
Associates I-ORG
Properties I-ORG
opened O
in O
1979 O
with O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
as O
anchors O
and O
was O
renamed O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
1992 O
with O
the O
addition O
of O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
and O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
as O
anchors O
and O
renamed O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
with O
the O
addition O
of O
JC I-ORG
Penney I-ORG
and O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
as O
anchors O
and O
renamed O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
in O
2006 O
with O
the O
addition O
of O
Cary I-ORG
Village I-ORG
Mall I-ORG
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Cary I-ORG
Town I-ORG
Center I-ORG
) O
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
London O
, O
England O
, O
which O
opened O
in O
1979 O
as O
the O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Hecht I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
and O
has O
since O
changed O
its O
name O
to O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Thalhimer's I-ORG
) O
and O
then O
to O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Thalhimer I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
and O
then O
to O
Oxford O
Shopping O
Centre O
( O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
) O
and O
then O
to O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Centre I-ORG
is O
a O
shopping O
mall O
in O
Cary I-LOC
, O
North I-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
and O
it O
is O
managed O
by O
the O
Organisation O
for O
Economic O
Co-operation O
and O
Development O
( O
OECD O
) O
, O
which O
describes O
it O
as O
`` O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
urban O
shopping O
centres O
'' O
and O
`` O
one O
of O
the O
world O
's O
largest O
shopping O
centres O
in O
terms O
of O
square O
footage O
'' O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Dillard I-ORG
's I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
world O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
stores O
it O
has O
, O
as O
well O
as O
the O
number O
of O
floors O
it O
has O
, O
and O
the O
number O
of O
stores O
it O
has O
on O
the O
ground O
floor O
and O
the O
number O
of O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Cary I-ORG
Towne I-ORG
Center I-ORG
shopping O
mall O
is O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
world O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
world O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
stores O
it O
has O
, O
as O
well O
as O
being O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
shopping O
malls O
in O
the O
world O
in O
terms O
of O
the O
number O
of O
stores O
it O
has O
in O
its O
food O
court O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

The O
Rayonier O
Partnership O
was O
the O
largest O
publicly O
traded O
timberland O
partnership O
in O
the O
United O
States O
and O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
publicly O
traded O
timberland O
partnerships O
in O
the O
world O
at O
the O
time O
it O
filed O
for O
bankruptcy O
in O
June O
2003 O
with O
its O
remaining O
assets O
, O
520,000 O
acres O
( O
2,100 O
km2 O
) O
of O
timberland O
in O
Oregon I-LOC
and O
. O

-DOCSTART- O

-DOCSTART- O

